{
    "name": "JPDB 35K",
    "cards": [
    {
      "question": "免状",
      "answer": "めんじょう",
      "meaning": "diploma, licence, license"
    },
    {
      "question": "新人類",
      "answer": "しんじんるい",
      "meaning": "new breed of humans (used to refer to the younger generation, who have different ideals and sensibil"
    },
    {
      "question": "官位",
      "answer": "かんい",
      "meaning": "office and rank, an official rank"
    },
    {
      "question": "核融合",
      "answer": "かくゆうごう",
      "meaning": "nuclear fusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "前肢",
      "answer": "まえあし,ぜんし",
      "meaning": "forefoot, forefeet, foreleg, forelimb"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼓",
      "answer": "つづみ",
      "meaning": "hand drum"
    },
    {
      "question": "鸚鵡返し",
      "answer": "オウムがえし,おうむがえし",
      "meaning": "parroting back, repeating (something one was told) like a parrot"
    },
    {
      "question": "有償",
      "answer": "ゆうしょう",
      "meaning": "(involving) payment, (involving) compensation, paying a fee"
    },
    {
      "question": "容れ物",
      "answer": "いれもの",
      "meaning": "container, case, receptacle, coffin, casket"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び石",
      "answer": "とびいし",
      "meaning": "stepping stones, stone skipping, ducks and drakes"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎧袖一触",
      "answer": "がいしゅういっしょく",
      "meaning": "(beating someone) hands down, with a single blow"
    },
    {
      "question": "幼気",
      "answer": "いたいけ",
      "meaning": "young and sweet, adorable, cute, tender, innocent, pitiful, touching, pathetic, helpless"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨子",
      "answer": "こっし,さいころ",
      "meaning": "main point, gist, essentials, bones (e.g. of an idea), pith, dice, die"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝寝坊",
      "answer": "あさねぼう",
      "meaning": "oversleeping, late riser"
    },
    {
      "question": "松風",
      "answer": "まつかぜ,しょうふう",
      "meaning": "(sound of) wind blowing through pine trees, (sound of) steam whistling in a kettle (at a tea ceremon"
    },
    {
      "question": "宇都宮",
      "answer": "うつのみや",
      "meaning": "Utsunomiya (city in Tochigi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "中島",
      "answer": "なかじま",
      "meaning": "island in a pond or river"
    },
    {
      "question": "覚る",
      "answer": "さとる",
      "meaning": "to perceive, to sense, to discern, to understand, to comprehend, to realize, to attain enlightenment"
    },
    {
      "question": "附属",
      "answer": "ふぞく",
      "meaning": "attached, belonging (to), included, enclosed, affiliated, annexed, associated, subordinate, incident"
    },
    {
      "question": "整備士",
      "answer": "せいびし",
      "meaning": "mechanic"
    },
    {
      "question": "扱き使う",
      "answer": "こきつかう",
      "meaning": "to work (someone) hard, to push (someone) around"
    },
    {
      "question": "概念的",
      "answer": "がいねんてき",
      "meaning": "general, conceptual"
    },
    {
      "question": "剛胆",
      "answer": "ごうたん",
      "meaning": "boldness, hardihood, courage, valour, valor"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨折り損",
      "answer": "ほねおりぞん",
      "meaning": "waste of labor or energy, waste of labour, vain effort"
    },
    {
      "question": "四つ葉",
      "answer": "よつば",
      "meaning": "plant having four leaves on one stalk"
    },
    {
      "question": "内務",
      "answer": "ないむ",
      "meaning": "internal or domestic affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "牡",
      "answer": "おす,おん,お",
      "meaning": "male (animal, plant), male, manly, brave, heroic, larger (of the two), greater, man, husband"
    },
    {
      "question": "生霊",
      "answer": "いきりょう,いきすだま,せいれい",
      "meaning": "vengeful spirit (spawned from a person's hate), doppelgänger, co-walker, wraith, mankind, souls, peo"
    },
    {
      "question": "指弾",
      "answer": "しだん",
      "meaning": "criticism, blame, rejection, disdain, contempt, flick (of the finger)"
    },
    {
      "question": "産婆",
      "answer": "さんば",
      "meaning": "midwife"
    },
    {
      "question": "操船",
      "answer": "そうせん",
      "meaning": "handling a ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "再臨",
      "answer": "さいりん",
      "meaning": "second coming, second advent"
    },
    {
      "question": "絞首台",
      "answer": "こうしゅだい",
      "meaning": "gallows"
    },
    {
      "question": "倦怠",
      "answer": "けんたい",
      "meaning": "weariness, fatigue, languor, boredom, tedium, ennui"
    },
    {
      "question": "惑",
      "answer": "わく",
      "meaning": "klesha"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚昧",
      "answer": "ぐまい",
      "meaning": "stupid"
    },
    {
      "question": "注進",
      "answer": "ちゅうしん",
      "meaning": "information, making a report (to a superior)"
    },
    {
      "question": "肌身",
      "answer": "はだみ",
      "meaning": "body"
    },
    {
      "question": "不正行為",
      "answer": "ふせいこうい",
      "meaning": "unfair practices, wrongdoing, malpractice, cheating, foul play"
    },
    {
      "question": "男親",
      "answer": "おとこおや",
      "meaning": "father, male parent"
    },
    {
      "question": "箱詰め",
      "answer": "はこづめ",
      "meaning": "boxing, packing into a box, something packed into a box"
    },
    {
      "question": "器械",
      "answer": "きかい",
      "meaning": "machine, mechanism, instrument, appliance, apparatus"
    },
    {
      "question": "辻斬り",
      "answer": "つじぎり",
      "meaning": "killing a passerby in order to test a new sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "炒飯",
      "answer": "チャーハン,ちゃあはん",
      "meaning": "Chinese-style fried rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "伽藍",
      "answer": "がらん",
      "meaning": "temple (esp. large one), monastery, temple building"
    },
    {
      "question": "拍動",
      "answer": "はくどう",
      "meaning": "pulsation, pulsebeat"
    },
    {
      "question": "痴",
      "answer": "ち,おこ",
      "meaning": "foolishness, fool, moha (ignorance, folly), foolish thing, stupid thing, absurdity"
    },
    {
      "question": "能う",
      "answer": "よう,あたう",
      "meaning": "well, properly, skillfully, often, how (could you), why (would you), to be able (to do), to be capab"
    },
    {
      "question": "通信機器",
      "answer": "つうしんきき",
      "meaning": "telecommunication equipment"
    },
    {
      "question": "希望的",
      "answer": "きぼうてき",
      "meaning": "wishful"
    },
    {
      "question": "差し",
      "answer": "さし",
      "meaning": "between (e.g. two people), face to face, hindrance, impediment, arrhythmic section of recitative in"
    },
    {
      "question": "加齢臭",
      "answer": "かれいしゅう",
      "meaning": "old person smell"
    },
    {
      "question": "中期",
      "answer": "ちゅうき",
      "meaning": "middle period, medium-term"
    },
    {
      "question": "十人十色",
      "answer": "じゅうにんといろ",
      "meaning": "several men, several minds, everyone has his own ideas and tastes, everyone has his own interests an"
    },
    {
      "question": "中等",
      "answer": "ちゅうとう",
      "meaning": "second grade, medium quality, average, middle class, secondary grade"
    },
    {
      "question": "軽音楽",
      "answer": "けいおんがく",
      "meaning": "light music, popular music"
    },
    {
      "question": "浜松",
      "answer": "はままつ",
      "meaning": "Hamamatsu (city)"
    },
    {
      "question": "買物",
      "answer": "かいもの,かいもん",
      "meaning": "shopping, purchased goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "仄",
      "answer": "ほの",
      "meaning": "slight, dim, faint"
    },
    {
      "question": "地殻変動",
      "answer": "ちかくへんどう",
      "meaning": "diastrophism, movement and deformation of the earth's crust, upheaval (e.g. in politics), seismic sh"
    },
    {
      "question": "睨める",
      "answer": "ねめる",
      "meaning": "to glare at, to scowl at, to glower at, to stare intensely at, to examine carefully"
    },
    {
      "question": "艘",
      "answer": "そう",
      "meaning": "counter for (small) boats"
    },
    {
      "question": "飼料",
      "answer": "しりょう",
      "meaning": "fodder, feed"
    },
    {
      "question": "剛毛",
      "answer": "ごうもう",
      "meaning": "bristle"
    },
    {
      "question": "何ぞ",
      "answer": "なんぞ,なにぞ,なぞ",
      "meaning": "something, what, why, how"
    },
    {
      "question": "目が出る",
      "answer": "めがでる",
      "meaning": "to have luck on one's side, to get lucky, to have one's eyes bulge out of one's head (with surprise)"
    },
    {
      "question": "色物",
      "answer": "いろもの",
      "meaning": "colored thing (clothing, fabric, paper, etc.) (coloured), variety shows"
    },
    {
      "question": "俵",
      "answer": "たわら,ひょう",
      "meaning": "straw bag, sack, bale, counter for sacks (of rice, potatoes, coal, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "体感温度",
      "answer": "たいかんおんど",
      "meaning": "effective temperature, wind-chill index (factor)"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗茶",
      "answer": "そちゃ",
      "meaning": "coarse, low-grade tea, tea (often used when offering someone a cup)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一日の長",
      "answer": "いちじつのちょう,いちにちのちょう",
      "meaning": "slight superiority (in knowledge, experience, ability, etc.), being slightly older"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒水晶",
      "answer": "くろすいしょう",
      "meaning": "black quartz"
    },
    {
      "question": "調略",
      "answer": "ちょうりゃく",
      "meaning": "plan, scheme, intention, project, design"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹奏楽",
      "answer": "すいそうがく",
      "meaning": "wind music, wind instrument music"
    },
    {
      "question": "教区",
      "answer": "きょうく",
      "meaning": "parish"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵科",
      "answer": "へいか",
      "meaning": "branch of the army"
    },
    {
      "question": "小水",
      "answer": "しょうすい",
      "meaning": "urine, urination, small quantity of water"
    },
    {
      "question": "色鉛筆",
      "answer": "いろえんぴつ",
      "meaning": "colored pencil, coloured pencil"
    },
    {
      "question": "生ける屍",
      "answer": "いけるしかばね",
      "meaning": "living corpse"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇形",
      "answer": "きけい,きぎょう",
      "meaning": "deformity, malformation, strange shape, unusual shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "前妻",
      "answer": "ぜんさい,こなみ",
      "meaning": "ex-wife, former wife, previous wife, first wife, legal wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "経済学",
      "answer": "けいざいがく",
      "meaning": "economics"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜け毛",
      "answer": "ぬけげ",
      "meaning": "fallen hair, combings, hair left on comb"
    },
    {
      "question": "不眠症",
      "answer": "ふみんしょう",
      "meaning": "sleeplessness, insomnia, wakefulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "不道徳",
      "answer": "ふどうとく",
      "meaning": "immorality, iniquity, impropriety"
    },
    {
      "question": "背水の陣",
      "answer": "はいすいのじん",
      "meaning": "fighting with one's back to the wall, having burnt one's bridges, last stand, from strategy of gener"
    },
    {
      "question": "魁",
      "answer": "さきがけ",
      "meaning": "pioneer, leader, taking the initiative, forerunner, harbinger, herald, leading an attack, charging a"
    },
    {
      "question": "心意",
      "answer": "しんい",
      "meaning": "mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "保険会社",
      "answer": "ほけんがいしゃ",
      "meaning": "insurance company"
    },
    {
      "question": "菜箸",
      "answer": "さいばし",
      "meaning": "long chopsticks (for cooking, serving, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "自家",
      "answer": "じか",
      "meaning": "one's own house, own, personal, autologous"
    },
    {
      "question": "初旬",
      "answer": "しょじゅん",
      "meaning": "first 10 days of the month"
    },
    {
      "question": "懐具合",
      "answer": "ふところぐあい",
      "meaning": "one's financial standing"
    },
    {
      "question": "無節操",
      "answer": "むせっそう",
      "meaning": "inconstant, unchastity, unprincipled"
    },
    {
      "question": "得意先",
      "answer": "とくいさき",
      "meaning": "(regular) customer, client, patron, clientele"
    },
    {
      "question": "仙術",
      "answer": "せんじゅつ",
      "meaning": "wizardry, secret of immortality"
    },
    {
      "question": "深山",
      "answer": "みやま,しんざん",
      "meaning": "mountain recess, deep in the mountains"
    },
    {
      "question": "教育実習",
      "answer": "きょういくじっしゅう",
      "meaning": "teaching practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "細工師",
      "answer": "さいくし",
      "meaning": "craftsman, artisan"
    },
    {
      "question": "終端",
      "answer": "しゅうたん",
      "meaning": "terminus, terminal, end edge"
    },
    {
      "question": "韜晦",
      "answer": "とうかい",
      "meaning": "hidden (talents, etc.), self-concealment, self-effacement"
    },
    {
      "question": "現代文",
      "answer": "げんだいぶん",
      "meaning": "modern Japanese, current written style"
    },
    {
      "question": "除夜の鐘",
      "answer": "じょやのかね",
      "meaning": "temple bell rung 108 times on New Year's Eve"
    },
    {
      "question": "拐かす",
      "answer": "かどわかす",
      "meaning": "to kidnap"
    },
    {
      "question": "書式",
      "answer": "しょしき",
      "meaning": "prescribed form (of writing), format"
    },
    {
      "question": "総計",
      "answer": "そうけい",
      "meaning": "total, sum"
    },
    {
      "question": "小顔",
      "answer": "こがお",
      "meaning": "small face (of a woman; generally considered attractive)"
    },
    {
      "question": "船橋",
      "answer": "ふなばし,せんきょう",
      "meaning": "pontoon bridge, temporary bridge made using ships, bridge (of a ship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "正史",
      "answer": "せいし",
      "meaning": "official history, authorized history"
    },
    {
      "question": "精妙",
      "answer": "せいみょう",
      "meaning": "exquisite"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏野菜",
      "answer": "なつやさい",
      "meaning": "summer vegetables"
    },
    {
      "question": "襲",
      "answer": "かさね",
      "meaning": "pile, heap, layers (e.g. of clothing), set (e.g. of boxes), course (e.g. of stones), counter for thi"
    },
    {
      "question": "産業革命",
      "answer": "さんぎょうかくめい",
      "meaning": "the Industrial Revolution"
    },
    {
      "question": "上申",
      "answer": "じょうしん",
      "meaning": "report to a superior"
    },
    {
      "question": "逝去",
      "answer": "せいきょ",
      "meaning": "death"
    },
    {
      "question": "大枠",
      "answer": "おおわく",
      "meaning": "general framework"
    },
    {
      "question": "意表",
      "answer": "いひょう",
      "meaning": "surprise, something unexpected"
    },
    {
      "question": "慶事",
      "answer": "けいじ",
      "meaning": "happy event, auspicious event, matter for congratulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "不信心",
      "answer": "ふしんじん",
      "meaning": "impiety, unbelief, infidelity"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜本的",
      "answer": "ばっぽんてき",
      "meaning": "drastic, radical"
    },
    {
      "question": "捌け口",
      "answer": "はけぐち,さばけぐち",
      "meaning": "outlet (e.g. for water or gas), market (for something), outlet (e.g. for excess energy), vent (e.g."
    },
    {
      "question": "漬かる",
      "answer": "つかる",
      "meaning": "to be submerged, to be soaked, to be pickled, to be well seasoned, to be totally immersed (in a cond"
    },
    {
      "question": "爪弾き",
      "answer": "つまはじき,つまびき,つめびき",
      "meaning": "black sheep (of a family), ostracism, playing with one's fingers (a guitar, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "汀",
      "answer": "なぎさ,みぎわ",
      "meaning": "water's edge, beach, shore, waterside"
    },
    {
      "question": "小父",
      "answer": "おじ",
      "meaning": "old man, mister"
    },
    {
      "question": "振袖",
      "answer": "ふりそで",
      "meaning": "long-sleeved kimono"
    },
    {
      "question": "内在",
      "answer": "ないざい",
      "meaning": "immanence, inherence, indwelling, intrinsic (cause)"
    },
    {
      "question": "慈母",
      "answer": "じぼ",
      "meaning": "affectionate mother"
    },
    {
      "question": "始点",
      "answer": "してん",
      "meaning": "point of departure, initial point, starting point"
    },
    {
      "question": "金ぴか",
      "answer": "きんぴか",
      "meaning": "golden and shiny, gaudy, gaudily decorated, brand spanking new, new and shiny"
    },
    {
      "question": "失する",
      "answer": "しっする",
      "meaning": "to lose, to miss, to forget, to be excessive"
    },
    {
      "question": "水漏れ",
      "answer": "みずもれ",
      "meaning": "(water) leak"
    },
    {
      "question": "型通り",
      "answer": "かたどおり",
      "meaning": "formal, proper, prescribed, conventional, stereotypical"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈍化",
      "answer": "どんか",
      "meaning": "becoming dull, slowing down"
    },
    {
      "question": "割り増し",
      "answer": "わりまし",
      "meaning": "extra (charge, fare, etc.), premium, bonus, (after a number) tenths increase"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍配",
      "answer": "ぐんばい",
      "meaning": "gourd-shaped war fan, referee's fan, stratagem, tactics"
    },
    {
      "question": "覚え込む",
      "answer": "おぼえこむ",
      "meaning": "to memorize, to fix in memory, to master"
    },
    {
      "question": "線上",
      "answer": "せんじょう",
      "meaning": "on the line, borderline"
    },
    {
      "question": "色魔",
      "answer": "しきま",
      "meaning": "sex maniac, seducer, libertine, Lothario, rake"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠浅",
      "answer": "とおあさ",
      "meaning": "shoal, wide shallow beach"
    },
    {
      "question": "総選挙",
      "answer": "そうせんきょ",
      "meaning": "general election (of the lower house)"
    },
    {
      "question": "三角錐",
      "answer": "さんかくすい",
      "meaning": "triangular pyramid"
    },
    {
      "question": "座敷牢",
      "answer": "ざしきろう",
      "meaning": "(Edo-period) room for confining criminals or lunatics"
    },
    {
      "question": "領海",
      "answer": "りょうかい",
      "meaning": "territorial waters"
    },
    {
      "question": "心停止",
      "answer": "しんていし",
      "meaning": "cardiac arrest"
    },
    {
      "question": "相対速度",
      "answer": "そうたいそくど",
      "meaning": "relative velocity"
    },
    {
      "question": "通用門",
      "answer": "つうようもん",
      "meaning": "side gate, side door, service entrance"
    },
    {
      "question": "狂態",
      "answer": "きょうたい",
      "meaning": "disgraceful behavior, disgraceful behaviour"
    },
    {
      "question": "陽性",
      "answer": "ようせい",
      "meaning": "positivity"
    },
    {
      "question": "針仕事",
      "answer": "はりしごと",
      "meaning": "needlework, sewing"
    },
    {
      "question": "一番風呂",
      "answer": "いちばんぶろ",
      "meaning": "freshly drawn bath, (taking) a bath before anyone else"
    },
    {
      "question": "入れ食い",
      "answer": "いれぐい",
      "meaning": "(fish) biting at every cast"
    },
    {
      "question": "永眠",
      "answer": "えいみん",
      "meaning": "eternal sleep, death"
    },
    {
      "question": "出来次第",
      "answer": "できしだい",
      "meaning": "as soon as completed"
    },
    {
      "question": "酵素",
      "answer": "こうそ",
      "meaning": "enzyme"
    },
    {
      "question": "顎鬚",
      "answer": "あごひげ",
      "meaning": "beard (esp. on the chin), goatee"
    },
    {
      "question": "願書",
      "answer": "がんしょ",
      "meaning": "(written) application, written request, petition, written prayer for a shrine or Buddhist temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "剝ぐ",
      "answer": "へぐ",
      "meaning": "to tear off, to peel off, to rip off, to strip off, to skin, to flay, to bark"
    },
    {
      "question": "寒冷",
      "answer": "かんれい",
      "meaning": "cold, coldness, chilliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "呵責",
      "answer": "かしゃく",
      "meaning": "blame, accusation, torture, maltreatment, pangs (of conscience)"
    },
    {
      "question": "付け回す",
      "answer": "つけまわす",
      "meaning": "to follow, to shadow, to hanker after, to hover around"
    },
    {
      "question": "動線",
      "answer": "どうせん",
      "meaning": "line of flow"
    },
    {
      "question": "菓子折り",
      "answer": "かしおり",
      "meaning": "box of cakes"
    },
    {
      "question": "借り出す",
      "answer": "かりだす",
      "meaning": "to borrow, to take out"
    },
    {
      "question": "法皇",
      "answer": "ほうおう",
      "meaning": "cloistered emperor, ex-emperor who has become a monk"
    },
    {
      "question": "食堂車",
      "answer": "しょくどうしゃ",
      "meaning": "dining car"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽土",
      "answer": "らくど",
      "meaning": "paradise"
    },
    {
      "question": "下民",
      "answer": "かみん,げみん",
      "meaning": "the masses, the lower classes, the common people"
    },
    {
      "question": "首長",
      "answer": "しゅちょう",
      "meaning": "head (of organization, organisation), chief, sheikh, emir"
    },
    {
      "question": "耐火",
      "answer": "たいか",
      "meaning": "fireproof"
    },
    {
      "question": "藤色",
      "answer": "ふじいろ",
      "meaning": "light purple"
    },
    {
      "question": "校歌",
      "answer": "こうか",
      "meaning": "school song"
    },
    {
      "question": "継ぎ接ぎ",
      "answer": "つぎはぎ",
      "meaning": "patching (clothing), darning, cobbling together, gathering"
    },
    {
      "question": "傍聴",
      "answer": "ぼうちょう",
      "meaning": "listening (to a lecture, hearing, parliament session, etc.), attending (without participating), sitt"
    },
    {
      "question": "沁み込む",
      "answer": "しみこむ",
      "meaning": "to soak into, to permeate, to penetrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "区画整理",
      "answer": "くかくせいり",
      "meaning": "land readjustment, town planning"
    },
    {
      "question": "値下げ",
      "answer": "ねさげ",
      "meaning": "cut in price"
    },
    {
      "question": "皮算用",
      "answer": "かわざんよう",
      "meaning": "over-optimistic calculation, counting one's chickens before they're hatched"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち見",
      "answer": "たちみ",
      "meaning": "watching while standing (e.g. a play)"
    },
    {
      "question": "住み込む",
      "answer": "すみこむ",
      "meaning": "to be a live-in employee, to live in, to live with"
    },
    {
      "question": "遼",
      "answer": "りょう",
      "meaning": "Liao (dynasty, 916-1125 CE), Khitan Empire"
    },
    {
      "question": "文机",
      "answer": "ふづくえ,ふみづくえ,ふんづくえ",
      "meaning": "Japanese-style writing desk"
    },
    {
      "question": "海運",
      "answer": "かいうん",
      "meaning": "maritime, marine transportation"
    },
    {
      "question": "羊水",
      "answer": "ようすい",
      "meaning": "amniotic fluid"
    },
    {
      "question": "食人",
      "answer": "しょくじん",
      "meaning": "cannibalism, anthropophagism"
    },
    {
      "question": "隣席",
      "answer": "りんせき",
      "meaning": "next seat, adjacent seat"
    },
    {
      "question": "終着",
      "answer": "しゅうちゃく",
      "meaning": "arriving at the final stop (of a bus, train, etc.), reaching the end of the line"
    },
    {
      "question": "珍事",
      "answer": "ちんじ",
      "meaning": "strange occurrence, unusual occurrence, unexpected occurrence, grave and unexpected occurrence"
    },
    {
      "question": "知識人",
      "answer": "ちしきじん",
      "meaning": "intellectual"
    },
    {
      "question": "門構え",
      "answer": "もんがまえ,かどがまえ",
      "meaning": "(in the) style of a gate, gate-equipped (house, shop, etc.), kanji 'gate' radical (radical 169)"
    },
    {
      "question": "高遠",
      "answer": "こうえん",
      "meaning": "noble, lofty"
    },
    {
      "question": "主上",
      "answer": "しゅじょう,しゅしょう",
      "meaning": "emperor"
    },
    {
      "question": "強制捜査",
      "answer": "きょうせいそうさ",
      "meaning": "compulsory investigation, compulsory search"
    },
    {
      "question": "碑",
      "answer": "いしぶみ,ひ",
      "meaning": "stone monument bearing an inscription (esp. memorial for future generations), stele, stela"
    },
    {
      "question": "恵比寿",
      "answer": "えびす,ゑびす",
      "meaning": "Ebisu, god of fishing and commerce"
    },
    {
      "question": "盆休み",
      "answer": "ぼんやすみ",
      "meaning": "Bon holidays, Bon holiday period (in mid-August)"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨床",
      "answer": "りんしょう",
      "meaning": "clinical (e.g. pathology, physiology)"
    },
    {
      "question": "傍迷惑",
      "answer": "はためいわく",
      "meaning": "nuisance to other people, inconvenience to others"
    },
    {
      "question": "安め",
      "answer": "やすめ",
      "meaning": "on the cheap side, comparatively cheap, wait tile which produces a winning hand with a lower score"
    },
    {
      "question": "一切合財",
      "answer": "いっさいがっさい",
      "meaning": "any and every thing, altogether, lock, stock, and barrel, the whole shooting match, the whole kit an"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き取り",
      "answer": "かきとり",
      "meaning": "writing down from other written material, writing kanji text from hiragana, transcription (of spoken"
    },
    {
      "question": "応急",
      "answer": "おうきゅう",
      "meaning": "emergency, first-aid"
    },
    {
      "question": "最多",
      "answer": "さいた",
      "meaning": "most (numerous), largest (number of)"
    },
    {
      "question": "五臓六腑",
      "answer": "ごぞうろっぷ",
      "meaning": "the internal organs"
    },
    {
      "question": "関心事",
      "answer": "かんしんじ,かんしんごと",
      "meaning": "matter of concern and interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "韻",
      "answer": "いん",
      "meaning": "rhyme, rhyme (of a Chinese character), rime"
    },
    {
      "question": "哀切",
      "answer": "あいせつ",
      "meaning": "pathetic, plaintive"
    },
    {
      "question": "短大",
      "answer": "たんだい",
      "meaning": "junior college, vocationally oriented two or three year post-secondary education institution"
    },
    {
      "question": "消音",
      "answer": "しょうおん",
      "meaning": "silencing (e.g. machine), muffling, muting (e.g. TV)"
    },
    {
      "question": "武士道",
      "answer": "ぶしどう",
      "meaning": "Bushido, samurai code of chivalry"
    },
    {
      "question": "敏い",
      "answer": "さとい",
      "meaning": "clever, smart, sharp (ear, etc.), sensitive, discerning"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁欲的",
      "answer": "きんよくてき",
      "meaning": "abstemious, austere"
    },
    {
      "question": "闊達",
      "answer": "かったつ,かつだつ",
      "meaning": "openhearted, frank, broad-minded"
    },
    {
      "question": "花摘み",
      "answer": "はなつみ",
      "meaning": "flower picking"
    },
    {
      "question": "多才",
      "answer": "たさい",
      "meaning": "talented"
    },
    {
      "question": "二本立て",
      "answer": "にほんだて",
      "meaning": "double feature (movie)"
    },
    {
      "question": "ローマ字",
      "answer": "ローマじ",
      "meaning": "Latin alphabet, Roman alphabet, rōmaji, romanized Japanese, system of transliterating Japanese into"
    },
    {
      "question": "長湯",
      "answer": "ながゆ",
      "meaning": "long, leisurely bath"
    },
    {
      "question": "半値",
      "answer": "はんね",
      "meaning": "half price"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜営",
      "answer": "やえい",
      "meaning": "encamping at night"
    },
    {
      "question": "白樺",
      "answer": "しらかば,しらかんば",
      "meaning": "Japanese white birch (Betula platyphylla var. japonica)"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺児",
      "answer": "いじ",
      "meaning": "orphan, child left by the deceased, abandoned child"
    },
    {
      "question": "立木",
      "answer": "たちき,りゅうぼく",
      "meaning": "standing tree, standing timber"
    },
    {
      "question": "一隅",
      "answer": "いちぐう,ひとすみ",
      "meaning": "corner, nook"
    },
    {
      "question": "風見鶏",
      "answer": "かざみどり",
      "meaning": "weather vane, fence-sitter, opportunist"
    },
    {
      "question": "総当たり",
      "answer": "そうあたり",
      "meaning": "round robin, having no losing tickets (of a lottery), brute force (in cryptography), using all combi"
    },
    {
      "question": "顕す",
      "answer": "あらわす",
      "meaning": "to represent, to signify, to stand for, to reveal, to show, to display, to express, to make widely k"
    },
    {
      "question": "吸い物",
      "answer": "すいもの",
      "meaning": "clear broth soup, with ingredients and garnish floating in and on it"
    },
    {
      "question": "避暑",
      "answer": "ひしょ",
      "meaning": "escaping the summer heat, going somewhere cooler during the summer, summering"
    },
    {
      "question": "色黒",
      "answer": "いろぐろ",
      "meaning": "swarthy, dark-skinned"
    },
    {
      "question": "年内",
      "answer": "ねんない",
      "meaning": "by the end of the year"
    },
    {
      "question": "下積み",
      "answer": "したづみ",
      "meaning": "goods piled beneath, lower layer, lowest social strata, bottom (of the ladder), low rank, obscurity"
    },
    {
      "question": "激安",
      "answer": "げきやす",
      "meaning": "dirt cheap, super cheap, bargain-priced"
    },
    {
      "question": "名誉毀損",
      "answer": "めいよきそん",
      "meaning": "libel, defamation, slander, character assassination"
    },
    {
      "question": "香川",
      "answer": "かがわ",
      "meaning": "Kagawa (prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大叔父",
      "answer": "おおおじ",
      "meaning": "granduncle"
    },
    {
      "question": "義勇軍",
      "answer": "ぎゆうぐん",
      "meaning": "volunteer army"
    },
    {
      "question": "元服",
      "answer": "げんぷく,げんぶく",
      "meaning": "male coming of age ceremony, for a woman to shave her eyebrows, dye her teeth and wear her hair in t"
    },
    {
      "question": "酢豚",
      "answer": "すぶた",
      "meaning": "sweet-and-sour pork"
    },
    {
      "question": "惑乱",
      "answer": "わくらん",
      "meaning": "bewilderment, confusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "臙脂色",
      "answer": "えんじいろ",
      "meaning": "dark red, deep red"
    },
    {
      "question": "急角度",
      "answer": "きゅうかくど",
      "meaning": "steep angle, acute angle"
    },
    {
      "question": "準拠",
      "answer": "じゅんきょ",
      "meaning": "basis, based on, conformance, conformity, authority (of), standard, reference"
    },
    {
      "question": "動詞",
      "answer": "どうし",
      "meaning": "verb"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄幸",
      "answer": "はっこう",
      "meaning": "unhappiness, sad fate, misfortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "人気取り",
      "answer": "にんきとり",
      "meaning": "bid for popularity, publicity stunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "二食",
      "answer": "にしょく,にじき",
      "meaning": "two meals, (eating) two meals a day"
    },
    {
      "question": "呈す",
      "answer": "ていす",
      "meaning": "to present, to offer, to give, to show, to display, to exhibit, to assume (e.g. a shape)"
    },
    {
      "question": "熾",
      "answer": "おき",
      "meaning": "embers, live charcoal"
    },
    {
      "question": "警察学校",
      "answer": "けいさつがっこう",
      "meaning": "police academy"
    },
    {
      "question": "母胎",
      "answer": "ぼたい",
      "meaning": "womb, uterus, parent body, base, basis"
    },
    {
      "question": "器物",
      "answer": "きぶつ,うつわもの",
      "meaning": "container, receptacle, utensil, implement, furniture, calibre, talent, ability, personal property"
    },
    {
      "question": "剣客",
      "answer": "けんかく,けんきゃく",
      "meaning": "fencer, swordsman"
    },
    {
      "question": "転院",
      "answer": "てんいん",
      "meaning": "transfer to a different hospital, hospital transfer"
    },
    {
      "question": "稿",
      "answer": "こう",
      "meaning": "manuscript, version, draft"
    },
    {
      "question": "宣戦",
      "answer": "せんせん",
      "meaning": "declaration of war"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠し球",
      "answer": "かくしだま",
      "meaning": "hidden ball trick, ace up one's sleeve, secret weapon"
    },
    {
      "question": "胴回り",
      "answer": "どうまわり",
      "meaning": "waist, girth, measurement around waist"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠因",
      "answer": "えんいん",
      "meaning": "underlying cause, indirect cause, remote cause"
    },
    {
      "question": "義務的",
      "answer": "ぎむてき",
      "meaning": "compulsory, obligatory, mandatory"
    },
    {
      "question": "神樹",
      "answer": "しんじゅ",
      "meaning": "god tree (Ailanthus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "推進剤",
      "answer": "すいしんざい",
      "meaning": "propellant"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣り場",
      "answer": "つりば",
      "meaning": "fishing place"
    },
    {
      "question": "大鷲",
      "answer": "おおわし",
      "meaning": "Steller's sea eagle (Haliaeetus pelagicus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "隣村",
      "answer": "りんそん,となりむら",
      "meaning": "neighboring village, neighbouring village"
    },
    {
      "question": "再突入",
      "answer": "さいとつにゅう",
      "meaning": "reentry"
    },
    {
      "question": "猥褻",
      "answer": "わいせつ",
      "meaning": "obscene, indecent, dirty, improper"
    },
    {
      "question": "山椒",
      "answer": "さんしょう,さんしょ",
      "meaning": "Japanese pepper (species of Sichuan pepper, Zanthoxylum piperitum), Japanese prickly ash"
    },
    {
      "question": "後目",
      "answer": "しりめ",
      "meaning": "backward glance, sidelong glance, faceless ghost with an eye in its rump"
    },
    {
      "question": "野卑",
      "answer": "やひ",
      "meaning": "vulgar, mean, base, coarse, crude"
    },
    {
      "question": "回覧板",
      "answer": "かいらんばん",
      "meaning": "circular notice (esp. distributed to households within a neighbourhood association)"
    },
    {
      "question": "男尊女卑",
      "answer": "だんそんじょひ",
      "meaning": "male domination of women, male chauvinism, subjection of women"
    },
    {
      "question": "立会い",
      "answer": "たちあい",
      "meaning": "presence (e.g. of an observer), observation, observer, witness, trading session (at an exchange)"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘱望",
      "answer": "しょくぼう",
      "meaning": "(having great) expectation, pinning one's hopes on"
    },
    {
      "question": "回し者",
      "answer": "まわしもの",
      "meaning": "spy, secret agent"
    },
    {
      "question": "子熊",
      "answer": "こぐま",
      "meaning": "small bear, bear cub"
    },
    {
      "question": "萩",
      "answer": "はぎ",
      "meaning": "bush clover, Japanese clover (any flowering plant of genus Lespedeza), dark red exterior with blue i"
    },
    {
      "question": "禿",
      "answer": "はげ,かぶろ,かむろ",
      "meaning": "baldness, bald head, idiot, moron, children's hairstyle of short untied hair, children with short un"
    },
    {
      "question": "新年会",
      "answer": "しんねんかい",
      "meaning": "New Year's party"
    },
    {
      "question": "禄",
      "answer": "ろく",
      "meaning": "stipend, reward"
    },
    {
      "question": "御苦労",
      "answer": "ごくろう",
      "meaning": "trouble (I have put you through), (your) hard work, thank you for your hard work, I appreciate your"
    },
    {
      "question": "肋",
      "answer": "あばら,ばら",
      "meaning": "rib, rib cage, boneless rib (esp. of pork or beef), boned rib"
    },
    {
      "question": "聴き取る",
      "answer": "ききとる",
      "meaning": "to catch (someone's words), to make out, to follow, to understand, to ask about (a situation, circum"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き手",
      "answer": "かきて",
      "meaning": "writer, painter, drawer, calligrapher, skilful writer, skilful painter"
    },
    {
      "question": "底面",
      "answer": "ていめん",
      "meaning": "bottom, underside, base"
    },
    {
      "question": "明文化",
      "answer": "めいぶんか",
      "meaning": "stipulation, stating clearly, documenting in writing, stating explicitly"
    },
    {
      "question": "標語",
      "answer": "ひょうご",
      "meaning": "motto, slogan, catchword"
    },
    {
      "question": "水回り",
      "answer": "みずまわり",
      "meaning": "part of a building where water is circulated (kitchen, bathroom, etc.), wet area"
    },
    {
      "question": "図解",
      "answer": "ずかい",
      "meaning": "schematic, schema, illustration, explanatory diagram"
    },
    {
      "question": "大恥",
      "answer": "おおはじ",
      "meaning": "humiliation, shame, loss of face"
    },
    {
      "question": "狛",
      "answer": "こま",
      "meaning": "Korea (esp. the Goguryeo kingdom or the Goryeo dynasty), (stone) guardian lion-dogs at Shinto shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "公主",
      "answer": "こうしゅ",
      "meaning": "princess"
    },
    {
      "question": "一揆",
      "answer": "いっき",
      "meaning": "uprising (esp. in Japan since middle ages, e.g. peasant uprising), revolt, insurrection, putsch, rio"
    },
    {
      "question": "読み切り",
      "answer": "よみきり",
      "meaning": "finishing reading, non-serialised story (e.g. in a magazine), complete story, breaks and pauses (in"
    },
    {
      "question": "腸壁",
      "answer": "ちょうへき",
      "meaning": "intestinal wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳兄弟",
      "answer": "ちきょうだい",
      "meaning": "foster sibling, foster brother, foster sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "幽玄",
      "answer": "ゆうげん",
      "meaning": "mysterious profundity, quiet beauty, the subtle and profound, yūgen"
    },
    {
      "question": "化粧室",
      "answer": "けしょうしつ",
      "meaning": "toilet, lavatory, powder room"
    },
    {
      "question": "消化器",
      "answer": "しょうかき",
      "meaning": "digestive organs"
    },
    {
      "question": "繁殖期",
      "answer": "はんしょくき",
      "meaning": "breeding season"
    },
    {
      "question": "罹患",
      "answer": "りかん",
      "meaning": "contracting a disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦中",
      "answer": "せんちゅう",
      "meaning": "during the war"
    },
    {
      "question": "唾棄",
      "answer": "だき",
      "meaning": "disdain, contempt, scorn, abhorrence"
    },
    {
      "question": "覗き穴",
      "answer": "のぞきあな",
      "meaning": "peephole, spyhole, inspection hole, observation window"
    },
    {
      "question": "公序良俗",
      "answer": "こうじょりょうぞく",
      "meaning": "public order and morals, social standards, public policy"
    },
    {
      "question": "炒る",
      "answer": "いる",
      "meaning": "to roast, to parch, to toast, to boil down"
    },
    {
      "question": "艶めく",
      "answer": "つやめく,なまめく",
      "meaning": "(for an object) to be shiny, to be glossy, (for a woman) to be alluring, to look sexy, to brim over"
    },
    {
      "question": "下戸",
      "answer": "げこ",
      "meaning": "non-drinker, someone who cannot drink"
    },
    {
      "question": "着付ける",
      "answer": "きつける",
      "meaning": "to put on, to wear, to be used to wearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "力試し",
      "answer": "ちからだめし",
      "meaning": "test of one's strength, test of one's ability"
    },
    {
      "question": "盗み取る",
      "answer": "ぬすみとる",
      "meaning": "to steal"
    },
    {
      "question": "海坊主",
      "answer": "うみぼうず",
      "meaning": "sea monster, green turtle"
    },
    {
      "question": "宝刀",
      "answer": "ほうとう",
      "meaning": "treasured sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "繁み",
      "answer": "しげみ",
      "meaning": "thicket, coppice, brushwood"
    },
    {
      "question": "未開拓",
      "answer": "みかいたく",
      "meaning": "undeveloped (area), unexplored (field of study), wild (areas), untapped area"
    },
    {
      "question": "研ぎ",
      "answer": "とぎ",
      "meaning": "polish, grinding, sharpening"
    },
    {
      "question": "葬送",
      "answer": "そうそう",
      "meaning": "funeral, burial rites, attendance at a funeral"
    },
    {
      "question": "印籠",
      "answer": "いんろう",
      "meaning": "inro, seal case, pill box, medicine case"
    },
    {
      "question": "虎穴",
      "answer": "こけつ",
      "meaning": "jaws of death, dangerous place, tiger's den"
    },
    {
      "question": "登頂",
      "answer": "とうちょう",
      "meaning": "climbing to the summit, summiting"
    },
    {
      "question": "累々",
      "answer": "るいるい",
      "meaning": "in heaps"
    },
    {
      "question": "添削",
      "answer": "てんさく",
      "meaning": "correction, looking over, touching up"
    },
    {
      "question": "着脱",
      "answer": "ちゃくだつ",
      "meaning": "attaching and detaching, putting on and removing"
    },
    {
      "question": "分業",
      "answer": "ぶんぎょう",
      "meaning": "division of labor, division of labour, specialization, specialisation, assembly-line production"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆三角形",
      "answer": "ぎゃくさんかくけい,ぎゃくさんかっけい",
      "meaning": "inverted triangle"
    },
    {
      "question": "佐渡",
      "answer": "さど",
      "meaning": "Sado (former province located on Sado Island in present-day Niigata Prefecture), Sado (island, Niiga"
    },
    {
      "question": "司法試験",
      "answer": "しほうしけん",
      "meaning": "bar examination"
    },
    {
      "question": "講習会",
      "answer": "こうしゅうかい",
      "meaning": "class, short course"
    },
    {
      "question": "内地",
      "answer": "ないち",
      "meaning": "within the borders of a country, domestic soil, inland area, Japan proper, as opposed to its oversea"
    },
    {
      "question": "迫",
      "answer": "せり",
      "meaning": "stage elevator, trapdoor"
    },
    {
      "question": "挽き肉",
      "answer": "ひきにく",
      "meaning": "minced meat, ground meat"
    },
    {
      "question": "養護教諭",
      "answer": "ようごきょうゆ",
      "meaning": "school nurse, nurse-teacher, health teacher"
    },
    {
      "question": "三角座り",
      "answer": "さんかくずわり,さんかくすわり",
      "meaning": "sitting on the floor grasping one's knees (as in a gym class)"
    },
    {
      "question": "双方向",
      "answer": "そうほうこう",
      "meaning": "two-way, bidirectional, interactive"
    },
    {
      "question": "実妹",
      "answer": "じつまい",
      "meaning": "biological younger sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "検定",
      "answer": "けんてい",
      "meaning": "official certification, official approval, inspection, verification, certification examination, lice"
    },
    {
      "question": "傍系",
      "answer": "ぼうけい",
      "meaning": "collateral family, subsidiary line, affiliate, coset"
    },
    {
      "question": "磐石",
      "answer": "ばんじゃく",
      "meaning": "huge rock, firmness, solidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄港",
      "answer": "きこう",
      "meaning": "stopping at a port"
    },
    {
      "question": "概略",
      "answer": "がいりゃく",
      "meaning": "outline, summary, gist, in brief"
    },
    {
      "question": "第三勢力",
      "answer": "だいさんせいりょく",
      "meaning": "a third force"
    },
    {
      "question": "吸い殻",
      "answer": "すいがら",
      "meaning": "cigarette end, cigarette butt, tobacco ashes"
    },
    {
      "question": "退任",
      "answer": "たいにん",
      "meaning": "retirement, resignation, stepping down"
    },
    {
      "question": "撒き餌",
      "answer": "まきえ",
      "meaning": "scattered animal feed, ground bait"
    },
    {
      "question": "枝毛",
      "answer": "えだげ",
      "meaning": "split end of hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "造語",
      "answer": "ぞうご",
      "meaning": "coined word, coinage, neologism"
    },
    {
      "question": "音域",
      "answer": "おんいき",
      "meaning": "singing range, register"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯型",
      "answer": "はがた",
      "meaning": "impression of the teeth, tooth mold (mould), tooth mark, teeth marks"
    },
    {
      "question": "灸",
      "answer": "きゅう,やいと",
      "meaning": "moxibustion"
    },
    {
      "question": "水軍",
      "answer": "すいぐん",
      "meaning": "navy (esp. the Japanese navy prior to the 1850s)"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏至",
      "answer": "げし",
      "meaning": "summer solstice"
    },
    {
      "question": "普通人",
      "answer": "ふつうじん",
      "meaning": "ordinary person"
    },
    {
      "question": "対地",
      "answer": "たいち",
      "meaning": "ground to ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉廷",
      "answer": "へいてい",
      "meaning": "adjourning court"
    },
    {
      "question": "呪言",
      "answer": "じゅごん,じゅげん",
      "meaning": "spell, curse, incantation"
    },
    {
      "question": "原生林",
      "answer": "げんせいりん",
      "meaning": "primeval forest, virgin forest"
    },
    {
      "question": "浪",
      "answer": "なみ,ろう",
      "meaning": "wave, ups and downs, person who has spent X years after graduating high school attempting to get adm"
    },
    {
      "question": "神前",
      "answer": "しんぜん",
      "meaning": "before god, before an altar"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁酒",
      "answer": "きんしゅ",
      "meaning": "abstinence from alcohol, temperance, prohibition of drinking"
    },
    {
      "question": "強火",
      "answer": "つよび",
      "meaning": "high flame (cooking), high heat, strong heat"
    },
    {
      "question": "腕自慢",
      "answer": "うでじまん",
      "meaning": "pride in one's strength or skill"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸し",
      "answer": "むし",
      "meaning": "steaming"
    },
    {
      "question": "問診",
      "answer": "もんしん",
      "meaning": "interview (with a doctor), history taking"
    },
    {
      "question": "奸計",
      "answer": "かんけい",
      "meaning": "evil design, crafty plan, plot"
    },
    {
      "question": "互い違い",
      "answer": "たがいちがい",
      "meaning": "alternate, alternation"
    },
    {
      "question": "不全",
      "answer": "ふぜん",
      "meaning": "partial, incomplete, imperfect"
    },
    {
      "question": "白壁",
      "answer": "しらかべ,はくへき",
      "meaning": "white plaster wall, tofu, bean curd"
    },
    {
      "question": "間髪",
      "answer": "かんぱつ,かんはつ",
      "meaning": "immediately, instantly, with nary a pause, without a moment's delay"
    },
    {
      "question": "辞む",
      "answer": "いなむ",
      "meaning": "to refuse, to decline, to deny"
    },
    {
      "question": "に於ける",
      "answer": "における",
      "meaning": "in, at, on, as for, regarding, with regards to"
    },
    {
      "question": "連座",
      "answer": "れんざ",
      "meaning": "implication (in a crime), involvement, sitting in a row (in the same seat)"
    },
    {
      "question": "援助交際",
      "answer": "えんじょこうさい",
      "meaning": "paid dating (esp. with an underage girl; oft. involving selling of sex), compensated dating"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵卒",
      "answer": "へいそつ",
      "meaning": "private (soldier), (common) soldier, ranks, rank and file"
    },
    {
      "question": "凡俗",
      "answer": "ぼんぞく",
      "meaning": "mediocrity, the masses, ordinary run of men"
    },
    {
      "question": "石礫",
      "answer": "いしつぶて,せきれき",
      "meaning": "throwing stone, sling stone, slingshot, pellet, pebble, small rock"
    },
    {
      "question": "快癒",
      "answer": "かいゆ",
      "meaning": "recovery, convalescence"
    },
    {
      "question": "輪投げ",
      "answer": "わなげ",
      "meaning": "quoits, ring toss"
    },
    {
      "question": "留め",
      "answer": "とめ",
      "meaning": "(a) stop (e.g. in a timber joint, or at the end of a kanji stroke), remaining (e.g. poste-restante),"
    },
    {
      "question": "耽溺",
      "answer": "たんでき",
      "meaning": "indulgence (e.g. in alcohol, women, etc.), debauchery, dissipation"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬漬け",
      "answer": "くすりづけ",
      "meaning": "overprescription, overmedication, drug dependence"
    },
    {
      "question": "曰く付き",
      "answer": "いわくつき",
      "meaning": "with an interesting history (story), with a shady history, with circumstances that are difficult to"
    },
    {
      "question": "在位",
      "answer": "ざいい",
      "meaning": "reign, being on the throne"
    },
    {
      "question": "軽犯罪",
      "answer": "けいはんざい",
      "meaning": "minor offence, minor offense, misdemeanor, misdemeanour"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼き直し",
      "answer": "やきなおし",
      "meaning": "adaptation (from), rebaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸筋",
      "answer": "きょうきん",
      "meaning": "pectoral (muscle)"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇っ怪",
      "answer": "きっかい",
      "meaning": "strange, wonderful, weird, outrageous, mysterious"
    },
    {
      "question": "謳い文句",
      "answer": "うたいもんく",
      "meaning": "catchphrase, promotional line, slogan"
    },
    {
      "question": "並々",
      "answer": "なみなみ",
      "meaning": "ordinary"
    },
    {
      "question": "原種",
      "answer": "げんしゅ",
      "meaning": "seed stock, seed grain, foundation seed, pure breed, original strain, ancestor"
    },
    {
      "question": "杵",
      "answer": "きね,しょ",
      "meaning": "mallet, pestle, pounder, vajra (mystical weapon in Hinduism and Buddhism)"
    },
    {
      "question": "元日",
      "answer": "がんじつ,がんにち",
      "meaning": "New Year's Day"
    },
    {
      "question": "外郭",
      "answer": "がいかく",
      "meaning": "outer wall (e.g. castle), outer block (enclosure), outline, contour"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂糖漬け",
      "answer": "さとうづけ",
      "meaning": "preserving in sugar, food preserved in sugar"
    },
    {
      "question": "心不全",
      "answer": "しんふぜん",
      "meaning": "heart failure"
    },
    {
      "question": "誇大妄想",
      "answer": "こだいもうそう",
      "meaning": "megalomania, delusions of grandeur"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛇蝎",
      "answer": "だかつ",
      "meaning": "serpent (snake) and scorpion, detestation"
    },
    {
      "question": "行脚",
      "answer": "あんぎゃ",
      "meaning": "pilgrimage, walking tour, travelling (on foot)"
    },
    {
      "question": "即金",
      "answer": "そっきん",
      "meaning": "spot cash, cash payment, immediate payment (in cash), cash down"
    },
    {
      "question": "心積もり",
      "answer": "こころづもり",
      "meaning": "anticipation, expectation, plan, preparation"
    },
    {
      "question": "忍耐強い",
      "answer": "にんたいづよい",
      "meaning": "persevering, very patient"
    },
    {
      "question": "斑鳩",
      "answer": "いかる,いかるが,はんきゅう",
      "meaning": "Japanese grosbeak (Eophona personata)"
    },
    {
      "question": "哲人",
      "answer": "てつじん",
      "meaning": "wise man, philosopher, sage"
    },
    {
      "question": "海人",
      "answer": "あま,うみんちゅ,かいじん",
      "meaning": "male diver (who collects shells, seaweed, etc.), fisherman, seashore dweller, sea god, Poseidon, Nep"
    },
    {
      "question": "代議士",
      "answer": "だいぎし",
      "meaning": "parliamentarian, member of a congress"
    },
    {
      "question": "驀進",
      "answer": "ばくしん",
      "meaning": "dash, rush"
    },
    {
      "question": "謀反人",
      "answer": "むほんにん",
      "meaning": "rebel, traitor"
    },
    {
      "question": "蠢かす",
      "answer": "うごめかす",
      "meaning": "to wriggle"
    },
    {
      "question": "合議",
      "answer": "ごうぎ",
      "meaning": "consultation, conference"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り替え",
      "answer": "とりかえ",
      "meaning": "swap, exchange"
    },
    {
      "question": "啜り泣く",
      "answer": "すすりなく",
      "meaning": "to sob"
    },
    {
      "question": "典雅",
      "answer": "てんが",
      "meaning": "refined, elegant, graceful, classic"
    },
    {
      "question": "卸し",
      "answer": "おろし",
      "meaning": "dropping, unloading, removing, grated vegetables, fruit, etc., grater, using new tools (or clothes,"
    },
    {
      "question": "模",
      "answer": "かたぎ",
      "meaning": "wooden printing block"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛根",
      "answer": "もうこん",
      "meaning": "hair root"
    },
    {
      "question": "詳らか",
      "answer": "つまびらか,つばひらか",
      "meaning": "detailed, clear"
    },
    {
      "question": "命脈",
      "answer": "めいみゃく",
      "meaning": "life, thread of life"
    },
    {
      "question": "適正価格",
      "answer": "てきせいかかく",
      "meaning": "fair or reasonable price"
    },
    {
      "question": "一服盛る",
      "answer": "いっぷくもる",
      "meaning": "to drug (someone, food, drink)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大病",
      "answer": "たいびょう",
      "meaning": "serious illness, dangerous disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "新しい女",
      "answer": "あたらしいおんな",
      "meaning": "liberated woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "漏る",
      "answer": "もる",
      "meaning": "to leak, to run out"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹を探る",
      "answer": "はらをさぐる",
      "meaning": "to probe someone's real intentions, to sound someone out, to try to fathom someone's thoughts"
    },
    {
      "question": "爪の垢",
      "answer": "つめのあか",
      "meaning": "dirt under one's fingernails, shred (of decency, etc.), scrap, bit, smidgen"
    },
    {
      "question": "太極",
      "answer": "たいきょく",
      "meaning": "taiji (in Chinese philosophy, the principle that embodies all potential things, incl. time and space"
    },
    {
      "question": "常夜",
      "answer": "とこよ,じょうや",
      "meaning": "perpetual night, continuing all night"
    },
    {
      "question": "渡来",
      "answer": "とらい",
      "meaning": "visit (from abroad), introduction (from abroad), importation"
    },
    {
      "question": "琉球",
      "answer": "りゅうきゅう",
      "meaning": "Ryukyu, chain of southwestern Japanese islands comprising Okinawa Prefecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "焙煎",
      "answer": "ばいせん",
      "meaning": "roasting (e.g. of coffee)"
    },
    {
      "question": "母の日",
      "answer": "ははのひ",
      "meaning": "Mother's Day (2nd Sunday of May)"
    },
    {
      "question": "橋頭堡",
      "answer": "きょうとうほ,きょうとうほう",
      "meaning": "bridgehead, beachhead"
    },
    {
      "question": "向い",
      "answer": "むかい",
      "meaning": "facing, opposite, across the street, other side"
    },
    {
      "question": "叙任",
      "answer": "じょにん",
      "meaning": "investiture"
    },
    {
      "question": "餓え",
      "answer": "うえ",
      "meaning": "hunger, starvation"
    },
    {
      "question": "押し合い",
      "answer": "おしあい",
      "meaning": "jostling, crowding"
    },
    {
      "question": "居住地",
      "answer": "きょじゅうち",
      "meaning": "residence, address"
    },
    {
      "question": "年を越す",
      "answer": "としをこす",
      "meaning": "to enter a New Year"
    },
    {
      "question": "希釈",
      "answer": "きしゃく",
      "meaning": "dilution"
    },
    {
      "question": "古今",
      "answer": "ここん,こきん",
      "meaning": "ancient and modern times, all ages, past and present"
    },
    {
      "question": "添え物",
      "answer": "そえもの",
      "meaning": "addition, supplement"
    },
    {
      "question": "事情通",
      "answer": "じじょうつう",
      "meaning": "having good knowledge of a certain matter, person who has good knowledge of a certain matter, inform"
    },
    {
      "question": "男冥利",
      "answer": "おとこみょうり",
      "meaning": "the good fortune to have been born male"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸が騒ぐ",
      "answer": "むねがさわぐ",
      "meaning": "to feel uneasy, to get into a panic, to feel excited, to have one's heart beat wildly, to have a pre"
    },
    {
      "question": "労する",
      "answer": "ろうする",
      "meaning": "to work, to labor, to labour, to put to work, to make (someone) work"
    },
    {
      "question": "反魂",
      "answer": "はんごん",
      "meaning": "reviving the dead, calling back the spirits of the dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "大凡",
      "answer": "おおよそ",
      "meaning": "about, roughly, approximately, generally, on the whole, as a rule, completely, quite, entirely, alto"
    },
    {
      "question": "訓",
      "answer": "おしえ,くん,くに",
      "meaning": "teaching, instruction, teachings, precept, lesson, doctrine, native Japanese reading of a Chinese ch"
    },
    {
      "question": "傾注",
      "answer": "けいちゅう",
      "meaning": "devotion, concentration"
    },
    {
      "question": "運動靴",
      "answer": "うんどうぐつ",
      "meaning": "sports shoes, sneakers"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄茶",
      "answer": "うすちゃ",
      "meaning": "weak matcha, light brown (color, colour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "善政",
      "answer": "ぜんせい",
      "meaning": "good government"
    },
    {
      "question": "淡水",
      "answer": "たんすい",
      "meaning": "fresh water (i.e. not salt water)"
    },
    {
      "question": "死後硬直",
      "answer": "しごこうちょく",
      "meaning": "rigor mortis"
    },
    {
      "question": "開口",
      "answer": "かいこう",
      "meaning": "opening, aperture (e.g. camera), opening one's mouth, beginning to speak, open, broad"
    },
    {
      "question": "倦む",
      "answer": "あぐむ,うむ",
      "meaning": "to get tired of (doing), to lose interest in"
    },
    {
      "question": "種々",
      "answer": "しゅじゅ,くさぐさ",
      "meaning": "various, a variety of, all kinds of, many, diverse"
    },
    {
      "question": "着崩れ",
      "answer": "きくずれ",
      "meaning": "worn out of shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "川幅",
      "answer": "かわはば",
      "meaning": "width of a river"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊ばす",
      "answer": "あそばす",
      "meaning": "to let (someone) play, to keep (someone) amused, to entertain, to leave idle, to not make use of, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "機能美",
      "answer": "きのうび",
      "meaning": "functional beauty, beauty of function, simplicity and elegance of design"
    },
    {
      "question": "定職",
      "answer": "ていしょく",
      "meaning": "occupation (i.e. field of regular employment), steady job, regular work"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き出し",
      "answer": "かきだし",
      "meaning": "beginning (of writing), opening passage (sentence, paragraph, etc.), written claim, bill"
    },
    {
      "question": "墓碑",
      "answer": "ぼひ",
      "meaning": "gravestone, tombstone"
    },
    {
      "question": "整理券",
      "answer": "せいりけん",
      "meaning": "numbered ticket (e.g. to determine order of service in shop, etc.), zone ticket, boarding ticket, bu"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹き矢",
      "answer": "ふきや",
      "meaning": "blowgun, blowpipe, dart"
    },
    {
      "question": "転ける",
      "answer": "こける",
      "meaning": "to fall over, to fall down, to fall, to collapse, to flop (e.g. of a play), to be a flop"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰布",
      "answer": "こしぬの",
      "meaning": "loincloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "入学金",
      "answer": "にゅうがくきん",
      "meaning": "matriculation fee"
    },
    {
      "question": "寒波",
      "answer": "かんぱ",
      "meaning": "cold wave"
    },
    {
      "question": "享楽的",
      "answer": "きょうらくてき",
      "meaning": "pleasure-seeking"
    },
    {
      "question": "自覚症状",
      "answer": "じかくしょうじょう",
      "meaning": "subjective symptoms, patient's complaints"
    },
    {
      "question": "皇太后",
      "answer": "こうたいごう,こうたいこう",
      "meaning": "Queen Mother, Empress Dowager"
    },
    {
      "question": "荼毘",
      "answer": "だび",
      "meaning": "cremation"
    },
    {
      "question": "棋士",
      "answer": "きし",
      "meaning": "professional shogi player, professional go player"
    },
    {
      "question": "挙兵",
      "answer": "きょへい",
      "meaning": "raising an army"
    },
    {
      "question": "搦め捕る",
      "answer": "からめとる",
      "meaning": "to catch and tie up, to apprehend, to arrest, to capture, to entangle, to trap, to get (something) s"
    },
    {
      "question": "検視",
      "answer": "けんし",
      "meaning": "autopsy, inquest, investigation of death"
    },
    {
      "question": "評論",
      "answer": "ひょうろん",
      "meaning": "criticism, critique"
    },
    {
      "question": "論評",
      "answer": "ろんぴょう",
      "meaning": "comment, criticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "物入れ",
      "answer": "ものいれ",
      "meaning": "place for storing things, container, compartment, closet, pocket"
    },
    {
      "question": "売り手",
      "answer": "うりて",
      "meaning": "seller, vendor"
    },
    {
      "question": "電話線",
      "answer": "でんわせん",
      "meaning": "telephone line"
    },
    {
      "question": "蟻地獄",
      "answer": "ありじごく",
      "meaning": "antlion (larva), doodlebug, antlion pit"
    },
    {
      "question": "一瞬間",
      "answer": "いっしゅんかん",
      "meaning": "moment, instant"
    },
    {
      "question": "万病",
      "answer": "まんびょう",
      "meaning": "all kinds of sicknesses"
    },
    {
      "question": "最後通牒",
      "answer": "さいごつうちょう",
      "meaning": "ultimatum"
    },
    {
      "question": "着信拒否",
      "answer": "ちゃくしんきょひ",
      "meaning": "blocking communications (from a phone number or an e-mail address)"
    },
    {
      "question": "強弁",
      "answer": "きょうべん",
      "meaning": "insisting (unreasonably), obstinate insistence"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋煩い",
      "answer": "こいわずらい",
      "meaning": "lovesickness"
    },
    {
      "question": "巨頭",
      "answer": "きょとう,おおあたま",
      "meaning": "leader, magnate, big head, large head, person with a large head"
    },
    {
      "question": "凝然",
      "answer": "ぎょうぜん",
      "meaning": "stock-still, motionless, frozen in place"
    },
    {
      "question": "番手",
      "answer": "ばんて",
      "meaning": "(yarn) count, nth place (e.g. in a race), nth position (e.g. in a starting lineup)"
    },
    {
      "question": "各位",
      "answer": "かくい",
      "meaning": "everyone, each and every one (of you), ladies and gentlemen"
    },
    {
      "question": "花札",
      "answer": "はなふだ",
      "meaning": "hanafuda, flower cards, playing cards consisting of 12 suits of 4 cards, each suit representing a mo"
    },
    {
      "question": "廻り",
      "answer": "めぐり,まわり",
      "meaning": "circumference, girth, tour, pilgrimage, circulation (e.g. of blood), rotation, making the rounds, sp"
    },
    {
      "question": "狂的",
      "answer": "きょうてき",
      "meaning": "insane, fanatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "更々",
      "answer": "さらさら",
      "meaning": "(not) at all, (not) in the least, (none) whatsoever"
    },
    {
      "question": "保湿",
      "answer": "ほしつ",
      "meaning": "moisturizing, maintenance of humidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "兼業",
      "answer": "けんぎょう",
      "meaning": "perusing as a side business, doing in addition to one's main work, running (businesses) simultaneous"
    },
    {
      "question": "と金",
      "answer": "ときん",
      "meaning": "promoted pawn"
    },
    {
      "question": "鰐",
      "answer": "わに",
      "meaning": "crocodile, alligator, shark"
    },
    {
      "question": "植物状態",
      "answer": "しょくぶつじょうたい",
      "meaning": "vegetative state"
    },
    {
      "question": "爪切り",
      "answer": "つめきり",
      "meaning": "nail clippers"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲殻類",
      "answer": "こうかくるい",
      "meaning": "crustacean"
    },
    {
      "question": "頸部",
      "answer": "けいぶ",
      "meaning": "neck (region)"
    },
    {
      "question": "自由恋愛",
      "answer": "じゆうれんあい",
      "meaning": "free love"
    },
    {
      "question": "気も無い",
      "answer": "けもない",
      "meaning": "showing no signs of, there being no hint of, unthinkable"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ平ら",
      "answer": "まったいら",
      "meaning": "perfectly level"
    },
    {
      "question": "実兄",
      "answer": "じっけい",
      "meaning": "biological older brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "対称",
      "answer": "たいしょう",
      "meaning": "symmetry, second person"
    },
    {
      "question": "海獣",
      "answer": "かいじゅう",
      "meaning": "marine mammal"
    },
    {
      "question": "颶風",
      "answer": "ぐふう",
      "meaning": "tornado, hurricane, typhoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "揺り椅子",
      "answer": "ゆりいす",
      "meaning": "rocking chair, rocker"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛火",
      "answer": "もうか,みょうか",
      "meaning": "raging flames, roaring flames, raging fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉門",
      "answer": "へいもん",
      "meaning": "closing of a gate, (Edo-period) house confinement"
    },
    {
      "question": "濛々",
      "answer": "もうもう",
      "meaning": "dense (e.g. fog, dust, etc.), thick, vague (as in being unable to think clearly), dim"
    },
    {
      "question": "性教育",
      "answer": "せいきょういく",
      "meaning": "sex education"
    },
    {
      "question": "予防線",
      "answer": "よぼうせん",
      "meaning": "defensive perimeter, defence line, defense line, defensive measures, precaution, safeguard, safety m"
    },
    {
      "question": "上滑り",
      "answer": "うわすべり",
      "meaning": "superficial, shallow, frivolous, careless, thoughtless, sliding along the surface of something, bein"
    },
    {
      "question": "自家用車",
      "answer": "じかようしゃ",
      "meaning": "private automobile"
    },
    {
      "question": "辛気",
      "answer": "しんき",
      "meaning": "mentality, mood, sentiment, feelings, fretfulness, tedium, irritation"
    },
    {
      "question": "男泣き",
      "answer": "おとこなき",
      "meaning": "man's weeping (esp. someone not prone to tears)"
    },
    {
      "question": "科する",
      "answer": "かする",
      "meaning": "to inflict, to impose (a fine, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "億万長者",
      "answer": "おくまんちょうじゃ",
      "meaning": "billionaire, multimillionaire, very rich person"
    },
    {
      "question": "足が出る",
      "answer": "あしがでる",
      "meaning": "to exceed the budget, to overrun the budget, to have a deficit, to go into the red, to have a secret"
    },
    {
      "question": "松原",
      "answer": "まつばら",
      "meaning": "pine grove"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰陽道",
      "answer": "おんみょうどう,おんようどう",
      "meaning": "Onmyōdō, way of Yin and Yang, occult divination system based on the Taoist theory of the five elemen"
    },
    {
      "question": "アホ毛",
      "answer": "アホげ",
      "meaning": "frizz, short tufts springing up from hair surface here and there, kink, idiot hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "受刑者",
      "answer": "じゅけいしゃ",
      "meaning": "prisoner, convict"
    },
    {
      "question": "核弾頭",
      "answer": "かくだんとう",
      "meaning": "nuclear warhead"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶無",
      "answer": "ぜつむ",
      "meaning": "nothing, nil, naught, nought"
    },
    {
      "question": "三面",
      "answer": "さんめん",
      "meaning": "three sides, three faces, page three (of a newspaper)"
    },
    {
      "question": "月明り",
      "answer": "つきあかり",
      "meaning": "moonlight"
    },
    {
      "question": "一子相伝",
      "answer": "いっしそうでん",
      "meaning": "transmission of the secrets of an art, craft, trade or learning from father to only one child"
    },
    {
      "question": "保冷",
      "answer": "ほれい",
      "meaning": "keeping (something) cool"
    },
    {
      "question": "転居",
      "answer": "てんきょ",
      "meaning": "moving, changing residence, change of address"
    },
    {
      "question": "倹約",
      "answer": "けんやく",
      "meaning": "thrift, economy, frugality"
    },
    {
      "question": "用無し",
      "answer": "ようなし",
      "meaning": "idle, useless"
    },
    {
      "question": "気が張る",
      "answer": "きがはる",
      "meaning": "to strain every nerve, to feel nervous"
    },
    {
      "question": "白子",
      "answer": "しらこ,しろこ,しらす",
      "meaning": "soft roe, milt, albino, whitebait, elver (young eel)"
    },
    {
      "question": "笑声",
      "answer": "しょうせい",
      "meaning": "laugh, laughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍港",
      "answer": "ぐんこう",
      "meaning": "naval port, naval station"
    },
    {
      "question": "腺",
      "answer": "せん",
      "meaning": "gland"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧壊",
      "answer": "あっかい",
      "meaning": "crushing, breaking by applying pressure"
    },
    {
      "question": "鹿児島",
      "answer": "かごしま",
      "meaning": "Kagoshima (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "揮発",
      "answer": "きはつ",
      "meaning": "volatilization, volatilisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮汁",
      "answer": "にじる",
      "meaning": "broth"
    },
    {
      "question": "成婚",
      "answer": "せいこん",
      "meaning": "marriage, wedding"
    },
    {
      "question": "不断",
      "answer": "ふだん",
      "meaning": "constant, persistent, unremitting, ceaseless, indecisiveness, usual, normal, everyday, habitual, ord"
    },
    {
      "question": "野戦病院",
      "answer": "やせんびょういん",
      "meaning": "field hospital"
    },
    {
      "question": "売れ筋",
      "answer": "うれすじ",
      "meaning": "popular line (of products), best-selling line, hot sellers"
    },
    {
      "question": "燦然",
      "answer": "さんぜん",
      "meaning": "brilliant, radiant, bright, sparkling"
    },
    {
      "question": "おっ死ぬ",
      "answer": "おっちぬ",
      "meaning": "to die"
    },
    {
      "question": "子離れ",
      "answer": "こばなれ",
      "meaning": "parents' ability (or inability) to let go of their children"
    },
    {
      "question": "脇が甘い",
      "answer": "わきがあまい",
      "meaning": "poor at preventing one's opponent from getting an underarm grip, having weak defenses, off one's gua"
    },
    {
      "question": "豪気",
      "answer": "ごうき,ごうぎ",
      "meaning": "sturdy spirit, bold, daring, brave, valiant, undaunted, stouthearted, great, grand, obstinate, stubb"
    },
    {
      "question": "奥の院",
      "answer": "おくのいん",
      "meaning": "inner sanctuary, inner shrine, sanctum sanctorum, holy of holies, place behind main hall of a temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪男",
      "answer": "ゆきおとこ",
      "meaning": "abominable snowman, yeti"
    },
    {
      "question": "陸橋",
      "answer": "りっきょう,りくきょう",
      "meaning": "viaduct, overhead bridge, overpass, land bridge (biogeography)"
    },
    {
      "question": "桑",
      "answer": "くわ",
      "meaning": "mulberry (tree)"
    },
    {
      "question": "事変",
      "answer": "じへん",
      "meaning": "accident, disaster, incident, uprising, emergency"
    },
    {
      "question": "盗掘",
      "answer": "とうくつ",
      "meaning": "illegal digging, illegal mining, grave robbing, tomb robbing"
    },
    {
      "question": "大胸筋",
      "answer": "だいきょうきん",
      "meaning": "pectoralis major muscle"
    },
    {
      "question": "公人",
      "answer": "こうじん",
      "meaning": "public character"
    },
    {
      "question": "妄念",
      "answer": "もうねん",
      "meaning": "conviction based on flawed ideas, obstructive thought"
    },
    {
      "question": "木偶の坊",
      "answer": "でくのぼう",
      "meaning": "wooden doll, blockhead, good-for-nothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "徴用",
      "answer": "ちょうよう",
      "meaning": "drafting, requisition, impressment, commandeering, expropriation"
    },
    {
      "question": "履物",
      "answer": "はきもの",
      "meaning": "footwear, footgear, shoes"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛繕い",
      "answer": "けづくろい",
      "meaning": "grooming oneself (esp. animals), mutual grooming (e.g. monkeys), social grooming, personal grooming"
    },
    {
      "question": "吊り目",
      "answer": "つりめ",
      "meaning": "slant eyes, almond-shaped eyes, eyes that are turned up at the corners"
    },
    {
      "question": "絨毯爆撃",
      "answer": "じゅうたんばくげき",
      "meaning": "carpet bombing"
    },
    {
      "question": "眉唾物",
      "answer": "まゆつばもの",
      "meaning": "dubious tale, cock-and-bull story, questionable information"
    },
    {
      "question": "社会問題",
      "answer": "しゃかいもんだい",
      "meaning": "social problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "足が付く",
      "answer": "あしがつく",
      "meaning": "to be traced (of a criminal), to be tracked, to have a (male) lover"
    },
    {
      "question": "国務",
      "answer": "こくむ",
      "meaning": "affairs of state"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬼ヶ島",
      "answer": "おにがしま",
      "meaning": "mythological island of demons"
    },
    {
      "question": "叙爵",
      "answer": "じょしゃく",
      "meaning": "conferring a peerage"
    },
    {
      "question": "水仙",
      "answer": "すいせん",
      "meaning": "daffodil (esp. Narcissus tazetta var. chinensis), narcissus"
    },
    {
      "question": "同期生",
      "answer": "どうきせい",
      "meaning": "classmate, graduates in the same class, wrestlers who began their professional careers in the same t"
    },
    {
      "question": "少数民族",
      "answer": "しょうすうみんぞく",
      "meaning": "minority peoples"
    },
    {
      "question": "発煙筒",
      "answer": "はつえんとう",
      "meaning": "smoke bomb, smoke candle"
    },
    {
      "question": "痔",
      "answer": "じ,ぢ",
      "meaning": "hemorrhoids, piles"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷やか",
      "answer": "ひややか",
      "meaning": "cold, chilly, cool, cold (attitude, stare, etc.), frigid, indifferent, distant, surly, curt, compose"
    },
    {
      "question": "一事",
      "answer": "いちじ",
      "meaning": "one thing"
    },
    {
      "question": "希求",
      "answer": "ききゅう",
      "meaning": "longing, great desire, aspiration"
    },
    {
      "question": "見果てる",
      "answer": "みはてる",
      "meaning": "to see through to the finish, to be seen to the end"
    },
    {
      "question": "外付け",
      "answer": "そとづけ",
      "meaning": "external (hard drive, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "添え木",
      "answer": "そえぎ",
      "meaning": "splint, brace, epithesis, splice, support (e.g. for a plant), prop"
    },
    {
      "question": "腐乱",
      "answer": "ふらん",
      "meaning": "decomposition, ulceration"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛好",
      "answer": "あいこう",
      "meaning": "love, adoration"
    },
    {
      "question": "読解",
      "answer": "どっかい",
      "meaning": "reading comprehension"
    },
    {
      "question": "放流",
      "answer": "ほうりゅう",
      "meaning": "discharge (e.g. of water from a dam), release (of young fish into a river, pond, etc.), stocking (a"
    },
    {
      "question": "六道",
      "answer": "ろくどう",
      "meaning": "the six realms (Deva realm, Asura realm, Human realm, Animal realm, Hungry Ghost realm, Naraka realm"
    },
    {
      "question": "嶺",
      "answer": "みね",
      "meaning": "peak, summit, ridge, top, back of a blade"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘗て",
      "answer": "かつて",
      "meaning": "once, before, formerly, ever, former, ex-, never yet, never before, first time, still not happened"
    },
    {
      "question": "火砲",
      "answer": "かほう",
      "meaning": "artillery"
    },
    {
      "question": "検問所",
      "answer": "けんもんじょ,けんもんしょ",
      "meaning": "check station, checkpoint"
    },
    {
      "question": "過疎",
      "answer": "かそ",
      "meaning": "depopulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "死産",
      "answer": "しざん,しさん",
      "meaning": "stillbirth"
    },
    {
      "question": "試射",
      "answer": "ししゃ",
      "meaning": "test firing"
    },
    {
      "question": "純正",
      "answer": "じゅんせい",
      "meaning": "genuine, pure, perfect"
    },
    {
      "question": "革命的",
      "answer": "かくめいてき",
      "meaning": "revolutionary (e.g. technology)"
    },
    {
      "question": "示威",
      "answer": "じい,しい",
      "meaning": "demonstration, show of force"
    },
    {
      "question": "分水嶺",
      "answer": "ぶんすいれい",
      "meaning": "watershed, divide"
    },
    {
      "question": "減給",
      "answer": "げんきゅう",
      "meaning": "pay cut, salary cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "麺類",
      "answer": "めんるい",
      "meaning": "noodles, vermicelli"
    },
    {
      "question": "読心術",
      "answer": "どくしんじゅつ",
      "meaning": "mind reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "男所帯",
      "answer": "おとこじょたい",
      "meaning": "all-male household"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち直す",
      "answer": "うちなおす",
      "meaning": "to fluff up (e.g. a futon), to retype (e.g. a letter)"
    },
    {
      "question": "自説",
      "answer": "じせつ",
      "meaning": "one's personal opinion"
    },
    {
      "question": "外出着",
      "answer": "がいしゅつぎ",
      "meaning": "street clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "熟慮",
      "answer": "じゅくりょ",
      "meaning": "deliberation, (thoughtful) consideration, to consider a matter carefully"
    },
    {
      "question": "二言目",
      "answer": "ふたことめ",
      "meaning": "favorite phrase, favourite phrase, byword, something one always talks about"
    },
    {
      "question": "重力場",
      "answer": "じゅうりょくば",
      "meaning": "gravitational field"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶碗蒸し",
      "answer": "ちゃわんむし",
      "meaning": "chawanmushi, savoury steamed egg custard with chicken, mushrooms, etc. (savory)"
    },
    {
      "question": "競る",
      "answer": "せる",
      "meaning": "to compete, to bid, to sell at auction"
    },
    {
      "question": "細工物",
      "answer": "さいくもの",
      "meaning": "handiwork, ware"
    },
    {
      "question": "下手糞",
      "answer": "へたくそ",
      "meaning": "unskilled, clumsy, lousy, poor, awkward, shitty"
    },
    {
      "question": "水桶",
      "answer": "みずおけ",
      "meaning": "pail (for water), bucket, cistern, water tank"
    },
    {
      "question": "出処",
      "answer": "しゅっしょ,でどころ,でどこ",
      "meaning": "origin, source, authority, birthplace, release (discharge) from prison, exit, point of departure, ti"
    },
    {
      "question": "叩き上げ",
      "answer": "たたきあげ",
      "meaning": "working one's way up, self-made person, veteran"
    },
    {
      "question": "珍重",
      "answer": "ちんちょう",
      "meaning": "prizing, valuing highly, esteeming"
    },
    {
      "question": "偏",
      "answer": "へん",
      "meaning": "left-hand radical of a character"
    },
    {
      "question": "具足",
      "answer": "ぐそく",
      "meaning": "completeness, being fully equipped, (suit of) armor, armour"
    },
    {
      "question": "天下一",
      "answer": "てんかいち",
      "meaning": "unique thing, best on earth"
    },
    {
      "question": "槍衾",
      "answer": "やりぶすま",
      "meaning": "line of spears held at the ready"
    },
    {
      "question": "市立",
      "answer": "しりつ,いちりつ",
      "meaning": "municipal, city"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛",
      "answer": "もり",
      "meaning": "serving (of food), helping, chilled soba served on a dish (often on a wicker basket or in a shallow"
    },
    {
      "question": "三つ指",
      "answer": "みつゆび",
      "meaning": "bowing while pressing three fingers of each hand on floor"
    },
    {
      "question": "小鼻",
      "answer": "こばな",
      "meaning": "nostrils, wings of the nose"
    },
    {
      "question": "速達",
      "answer": "そくたつ",
      "meaning": "express, special delivery"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉幕",
      "answer": "へいまく",
      "meaning": "falling of the curtain, coming to an end"
    },
    {
      "question": "籠の鳥",
      "answer": "かごのとり",
      "meaning": "caged bird, person whose freedom has been restricted (esp. a prostitute, mistress, concubine, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り沙汰",
      "answer": "とりざた",
      "meaning": "talk (of the town), rumour, rumor, gossip"
    },
    {
      "question": "傷害罪",
      "answer": "しょうがいざい",
      "meaning": "(crime of) inflicting bodily injury"
    },
    {
      "question": "芹",
      "answer": "せり",
      "meaning": "Java water dropwort (Oenanthe javanica), Japanese parsley"
    },
    {
      "question": "臀",
      "answer": "しり",
      "meaning": "buttocks, behind, rump, bottom, hips, undersurface, last place, end, consequence"
    },
    {
      "question": "上洛",
      "answer": "じょうらく",
      "meaning": "proceeding to the capital"
    },
    {
      "question": "庄",
      "answer": "しょう,そう",
      "meaning": "manor, villa"
    },
    {
      "question": "日米",
      "answer": "にちべい",
      "meaning": "Japan and the United States, Japanese-American"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬘",
      "answer": "かつら,かずら",
      "meaning": "wig, hairpiece, toupee"
    },
    {
      "question": "落ち武者",
      "answer": "おちむしゃ",
      "meaning": "fleeing soldier, warrior fleeing the battlefield, deserter"
    },
    {
      "question": "取締",
      "answer": "とりしまり",
      "meaning": "control, management, supervision"
    },
    {
      "question": "託児所",
      "answer": "たくじしょ",
      "meaning": "creche, day nursery"
    },
    {
      "question": "水風呂",
      "answer": "みずぶろ,すいふろ",
      "meaning": "cold bath, taking a cold bath, bathtub heated from below"
    },
    {
      "question": "相合傘",
      "answer": "あいあいがさ",
      "meaning": "sharing an umbrella, under one umbrella"
    },
    {
      "question": "通電",
      "answer": "つうでん",
      "meaning": "the passage of electric current"
    },
    {
      "question": "争奪",
      "answer": "そうだつ",
      "meaning": "struggle (for), scramble, contest"
    },
    {
      "question": "無聊",
      "answer": "ぶりょう",
      "meaning": "boredom, ennui"
    },
    {
      "question": "不感症",
      "answer": "ふかんしょう",
      "meaning": "sexual frigidity, insensitivity, indifference"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き知る",
      "answer": "ききしる",
      "meaning": "to learn something through hearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "呼吸器",
      "answer": "こきゅうき",
      "meaning": "respiratory organs"
    },
    {
      "question": "生野菜",
      "answer": "なまやさい",
      "meaning": "fresh vegetables"
    },
    {
      "question": "舌が回る",
      "answer": "したがまわる",
      "meaning": "to speak without hesitation or problems, to speak fluently or skillfully, to be talkative, to have a"
    },
    {
      "question": "奥庭",
      "answer": "おくにわ",
      "meaning": "inner garden, back yard"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕手",
      "answer": "して",
      "meaning": "doer, performer, protagonist (in noh or kyogen), hero, leading part, main character, speculator (in"
    },
    {
      "question": "音大",
      "answer": "おんだい",
      "meaning": "college of music"
    },
    {
      "question": "歓呼",
      "answer": "かんこ",
      "meaning": "acclamation, jubilation"
    },
    {
      "question": "麻酔薬",
      "answer": "ますいやく",
      "meaning": "anesthetic, anaesthetic, narcotic"
    },
    {
      "question": "練り",
      "answer": "ねり",
      "meaning": "kneading, gloss, tempering, paste (e.g. bean paste, mustard paste), parading of portable shrines and"
    },
    {
      "question": "先着",
      "answer": "せんちゃく",
      "meaning": "arriving first"
    },
    {
      "question": "懇々",
      "answer": "こんこん",
      "meaning": "earnest, kind, sincere"
    },
    {
      "question": "荷が勝つ",
      "answer": "にがかつ",
      "meaning": "to be unequal to the burden (job), to be too heavy a load for"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち切り",
      "answer": "もちきり",
      "meaning": "hot topic, talk of the town"
    },
    {
      "question": "溜飲",
      "answer": "りゅういん",
      "meaning": "acid reflux, bile reflux, pyrosis, stomach acid (when it enters the esophagus), heartburn, indigesti"
    },
    {
      "question": "片親",
      "answer": "かたおや",
      "meaning": "one parent, single parent"
    },
    {
      "question": "雷電",
      "answer": "らいでん",
      "meaning": "thunder and lightning"
    },
    {
      "question": "電器",
      "answer": "でんき",
      "meaning": "electric (goods)"
    },
    {
      "question": "崇敬",
      "answer": "すうけい",
      "meaning": "reverence"
    },
    {
      "question": "下剋上",
      "answer": "げこくじょう",
      "meaning": "juniors dominating seniors, inferiors overthrowing their superiors, retainer supplanting his lord"
    },
    {
      "question": "同属",
      "answer": "どうぞく",
      "meaning": "same sort, same kind, same genus, homologous, congeneric"
    },
    {
      "question": "間接照明",
      "answer": "かんせつしょうめい",
      "meaning": "indirect lighting"
    },
    {
      "question": "日給",
      "answer": "にっきゅう",
      "meaning": "daily wages"
    },
    {
      "question": "入館",
      "answer": "にゅうかん",
      "meaning": "entry (e.g. library, school, museum), entering"
    },
    {
      "question": "誕生祝い",
      "answer": "たんじょういわい",
      "meaning": "birthday celebration"
    },
    {
      "question": "監視網",
      "answer": "かんしもう",
      "meaning": "surveillance network"
    },
    {
      "question": "老眼鏡",
      "answer": "ろうがんきょう",
      "meaning": "reading (farsighted) glasses, spectacles for the aged"
    },
    {
      "question": "無銭飲食",
      "answer": "むせんいんしょく",
      "meaning": "dine and dash, leaving a restaurant without paying"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸し風呂",
      "answer": "むしぶろ",
      "meaning": "steam bath"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬱血",
      "answer": "うっけつ",
      "meaning": "blood congestion, -stasis"
    },
    {
      "question": "行水",
      "answer": "ぎょうずい",
      "meaning": "tub bath, washing oneself in a tub, taking a bath in a washtub, cleaning oneself for religious purif"
    },
    {
      "question": "商法",
      "answer": "しょうほう",
      "meaning": "business practice, business method, commerce, commercial law"
    },
    {
      "question": "草葉の陰",
      "answer": "くさばのかげ",
      "meaning": "under the sod, one's grave, the other world"
    },
    {
      "question": "数行",
      "answer": "すうぎょう",
      "meaning": "several lines, many lines"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤血球",
      "answer": "せっけっきゅう",
      "meaning": "red blood cell, erythrocyte"
    },
    {
      "question": "砲声",
      "answer": "ほうせい",
      "meaning": "sound of a gun, roar of cannon"
    },
    {
      "question": "北京",
      "answer": "ペキン,ペイチン",
      "meaning": "Beijing (China), Peking"
    },
    {
      "question": "冒瀆",
      "answer": "ぼうとく",
      "meaning": "blasphemy, curse, profanity, sacrilege, desecration"
    },
    {
      "question": "副賞",
      "answer": "ふくしょう",
      "meaning": "extra prize"
    },
    {
      "question": "飯時",
      "answer": "めしどき",
      "meaning": "mealtime"
    },
    {
      "question": "信望",
      "answer": "しんぼう",
      "meaning": "confidence, popularity"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠大",
      "answer": "えんだい",
      "meaning": "grand, far-reaching, ambitious"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀幕",
      "answer": "ぎんまく",
      "meaning": "(projection) screen, the silver screen, the film world, movies"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝書",
      "answer": "でんしょ",
      "meaning": "book or scroll that has been handed down through generations, book of secrets, delivering a letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹腔",
      "answer": "ふっこう,ふくこう,ふくくう",
      "meaning": "abdominal cavity"
    },
    {
      "question": "報奨",
      "answer": "ほうしょう",
      "meaning": "bonus, bounty, reward, compensation"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄達",
      "answer": "えいたつ",
      "meaning": "fame, distinction, rise, advancement"
    },
    {
      "question": "天下無双",
      "answer": "てんかむそう,てんかぶそう",
      "meaning": "peerless, unequaled, unequalled"
    },
    {
      "question": "山芋",
      "answer": "やまいも",
      "meaning": "Japanese yam (Dioscorea japonica)"
    },
    {
      "question": "明度",
      "answer": "めいど",
      "meaning": "brightness, lightness"
    },
    {
      "question": "平服",
      "answer": "へいふく",
      "meaning": "ordinary clothes, everyday attire, plain clothes, civilian clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "落涙",
      "answer": "らくるい",
      "meaning": "shedding tears"
    },
    {
      "question": "火薬庫",
      "answer": "かやくこ",
      "meaning": "gunpowder magazine, magazine, explosives warehouse, powder keg"
    },
    {
      "question": "差し障る",
      "answer": "さしさわる",
      "meaning": "to hinder, to obstruct, to adversely affect"
    },
    {
      "question": "難物",
      "answer": "なんぶつ",
      "meaning": "hard problem, person hard to please, hard nut to crack"
    },
    {
      "question": "転がし",
      "answer": "ころがし",
      "meaning": "rolling (something), knocking down, fishing with multiple hooks on a weighted line, repeatedly buyin"
    },
    {
      "question": "格調",
      "answer": "かくちょう",
      "meaning": "tone (of speech, writing, etc.), style"
    },
    {
      "question": "梅酒",
      "answer": "うめしゅ",
      "meaning": "ume liqueur, Japanese plum brandy, unripe ume infused in liquor (esp. shōchū) with added sugar"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵葉書",
      "answer": "えはがき",
      "meaning": "picture postcard"
    },
    {
      "question": "陶",
      "answer": "すえ",
      "meaning": "ceramics, pottery, porcelain"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴方方",
      "answer": "あなたがた",
      "meaning": "you (plural)"
    },
    {
      "question": "入稿",
      "answer": "にゅうこう",
      "meaning": "sending a manuscript to the printer, receiving a manuscript from the author"
    },
    {
      "question": "南海",
      "answer": "なんかい",
      "meaning": "southern sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "破断",
      "answer": "はだん",
      "meaning": "rupture, break, fracture"
    },
    {
      "question": "山の神",
      "answer": "やまのかみ",
      "meaning": "mountain god, one's wife (esp. a nagging wife), roughskin sculpin (Trachidermus fasciatus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "連れ合い",
      "answer": "つれあい",
      "meaning": "one's husband, one's wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "主夫",
      "answer": "しゅふ",
      "meaning": "househusband, stay-at-home dad"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝負下着",
      "answer": "しょうぶしたぎ",
      "meaning": "'lucky' underwear (esp. panties), set aside for special dates"
    },
    {
      "question": "特集記事",
      "answer": "とくしゅうきじ",
      "meaning": "special feature article"
    },
    {
      "question": "蹴り込む",
      "answer": "けりこむ",
      "meaning": "to kick in"
    },
    {
      "question": "肌荒れ",
      "answer": "はだあれ",
      "meaning": "dry skin, bad skin, rough skin, unhealthy skin"
    },
    {
      "question": "行状",
      "answer": "ぎょうじょう",
      "meaning": "behavior, behaviour"
    },
    {
      "question": "上端",
      "answer": "じょうたん",
      "meaning": "upper end, top, tip, top edge"
    },
    {
      "question": "一敗",
      "answer": "いっぱい",
      "meaning": "one defeat"
    },
    {
      "question": "琴線",
      "answer": "きんせん",
      "meaning": "heartstrings, koto string"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕入れ先",
      "answer": "しいれさき",
      "meaning": "supplier"
    },
    {
      "question": "預かり物",
      "answer": "あずかりもの",
      "meaning": "something left in charge"
    },
    {
      "question": "金遣い",
      "answer": "かねづかい",
      "meaning": "(way of) spending money"
    },
    {
      "question": "小降り",
      "answer": "こぶり",
      "meaning": "light rain, drizzle"
    },
    {
      "question": "大森",
      "answer": "おおもり",
      "meaning": "large forest"
    },
    {
      "question": "御家",
      "answer": "おうち",
      "meaning": "your home, your family, their home, their family, (my) home"
    },
    {
      "question": "開国",
      "answer": "かいこく",
      "meaning": "founding a country, opening of a country (e.g. Japan) to the world"
    },
    {
      "question": "獄門",
      "answer": "ごくもん",
      "meaning": "prison gate"
    },
    {
      "question": "女子校生",
      "answer": "じょしこうせい",
      "meaning": "student of a girls' school"
    },
    {
      "question": "補講",
      "answer": "ほこう",
      "meaning": "supplementary classes or lectures"
    },
    {
      "question": "心算",
      "answer": "しんさん,しんざん,つもり",
      "meaning": "intention, purpose"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮え滾る",
      "answer": "にえたぎる",
      "meaning": "to boil, to be boiling hot, to be on a rolling boil"
    },
    {
      "question": "独善",
      "answer": "どくぜん",
      "meaning": "self-righteousness, self-justified"
    },
    {
      "question": "練達",
      "answer": "れんたつ",
      "meaning": "expert(ise), skill, dexterity"
    },
    {
      "question": "視野狭窄",
      "answer": "しやきょうさく",
      "meaning": "narrowing of visual field, narrow-mindedness, lack of vision"
    },
    {
      "question": "法治国家",
      "answer": "ほうちこっか",
      "meaning": "country with a constitutional government, constitutional state, country where the rule of law prevai"
    },
    {
      "question": "地階",
      "answer": "ちかい",
      "meaning": "basement, cellar"
    },
    {
      "question": "畏い",
      "answer": "かしこい",
      "meaning": "wise, clever, smart"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝市",
      "answer": "あさいち",
      "meaning": "morning market"
    },
    {
      "question": "外伝",
      "answer": "がいでん",
      "meaning": "supplementary biography, anecdote, side story, spin-off"
    },
    {
      "question": "置換",
      "answer": "ちかん",
      "meaning": "substitution, replacement, permutation, displacement"
    },
    {
      "question": "手羽先",
      "answer": "てばさき",
      "meaning": "(tip section of) chicken wing, second segment of chicken wing"
    },
    {
      "question": "外様",
      "answer": "とざま",
      "meaning": "outside daimyo, non-Tokugawa daimyo, outsider, one not included in the favored (favoured) group"
    },
    {
      "question": "範",
      "answer": "はん",
      "meaning": "example, model"
    },
    {
      "question": "抗生物質",
      "answer": "こうせいぶっしつ",
      "meaning": "antibiotic, antibiotics"
    },
    {
      "question": "卵白",
      "answer": "らんぱく",
      "meaning": "white of an egg, albumen"
    },
    {
      "question": "美人局",
      "answer": "つつもたせ",
      "meaning": "badger game, scheme in which a man and woman trick another man into a compromising situation for bla"
    },
    {
      "question": "彫り物",
      "answer": "ほりもの",
      "meaning": "carving, engraving, sculpture, tattoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗黒面",
      "answer": "あんこくめん",
      "meaning": "the dark or seamy side"
    },
    {
      "question": "職質",
      "answer": "しょくしつ",
      "meaning": "questioning (e.g. by police)"
    },
    {
      "question": "漕ぎ出す",
      "answer": "こぎだす",
      "meaning": "to start rowing, to begin to row, to row out (e.g. to sea), to pull out, to set off, to start pedali"
    },
    {
      "question": "不穏当",
      "answer": "ふおんとう",
      "meaning": "improper, inappropriate, unjust, unfair, unreasonable"
    },
    {
      "question": "同級",
      "answer": "どうきゅう",
      "meaning": "the same grade, same class"
    },
    {
      "question": "口八丁",
      "answer": "くちはっちょう",
      "meaning": "voluble, eloquent"
    },
    {
      "question": "縮れる",
      "answer": "ちぢれる",
      "meaning": "to be wavy, to be curled, to be frizzled"
    },
    {
      "question": "似た者",
      "answer": "にたもの",
      "meaning": "similar people"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬代",
      "answer": "くすりだい",
      "meaning": "charge for medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒武者",
      "answer": "あらむしゃ",
      "meaning": "daredevil, rowdy"
    },
    {
      "question": "法術",
      "answer": "ほうじゅつ",
      "meaning": "practising law, legal processes in running a country, method, way, means, magic"
    },
    {
      "question": "膠",
      "answer": "にかわ",
      "meaning": "glue (usu. from animal and fish bone, skin, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗艦",
      "answer": "じょうかん",
      "meaning": "joining one's warship"
    },
    {
      "question": "夕映え",
      "answer": "ゆうばえ",
      "meaning": "sunset glow"
    },
    {
      "question": "刑場",
      "answer": "けいじょう",
      "meaning": "place of execution"
    },
    {
      "question": "流砂",
      "answer": "りゅうしゃ,りゅうさ",
      "meaning": "quicksand"
    },
    {
      "question": "花輪",
      "answer": "はなわ",
      "meaning": "wreath, garland"
    },
    {
      "question": "人買い",
      "answer": "ひとかい",
      "meaning": "slave traffic, slave dealer"
    },
    {
      "question": "神経毒",
      "answer": "しんけいどく",
      "meaning": "neurotoxin, nerve poison"
    },
    {
      "question": "法令",
      "answer": "ほうれい",
      "meaning": "laws and ordinances, acts (of parliament, congress, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "供出",
      "answer": "きょうしゅつ",
      "meaning": "obligatory supply (of goods to the government, e.g. during wartime), delivery (to the government at"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨月",
      "answer": "りんげつ",
      "meaning": "final month of pregnancy, month in which childbirth is due"
    },
    {
      "question": "無理心中",
      "answer": "むりしんじゅう",
      "meaning": "forced double suicide"
    },
    {
      "question": "蔑ろ",
      "answer": "ないがしろ",
      "meaning": "(a) slight, disrespect, making light (of), neglect"
    },
    {
      "question": "佳",
      "answer": "か",
      "meaning": "beautiful, good, excellent"
    },
    {
      "question": "石窯",
      "answer": "いしがま",
      "meaning": "stone oven, masonry oven, brick oven"
    },
    {
      "question": "新橋",
      "answer": "しんばし",
      "meaning": "Shinbashi (section of Tokyo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "組手",
      "answer": "くみて",
      "meaning": "wooden joints, paired karate kata, beltwork"
    },
    {
      "question": "大船",
      "answer": "おおぶね,おおふね,たいせん",
      "meaning": "large boat"
    },
    {
      "question": "厭味",
      "answer": "いやみ",
      "meaning": "disagreeableness, unpleasantness, nastiness, offensiveness, tastelessness, cutting remark, disagreea"
    },
    {
      "question": "浅薄",
      "answer": "せんぱく",
      "meaning": "shallow, superficial"
    },
    {
      "question": "社会生活",
      "answer": "しゃかいせいかつ",
      "meaning": "social life"
    },
    {
      "question": "亡き者",
      "answer": "なきもの",
      "meaning": "dead person"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖餐",
      "answer": "せいさん,せいざん",
      "meaning": "Holy Communion, Lord's Supper, Eucharist"
    },
    {
      "question": "政務官",
      "answer": "せいむかん",
      "meaning": "parliamentary official"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝鮮",
      "answer": "ちょうせん",
      "meaning": "Korea"
    },
    {
      "question": "天球",
      "answer": "てんきゅう",
      "meaning": "celestial sphere, the heavens"
    },
    {
      "question": "少年院",
      "answer": "しょうねんいん",
      "meaning": "reform school, reformatory, youth detention center (centre)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋤",
      "answer": "すき",
      "meaning": "spade, plough, plow"
    },
    {
      "question": "痰",
      "answer": "たん",
      "meaning": "phlegm, sputum"
    },
    {
      "question": "増進",
      "answer": "ぞうしん",
      "meaning": "promoting, increase, advance"
    },
    {
      "question": "一芸",
      "answer": "いちげい",
      "meaning": "an art, one talent"
    },
    {
      "question": "生魚",
      "answer": "なまざかな,なまうお,せいぎょ",
      "meaning": "raw fish, uncooked fish, fresh fish, live fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "運試し",
      "answer": "うんだめし",
      "meaning": "trying one's luck, test of one's luck"
    },
    {
      "question": "枠内",
      "answer": "わくない",
      "meaning": "within the limits (framework, boundaries, price, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "何何",
      "answer": "なになに",
      "meaning": "what, so-and-so, such and such, something (or other), what?, wait, hang on, well, well, let's see, n"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗喩",
      "answer": "あんゆ",
      "meaning": "metaphor"
    },
    {
      "question": "格差社会",
      "answer": "かくさしゃかい",
      "meaning": "disparate society, stratified society"
    },
    {
      "question": "百花",
      "answer": "ひゃっか",
      "meaning": "all varieties of flowers, many flowers"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄衣",
      "answer": "うすぎぬ,うすごろも",
      "meaning": "thin or light silk, sheer silk, veil (mystery)"
    },
    {
      "question": "針子",
      "answer": "はりこ",
      "meaning": "seamstress"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜色",
      "answer": "やしょく",
      "meaning": "shades of night, night scene"
    },
    {
      "question": "胡蝶",
      "answer": "こちょう",
      "meaning": "butterfly"
    },
    {
      "question": "探偵小説",
      "answer": "たんていしょうせつ",
      "meaning": "detective story"
    },
    {
      "question": "自動小銃",
      "answer": "じどうしょうじゅう",
      "meaning": "automatic rifle, weapon"
    },
    {
      "question": "炯々",
      "answer": "けいけい",
      "meaning": "glaring (e.g. eyes), piercing, penetrating"
    },
    {
      "question": "逸",
      "answer": "いっち,いち",
      "meaning": "most, best, very, excellent"
    },
    {
      "question": "不整脈",
      "answer": "ふせいみゃく",
      "meaning": "irregular pulse, arrhythmia"
    },
    {
      "question": "軛",
      "answer": "くびき",
      "meaning": "yoke, constraints, oppression"
    },
    {
      "question": "配当",
      "answer": "はいとう",
      "meaning": "allotment, apportionment, share, dividend"
    },
    {
      "question": "救い主",
      "answer": "すくいぬし",
      "meaning": "savior, saviour, rescuer, the Savior (in Christianity), the Saviour"
    },
    {
      "question": "浸みる",
      "answer": "しみる",
      "meaning": "to pierce, to penetrate, to soak in, to permeate, to be infected (with vice), to be steeped (with pr"
    },
    {
      "question": "慈善",
      "answer": "じぜん",
      "meaning": "charity, philanthropy"
    },
    {
      "question": "練乳",
      "answer": "れんにゅう",
      "meaning": "condensed milk"
    },
    {
      "question": "縫い物",
      "answer": "ぬいもの",
      "meaning": "sewing, needlework, embroidery"
    },
    {
      "question": "捕り物",
      "answer": "とりもの",
      "meaning": "capture, arrest"
    },
    {
      "question": "採決",
      "answer": "さいけつ",
      "meaning": "vote, ballot, division"
    },
    {
      "question": "訛る",
      "answer": "なまる",
      "meaning": "to speak with an accent, to be corrupted (of word), to mispronounce"
    },
    {
      "question": "中高",
      "answer": "なかだか,ちゅうこう",
      "meaning": "convex, middle and high school, medium and high (level)"
    },
    {
      "question": "習字",
      "answer": "しゅうじ",
      "meaning": "penmanship"
    },
    {
      "question": "代え",
      "answer": "かえ,がえ",
      "meaning": "change, alteration, substitute, spare, replacement, proxy, rate of exchange"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷え込み",
      "answer": "ひえこみ",
      "meaning": "turning into a cooler state, cooling down"
    },
    {
      "question": "男が廃る",
      "answer": "おとこがすたる",
      "meaning": "to hurt one's reputation, to be ashamed of oneself, to lose one's honour"
    },
    {
      "question": "緩め",
      "answer": "ゆるめ",
      "meaning": "somewhat loose"
    },
    {
      "question": "多方面",
      "answer": "たほうめん",
      "meaning": "many-sided, multifarious, versatility"
    },
    {
      "question": "片棒",
      "answer": "かたぼう",
      "meaning": "front or rear of a palanquin (carried by two people), one of two people carrying a palanquin"
    },
    {
      "question": "八咫烏",
      "answer": "やたがらす",
      "meaning": "Yatagarasu (mythical raven who aided Emperor Jimmu on his eastern expedition), three-legged crow inh"
    },
    {
      "question": "天竜",
      "answer": "てんりゅう,てんりょう",
      "meaning": "deva and naga, heavenly dragon"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈴蘭",
      "answer": "すずらん",
      "meaning": "lily of the valley (Convallaria keiskei)"
    },
    {
      "question": "蓮華",
      "answer": "れんげ",
      "meaning": "lotus flower, Chinese milk vetch (Astragalus sinicus), china spoon, lotus-shaped pedestal for a grav"
    },
    {
      "question": "有明",
      "answer": "ありあけ",
      "meaning": "dawn (sometimes esp. in ref. to the 16th day of the lunar month onward)"
    },
    {
      "question": "天元",
      "answer": "てんげん",
      "meaning": "central black dot on a go board, Tengen era (978.11.29-983.4.15)"
    },
    {
      "question": "贋物",
      "answer": "にせもの,にせもん,がんぶつ",
      "meaning": "spurious article, forgery, counterfeit, imitation, sham"
    },
    {
      "question": "火の鳥",
      "answer": "ひのとり",
      "meaning": "phoenix (esp. fenghuang, the Chinese phoenix)"
    },
    {
      "question": "片端",
      "answer": "かたはし,かたわ",
      "meaning": "one edge, one end, one side, crippled, deformed, imperfect, incomplete"
    },
    {
      "question": "五代",
      "answer": "ごだい",
      "meaning": "Five Dynasties (China, 907-979)"
    },
    {
      "question": "中てる",
      "answer": "あてる",
      "meaning": "to hit something aimed at (maliciously), to hit a prize (lottery, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "所内",
      "answer": "しょない",
      "meaning": "inside, interior"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒婦",
      "answer": "どくふ",
      "meaning": "evil woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "読唇術",
      "answer": "どくしんじゅつ",
      "meaning": "lip reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "宝飾",
      "answer": "ほうしょく",
      "meaning": "jewels and ornaments, jewelry, jewellery"
    },
    {
      "question": "係累",
      "answer": "けいるい",
      "meaning": "dependents, family members that one has to support, encumbrances, things that tie one down"
    },
    {
      "question": "慣らし",
      "answer": "ならし",
      "meaning": "running-in, breaking in (e.g. engine, etc.), accustomizing, warming up"
    },
    {
      "question": "月給",
      "answer": "げっきゅう",
      "meaning": "monthly salary"
    },
    {
      "question": "門戸",
      "answer": "もんこ",
      "meaning": "door"
    },
    {
      "question": "大往生",
      "answer": "だいおうじょう",
      "meaning": "peaceful death"
    },
    {
      "question": "七夕祭り",
      "answer": "たなばたまつり",
      "meaning": "Star Festival (held in July or August), Tanabata, Festival of the Weaver"
    },
    {
      "question": "事務長",
      "answer": "じむちょう",
      "meaning": "manager, purser"
    },
    {
      "question": "津軽",
      "answer": "つがる",
      "meaning": "Tsugaru (Western region of Aomori Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "単車",
      "answer": "たんしゃ",
      "meaning": "motorcycle"
    },
    {
      "question": "内野",
      "answer": "ないや",
      "meaning": "infield, diamond"
    },
    {
      "question": "称",
      "answer": "しょう",
      "meaning": "name, title, designation, fame, reputation"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫣然",
      "answer": "えんぜん",
      "meaning": "sweetly smiling, like the smiling of a beauty, gracious"
    },
    {
      "question": "原案",
      "answer": "げんあん",
      "meaning": "original plan, original bill, original motion, draft"
    },
    {
      "question": "心胆",
      "answer": "しんたん",
      "meaning": "heart"
    },
    {
      "question": "丹田",
      "answer": "たんでん",
      "meaning": "point below the navel (a focus point for internal meditative techniques)"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り分け",
      "answer": "とりわけ",
      "meaning": "especially, above all, inter alia, among others"
    },
    {
      "question": "新卒",
      "answer": "しんそつ",
      "meaning": "new graduate, recent graduate"
    },
    {
      "question": "立件",
      "answer": "りっけん",
      "meaning": "assembling a criminal case"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳目",
      "answer": "じもく,じぼく",
      "meaning": "eyes and ears, seeing and hearing, one's attention, one's interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "無学",
      "answer": "むがく",
      "meaning": "illiteracy, ignorance, arhat, someone who has attained nirvana"
    },
    {
      "question": "火の車",
      "answer": "ひのくるま",
      "meaning": "fiery chariot (which carries the souls of sinners into hell), desperate financial situation, dire st"
    },
    {
      "question": "異国情緒",
      "answer": "いこくじょうちょ,いこくじょうしょ",
      "meaning": "exotic mood, exotic atmosphere, exoticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "喉越し",
      "answer": "のどごし",
      "meaning": "feeling of food or drink going down one's throat"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚切り",
      "answer": "あつぎり",
      "meaning": "thick slice"
    },
    {
      "question": "高飛び",
      "answer": "たかとび",
      "meaning": "flight, escape, running away, fleeing, flying high"
    },
    {
      "question": "這い上る",
      "answer": "はいあがる,はいのぼる",
      "meaning": "to creep up, to crawl up, to clamber, to climb with hands and feet"
    },
    {
      "question": "言付ける",
      "answer": "いいつける,ことづける",
      "meaning": "to tell (to do), to order, to charge, to direct, to tell on (someone), to tattle, to report, to ofte"
    },
    {
      "question": "牙を研ぐ",
      "answer": "きばをとぐ",
      "meaning": "to sharpen one's fangs"
    },
    {
      "question": "押さえ",
      "answer": "おさえ",
      "meaning": "weight (e.g. paperweight), pressing down, keeping control, exercising authority, having self-control"
    },
    {
      "question": "勉強家",
      "answer": "べんきょうか",
      "meaning": "diligent student, studious person"
    },
    {
      "question": "司馬",
      "answer": "しば",
      "meaning": "Minister of War (Zhou-dynasty China)"
    },
    {
      "question": "女陰",
      "answer": "じょいん,にょいん",
      "meaning": "female genitals, vulva"
    },
    {
      "question": "小宇宙",
      "answer": "しょううちゅう",
      "meaning": "microcosmos, microcosm"
    },
    {
      "question": "教習",
      "answer": "きょうしゅう",
      "meaning": "training, instruction"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛機",
      "answer": "あいき",
      "meaning": "favourite aeroplane, camera or other machine (favorite, airplane)"
    },
    {
      "question": "味噌煮",
      "answer": "みそに",
      "meaning": "food cooked in miso, cooking in miso"
    },
    {
      "question": "登攀",
      "answer": "とうはん,とはん",
      "meaning": "scaling, climbing, ascending"
    },
    {
      "question": "有権者",
      "answer": "ゆうけんしゃ",
      "meaning": "(eligible) voter, elector, constituent, the electorate, holder of a right, rightsholder, right holde"
    },
    {
      "question": "執政",
      "answer": "しっせい",
      "meaning": "administration, government, administrator, governor"
    },
    {
      "question": "果樹",
      "answer": "かじゅ",
      "meaning": "fruit tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "流域",
      "answer": "りゅういき",
      "meaning": "drainage basin, catchment basin, river basin, watershed, valley"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち取る",
      "answer": "うちとる",
      "meaning": "to kill (with a weapon), to defeat an opponent, to get someone out, to arrest, to take prisoner"
    },
    {
      "question": "一眼レフ",
      "answer": "いちがんレフ",
      "meaning": "single-lens reflex camera"
    },
    {
      "question": "整髪料",
      "answer": "せいはつりょう",
      "meaning": "hairdressing product (creams, gels, etc.), hairdressing fee, charge for a haircut"
    },
    {
      "question": "化粧台",
      "answer": "けしょうだい",
      "meaning": "dressing table, dresser"
    },
    {
      "question": "観念的",
      "answer": "かんねんてき",
      "meaning": "conceptual, ideational, notional, theoretical, academic"
    },
    {
      "question": "消費税",
      "answer": "しょうひぜい",
      "meaning": "consumption tax (incl. sales tax, VAT, excise duty, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹き渡る",
      "answer": "ふきわたる",
      "meaning": "to blow across"
    },
    {
      "question": "濾す",
      "answer": "こす",
      "meaning": "to filter, to strain"
    },
    {
      "question": "自家用",
      "answer": "じかよう",
      "meaning": "for private or home use"
    },
    {
      "question": "色事",
      "answer": "いろごと",
      "meaning": "love affair, sensual pleasures"
    },
    {
      "question": "転嫁",
      "answer": "てんか",
      "meaning": "imputation, shifting (blame, responsibility, etc.), passing the buck, second marriage, remarriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜陰",
      "answer": "やいん",
      "meaning": "shades of evening, dead of night"
    },
    {
      "question": "難産",
      "answer": "なんざん",
      "meaning": "difficult delivery, difficult childbirth, dystocia"
    },
    {
      "question": "代る",
      "answer": "かわる",
      "meaning": "to succeed, to relieve, to replace, to take the place of, to substitute for, to take over for, to re"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸キュン",
      "answer": "むねキュン",
      "meaning": "heart pounding, chest tightening"
    },
    {
      "question": "気付",
      "answer": "きづけ,きつけ",
      "meaning": "care of (e.g. address on letter), c/o, encouragement, bringing around, resuscitation, stimulant, ton"
    },
    {
      "question": "条理",
      "answer": "じょうり",
      "meaning": "reason"
    },
    {
      "question": "輪姦",
      "answer": "りんかん",
      "meaning": "gang rape"
    },
    {
      "question": "落とし子",
      "answer": "おとしご",
      "meaning": "nobleman's illegitimate child, product (of e.g. war), offspring, aftermath"
    },
    {
      "question": "残心",
      "answer": "ざんしん",
      "meaning": "continued alertness, unrelaxed alertness, remaining on one's guard, being prepared for a counterstro"
    },
    {
      "question": "捕らわれ",
      "answer": "とらわれ",
      "meaning": "imprisonment, captive"
    },
    {
      "question": "穴倉",
      "answer": "あなぐら",
      "meaning": "cellar, cave, hole in the ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "緑地",
      "answer": "りょくち",
      "meaning": "green tract of land, green space"
    },
    {
      "question": "西欧",
      "answer": "せいおう",
      "meaning": "Western Europe, the West, the Occident, Europe"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄紙",
      "answer": "うすがみ",
      "meaning": "thin paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "字形",
      "answer": "じけい",
      "meaning": "character style, character form"
    },
    {
      "question": "国家的",
      "answer": "こっかてき",
      "meaning": "national"
    },
    {
      "question": "睦まじい",
      "answer": "むつまじい",
      "meaning": "harmonious (couple, family, etc.), happy, affectionate, friendly, intimate"
    },
    {
      "question": "前略",
      "answer": "ぜんりゃく",
      "meaning": "dispensing with the preliminaries ..., omitting the previous part"
    },
    {
      "question": "菊花",
      "answer": "きっか,きくか",
      "meaning": "chrysanthemum flower"
    },
    {
      "question": "出涸らし",
      "answer": "でがらし",
      "meaning": "used up (tea leaves, coffee grounds), insipid (tea, coffee made from such leaves or grounds), watery"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳥取",
      "answer": "とっとり",
      "meaning": "Tottori (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "税理士",
      "answer": "ぜいりし",
      "meaning": "tax counsellor, tax counselor, licensed tax accountant"
    },
    {
      "question": "擬",
      "answer": "もどき,ぎ",
      "meaning": "-like, pseudo-, mock ..., imitation ..., in the style of ..., comical character who mocks or apes th"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗黒街",
      "answer": "あんこくがい",
      "meaning": "the underworld"
    },
    {
      "question": "物販",
      "answer": "ぶっぱん",
      "meaning": "sale of goods (as opposed to services)"
    },
    {
      "question": "背部",
      "answer": "はいぶ",
      "meaning": "back"
    },
    {
      "question": "快音",
      "answer": "かいおん",
      "meaning": "pleasant sound, crack (of a baseball bat), roar (of a motor)"
    },
    {
      "question": "沐浴",
      "answer": "もくよく",
      "meaning": "bathing, washing one's body or hair, ablution, receiving a blessing"
    },
    {
      "question": "後編",
      "answer": "こうへん",
      "meaning": "latter part (of book, etc.), sequel, concluding part"
    },
    {
      "question": "淫売",
      "answer": "いんばい",
      "meaning": "prostitution, prostitute"
    },
    {
      "question": "先兵",
      "answer": "せんぺい",
      "meaning": "vanguard, advance-guard point, advance detachment, pioneer, avant-garde, leader"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆上がり",
      "answer": "さかあがり",
      "meaning": "(gymnastics) pulling oneself upward with a forward, circling movement, back hip circle"
    },
    {
      "question": "冬物",
      "answer": "ふゆもの",
      "meaning": "winter clothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "軽症",
      "answer": "けいしょう",
      "meaning": "minor illness"
    },
    {
      "question": "内申",
      "answer": "ないしん",
      "meaning": "unofficial report, confidential report"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪逆",
      "answer": "あくぎゃく",
      "meaning": "atrocity, treason"
    },
    {
      "question": "能率",
      "answer": "のうりつ",
      "meaning": "efficiency, moment (i.e. magnetic moment)"
    },
    {
      "question": "正夢",
      "answer": "まさゆめ",
      "meaning": "dream that comes true"
    },
    {
      "question": "働き詰め",
      "answer": "はたらきづめ",
      "meaning": "incessant working, working non-stop"
    },
    {
      "question": "邪視",
      "answer": "じゃし",
      "meaning": "evil eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "罅割れる",
      "answer": "ひびわれる",
      "meaning": "to crack, to develop a crack"
    },
    {
      "question": "湿原",
      "answer": "しつげん",
      "meaning": "marshy grassland, wetlands"
    },
    {
      "question": "潰走",
      "answer": "かいそう",
      "meaning": "rout, stampede"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎮",
      "answer": "ちん,しず",
      "meaning": "a weight, temple supervisor, town (of China)"
    },
    {
      "question": "献血",
      "answer": "けんけつ",
      "meaning": "blood donation"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺処分",
      "answer": "さつしょぶん,さっしょぶん",
      "meaning": "culling, putting down, slaughtering, killing"
    },
    {
      "question": "ゲーム脳",
      "answer": "ゲームのう",
      "meaning": "game brain, dementia caused by overuse of electronic games"
    },
    {
      "question": "原則的",
      "answer": "げんそくてき",
      "meaning": "general"
    },
    {
      "question": "流木",
      "answer": "りゅうぼく",
      "meaning": "driftwood"
    },
    {
      "question": "任意同行",
      "answer": "にんいどうこう",
      "meaning": "going along voluntarily to be questioned by police"
    },
    {
      "question": "孤独死",
      "answer": "こどくし",
      "meaning": "dying alone (esp. of someone who lives alone and dies of natural causes at home without anyone knowi"
    },
    {
      "question": "前門",
      "answer": "ぜんもん",
      "meaning": "front gate"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗愚",
      "answer": "あんぐ",
      "meaning": "imbecility, feeblemindedness, dark"
    },
    {
      "question": "眺望",
      "answer": "ちょうぼう",
      "meaning": "prospect, view, outlook"
    },
    {
      "question": "杓子定規",
      "answer": "しゃくしじょうぎ",
      "meaning": "strict, hidebound, inflexible, being a sticker for the rules, sticking hard and fast to the rules"
    },
    {
      "question": "縁起物",
      "answer": "えんぎもの",
      "meaning": "talisman, lucky charm"
    },
    {
      "question": "済まない",
      "answer": "すまない",
      "meaning": "inexcusable, unjustifiable, unpardonable, sorry, remorseful, apologetic, conscience-stricken, contri"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑味",
      "answer": "ざつみ",
      "meaning": "off-flavor, odd taste"
    },
    {
      "question": "凡ミス",
      "answer": "ぼんミス",
      "meaning": "basic mistake, careless mistake"
    },
    {
      "question": "縫い込む",
      "answer": "ぬいこむ",
      "meaning": "to sew in"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸囲",
      "answer": "きょうい",
      "meaning": "chest measurement"
    },
    {
      "question": "年功序列",
      "answer": "ねんこうじょれつ",
      "meaning": "seniority by length of service"
    },
    {
      "question": "十二使徒",
      "answer": "じゅうにしと",
      "meaning": "Twelve Apostles"
    },
    {
      "question": "右方",
      "answer": "うほう",
      "meaning": "right side, style of Japanese court music"
    },
    {
      "question": "農",
      "answer": "のう",
      "meaning": "farming, agriculture"
    },
    {
      "question": "音楽隊",
      "answer": "おんがくたい",
      "meaning": "band"
    },
    {
      "question": "幇助",
      "answer": "ほうじょ",
      "meaning": "assistance, backing, support, aiding and abetting (a crime), abetment"
    },
    {
      "question": "避雷針",
      "answer": "ひらいしん",
      "meaning": "lightning rod"
    },
    {
      "question": "要す",
      "answer": "ようす",
      "meaning": "to need, to require, to take, to demand"
    },
    {
      "question": "顔を売る",
      "answer": "かおをうる",
      "meaning": "to make oneself known to the public, to become popular, to gain influence"
    },
    {
      "question": "笑止千万",
      "answer": "しょうしせんばん",
      "meaning": "highly ridiculous, quite absurd"
    },
    {
      "question": "土蜘蛛",
      "answer": "つちぐも",
      "meaning": "Atypus karschi (Asian species of mygalomorph spider), tsuchigumo (people of ancient Japan who were n"
    },
    {
      "question": "口絵",
      "answer": "くちえ",
      "meaning": "illustration appearing in the first pages of a publication, frontispiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "家政",
      "answer": "かせい",
      "meaning": "household economy, housekeeping, homemaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "置手紙",
      "answer": "おきてがみ",
      "meaning": "letter left behind by someone who has departed, farewell letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "足回り",
      "answer": "あしまわり",
      "meaning": "suspension system (of a vehicle), undercarriage, area around one's feet, footwear"
    },
    {
      "question": "組織化",
      "answer": "そしきか",
      "meaning": "organization, organisation, systematization, systematisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "経験的",
      "answer": "けいけんてき",
      "meaning": "experiential, empirical, experimental"
    },
    {
      "question": "登壇",
      "answer": "とうだん",
      "meaning": "taking the podium, mounting the rostrum, going on stage to give a speech, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "萌芽",
      "answer": "ほうが",
      "meaning": "germination, germ, sprout, bud, sign"
    },
    {
      "question": "凡才",
      "answer": "ぼんさい",
      "meaning": "mediocrity, ordinary ability"
    },
    {
      "question": "寡聞",
      "answer": "かぶん",
      "meaning": "having little knowledge (of), being ill-informed"
    },
    {
      "question": "空きっ腹",
      "answer": "すきっぱら",
      "meaning": "empty stomach, hunger"
    },
    {
      "question": "非生産的",
      "answer": "ひせいさんてき",
      "meaning": "unproductive, counterproductive"
    },
    {
      "question": "急カーブ",
      "answer": "きゅうカーブ",
      "meaning": "sharp curve (turn)"
    },
    {
      "question": "玉藻",
      "answer": "たまも",
      "meaning": "seaweed"
    },
    {
      "question": "町奉行",
      "answer": "まちぶぎょう",
      "meaning": "(Edo-period) town magistrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "魏",
      "answer": "ぎ",
      "meaning": "Wei, Cao Wei, kingdom in China during the Three Kingdoms period (220-266), kingdom in China during t"
    },
    {
      "question": "私塾",
      "answer": "しじゅく",
      "meaning": "small private school (esp. for cramming), private school (in the Edo period, orig. run by Confuciani"
    },
    {
      "question": "阪神",
      "answer": "はんしん",
      "meaning": "Osaka-Kobe, Hanshin (company name: railway, dept. store, baseball team, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "防諜",
      "answer": "ぼうちょう",
      "meaning": "counterintelligence, counterespionage"
    },
    {
      "question": "日報",
      "answer": "にっぽう",
      "meaning": "daily report"
    },
    {
      "question": "内的",
      "answer": "ないてき",
      "meaning": "inner, intrinsic, mental, inherited"
    },
    {
      "question": "二十世紀",
      "answer": "にじっせいき,にじゅっせいき",
      "meaning": "twentieth century"
    },
    {
      "question": "指向",
      "answer": "しこう",
      "meaning": "being orientated (towards), pointing (towards), directing (towards), directional (e.g. microphone),"
    },
    {
      "question": "端切れ",
      "answer": "はぎれ",
      "meaning": "scrap of cloth, odds and ends"
    },
    {
      "question": "低層",
      "answer": "ていそう",
      "meaning": "low-rise (architecture), low-level, low-class"
    },
    {
      "question": "揉み上げ",
      "answer": "もみあげ",
      "meaning": "tuft of hair under temple, sideburns, sidelocks"
    },
    {
      "question": "当地",
      "answer": "とうち",
      "meaning": "this place, here"
    },
    {
      "question": "事務方",
      "answer": "じむかた",
      "meaning": "office workers, office staff, clerical staff"
    },
    {
      "question": "三拍子",
      "answer": "さんびょうし",
      "meaning": "triple time, three important requisites"
    },
    {
      "question": "原産",
      "answer": "げんさん",
      "meaning": "place of origin, habitat"
    },
    {
      "question": "見本市",
      "answer": "みほんいち",
      "meaning": "trade fair"
    },
    {
      "question": "餅は餅屋",
      "answer": "もちはもちや",
      "meaning": "every man knows his own business best, one should go to specialists for the best results, for rice c"
    },
    {
      "question": "叢雲",
      "answer": "むらくも,そううん",
      "meaning": "gathering clouds, group of clouds"
    },
    {
      "question": "佐伯",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "一子",
      "answer": "いっし",
      "meaning": "one child, only child, one of several children (esp. the son and heir), one stone (in the game of go"
    },
    {
      "question": "刑務官",
      "answer": "けいむかん",
      "meaning": "prison officer, corrections officer, penal officer, prison guard, jailor, warder"
    },
    {
      "question": "評議",
      "answer": "ひょうぎ",
      "meaning": "conference, discussion"
    },
    {
      "question": "野兎",
      "answer": "のうさぎ,やと",
      "meaning": "Japanese hare (Lepus brachyurus), wild rabbit"
    },
    {
      "question": "巳",
      "answer": "み,し",
      "meaning": "the Snake (sixth sign of the Chinese zodiac), the Serpent, hour of the Snake (around 10am, 9-11am, o"
    },
    {
      "question": "水虫",
      "answer": "みずむし",
      "meaning": "athlete's foot, water boatman (esp. species Hesperocorixa distanti), Asellus hilgendorfi (species of"
    },
    {
      "question": "管制塔",
      "answer": "かんせいとう",
      "meaning": "control tower"
    },
    {
      "question": "除雪",
      "answer": "じょせつ",
      "meaning": "snow removal"
    },
    {
      "question": "創生",
      "answer": "そうせい",
      "meaning": "creation, birth, formation, naissance, construction"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛇腹",
      "answer": "じゃばら",
      "meaning": "bellows (of an accordion, camera, etc.), cornice, rickrack, ricrac, wave-shaped braid, pleated shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "流言",
      "answer": "りゅうげん",
      "meaning": "groundless rumor (rumour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "家並み",
      "answer": "いえなみ,やなみ",
      "meaning": "row of houses, each house, every house, every door"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰途",
      "answer": "きと",
      "meaning": "on the way back, returning"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝ち越す",
      "answer": "かちこす",
      "meaning": "to have more wins than losses, to lead someone (by no. of matches), to take the lead over an opponen"
    },
    {
      "question": "昼ドラ",
      "answer": "ひるドラ",
      "meaning": "daytime television serial, soap opera"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄曇り",
      "answer": "うすぐもり",
      "meaning": "slightly cloudy"
    },
    {
      "question": "湿り",
      "answer": "しめり",
      "meaning": "dampness, humidity, moisture"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぶつ切り",
      "answer": "ぶつぎり",
      "meaning": "chunk, lump, thick slice, cutting into chunks"
    },
    {
      "question": "噎せ返る",
      "answer": "むせかえる",
      "meaning": "to choke, to be choked (by), to sob convulsively"
    },
    {
      "question": "売り切る",
      "answer": "うりきる",
      "meaning": "to sell out, to sell off"
    },
    {
      "question": "濡れ鼠",
      "answer": "ぬれねずみ",
      "meaning": "soaked to the skin, like a drowned rat"
    },
    {
      "question": "細る",
      "answer": "ほそる",
      "meaning": "to get thin, to taper off"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹の足し",
      "answer": "はらのたし",
      "meaning": "food to fill one's stomach, something to satisfy one's hunger"
    },
    {
      "question": "初孫",
      "answer": "ういまご,はつまご",
      "meaning": "first grandchild"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬼婆",
      "answer": "おにばば,おにばばあ",
      "meaning": "hag, witch, bitch, penurious or spiteful old woman, termagant, virago"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜天",
      "answer": "やてん",
      "meaning": "night sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "攻撃機",
      "answer": "こうげきき",
      "meaning": "attack aircraft"
    },
    {
      "question": "牌",
      "answer": "パイ,はい",
      "meaning": "tile, medal, shield, badge, card on which dharani (etc.) are written, notice board (in a Zen temple)"
    },
    {
      "question": "造物主",
      "answer": "ぞうぶつしゅ",
      "meaning": "the Creator, Maker"
    },
    {
      "question": "渡河",
      "answer": "とか",
      "meaning": "river crossing"
    },
    {
      "question": "銃火",
      "answer": "じゅうか",
      "meaning": "gunfire"
    },
    {
      "question": "僭称",
      "answer": "せんしょう",
      "meaning": "pretension, assumption (of a title)"
    },
    {
      "question": "航跡",
      "answer": "こうせき",
      "meaning": "wake (of boat)"
    },
    {
      "question": "白兵",
      "answer": "はくへい",
      "meaning": "unsheathed sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "割烹着",
      "answer": "かっぽうぎ",
      "meaning": "coverall apron, cook's apron"
    },
    {
      "question": "偉容",
      "answer": "いよう",
      "meaning": "dignified appearance, majestic appearance, imposing appearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "林業",
      "answer": "りんぎょう",
      "meaning": "forestry"
    },
    {
      "question": "沈着",
      "answer": "ちんちゃく",
      "meaning": "settling or depositing (at the bottom of something), deposition, pigmentation, composure, calmness"
    },
    {
      "question": "国立大学",
      "answer": "こくりつだいがく",
      "meaning": "national university"
    },
    {
      "question": "戸外",
      "answer": "こがい",
      "meaning": "open-air, outdoors"
    },
    {
      "question": "相俟って",
      "answer": "あいまって",
      "meaning": "coupled with, together"
    },
    {
      "question": "体色",
      "answer": "たいしょく",
      "meaning": "body color"
    },
    {
      "question": "時価",
      "answer": "じか",
      "meaning": "current value, price, market value"
    },
    {
      "question": "技術革新",
      "answer": "ぎじゅつかくしん",
      "meaning": "technological innovation"
    },
    {
      "question": "名前負け",
      "answer": "なまえまけ",
      "meaning": "failing to live up to one's name, being beaten by one's name"
    },
    {
      "question": "伏する",
      "answer": "ふくする",
      "meaning": "to crouch, to stoop, to bend down, to prostrate oneself, to lie down, to yield, to submit, to surren"
    },
    {
      "question": "特効",
      "answer": "とっこう",
      "meaning": "(having) striking effects, (producing) dramatic results, of particular efficacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "門下",
      "answer": "もんか",
      "meaning": "one's pupil, one's student, one's follower"
    },
    {
      "question": "恥骨",
      "answer": "ちこつ",
      "meaning": "pubis, pubes"
    },
    {
      "question": "職責",
      "answer": "しょくせき",
      "meaning": "one's duty, responsibilities pertaining to one's work"
    },
    {
      "question": "言下",
      "answer": "げんか,ごんか",
      "meaning": "promptly"
    },
    {
      "question": "家風",
      "answer": "かふう,いえかぜ",
      "meaning": "family tradition, wind blowing from the direction of one's home"
    },
    {
      "question": "避難勧告",
      "answer": "ひなんかんこく",
      "meaning": "evacuation advisory, official advice to evacuate"
    },
    {
      "question": "震源地",
      "answer": "しんげんち",
      "meaning": "epicenter, epicentre"
    },
    {
      "question": "座礁",
      "answer": "ざしょう",
      "meaning": "running aground, being stranded, grounding, beaching"
    },
    {
      "question": "身綺麗",
      "answer": "みぎれい",
      "meaning": "neat personal appearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "馴らす",
      "answer": "ならす",
      "meaning": "to accustom, to train (e.g. one's ear), to tame, to domesticate, to train (an animal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪ぐ",
      "answer": "すすぐ,そそぐ",
      "meaning": "to rinse, to wash out, to have one's revenge, to wipe out a disgrace"
    },
    {
      "question": "激論",
      "answer": "げきろん",
      "meaning": "heated argument, heated discussion, heated debate"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗り降り",
      "answer": "のりおり",
      "meaning": "getting on and off (a vehicle), boarding and alighting"
    },
    {
      "question": "公妃",
      "answer": "こうひ",
      "meaning": "noble's consort, consort of a prince, consort of a duke, duchess, princess"
    },
    {
      "question": "花街",
      "answer": "かがい,はなまち",
      "meaning": "red-light district, prostitution quarter, geisha quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "歌人",
      "answer": "かじん,うたびと",
      "meaning": "poet (of tanka poems), skillful tanka poet, official in charge of court poetry and music (ritsuryo p"
    },
    {
      "question": "一塁",
      "answer": "いちるい",
      "meaning": "first base, first baseman, one fort"
    },
    {
      "question": "投書",
      "answer": "とうしょ",
      "meaning": "letter (e.g. of complaint), letter to the editor, letter from a reader, contribution (to a newspaper"
    },
    {
      "question": "木苺",
      "answer": "きいちご",
      "meaning": "raspberry (any plant of genus Rubus, esp. Rubus palmatus var. coptophyllus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "腋の下",
      "answer": "わきのした",
      "meaning": "armpit, axilla"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦労性",
      "answer": "くろうしょう",
      "meaning": "nervous temperament, worry habit, pessimistic nature, pessimism"
    },
    {
      "question": "一間",
      "answer": "いっけん,ひとま",
      "meaning": "one ken, six feet, one room"
    },
    {
      "question": "進ぜる",
      "answer": "しんぜる",
      "meaning": "to offer, to present"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼け残る",
      "answer": "やけのこる",
      "meaning": "to escape being burned (esp. of a building or the items in it), to survive a fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "火の番",
      "answer": "ひのばん",
      "meaning": "night watch, fire watchman"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱戦",
      "answer": "ねっせん",
      "meaning": "fierce fight, close contest"
    },
    {
      "question": "色使い",
      "answer": "いろづかい",
      "meaning": "colour usage, color usage, use of colour"
    },
    {
      "question": "菖蒲",
      "answer": "しょうぶ,そうぶ,あやめ",
      "meaning": "sweet flag (Acorus calamus), calamus, Japanese iris (Iris ensata var. ensata), iris (flower), Siberi"
    },
    {
      "question": "氏子",
      "answer": "うじこ",
      "meaning": "shrine parishioner"
    },
    {
      "question": "石臼",
      "answer": "いしうす",
      "meaning": "stone mortar, millstone, quern"
    },
    {
      "question": "蟠る",
      "answer": "わだかまる",
      "meaning": "to lurk, to hover in the background, to be coiled up, to stretch tortuously"
    },
    {
      "question": "玉入れ",
      "answer": "たまいれ",
      "meaning": "ball-toss game, in which balls are thrown into a basket on a high pole (played at sports festivals)"
    },
    {
      "question": "石鹼",
      "answer": "せっけん",
      "meaning": "soap"
    },
    {
      "question": "鮮魚",
      "answer": "せんぎょ",
      "meaning": "fresh fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "心臓麻痺",
      "answer": "しんぞうまひ",
      "meaning": "cardioplegia, heart attack"
    },
    {
      "question": "専横",
      "answer": "せんおう",
      "meaning": "arbitrariness, despotism, high-handedness, tyranny"
    },
    {
      "question": "三曲",
      "answer": "さんきょく",
      "meaning": "instrumental trio"
    },
    {
      "question": "疎",
      "answer": "そ,おろ",
      "meaning": "sparse, distant (of a relationship), estranged, alienated, incompletely, insufficiently, partially,"
    },
    {
      "question": "酢漬け",
      "answer": "すづけ",
      "meaning": "pickling, pickles"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮え立つ",
      "answer": "にえたつ",
      "meaning": "to boil, to come to a boil, to seethe (with rage, etc.), to be furious"
    },
    {
      "question": "辞",
      "answer": "ことば,じ",
      "meaning": "language, dialect, word, words, phrase, term, expression, remark, speech, (manner of) speaking, lear"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉体美",
      "answer": "にくたいび",
      "meaning": "physical beauty"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰が低い",
      "answer": "こしがひくい",
      "meaning": "humble, modest"
    },
    {
      "question": "陸戦隊",
      "answer": "りくせんたい",
      "meaning": "landing force"
    },
    {
      "question": "函",
      "answer": "はこ",
      "meaning": "box, case, chest, package, pack, crate, car (of a train, etc.), shamisen case, shamisen, public buil"
    },
    {
      "question": "把手",
      "answer": "とって,はしゅ",
      "meaning": "handle, grip, knob"
    },
    {
      "question": "佇立",
      "answer": "ちょりつ",
      "meaning": "standing still"
    },
    {
      "question": "豚骨",
      "answer": "とんこつ",
      "meaning": "dish made with pork belly and bones, simmered with miso, sake, vegetables, etc. (from Kagoshima)"
    },
    {
      "question": "褥",
      "answer": "しとね,じょく",
      "meaning": "cushion, pillow, mattress"
    },
    {
      "question": "沿線",
      "answer": "えんせん",
      "meaning": "alongside a railway line, bus route, major thoroughfare, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "環状",
      "answer": "かんじょう",
      "meaning": "annulation, ring shape, loop shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "口減らし",
      "answer": "くちべらし",
      "meaning": "reducing the number of mouths one needs to feed (esp. by giving up children for adoption, apprentice"
    },
    {
      "question": "主成分",
      "answer": "しゅせいぶん",
      "meaning": "main ingredient, main component"
    },
    {
      "question": "固定電話",
      "answer": "こていでんわ",
      "meaning": "landline telephone, fixed-line telephone"
    },
    {
      "question": "踏み場",
      "answer": "ふみば",
      "meaning": "place to stand"
    },
    {
      "question": "今は昔",
      "answer": "いまはむかし",
      "meaning": "once upon a time, a long time ago"
    },
    {
      "question": "石神",
      "answer": "しゃくじん,いしがみ",
      "meaning": "stone which is worshipped, image of a god in stone"
    },
    {
      "question": "助祭",
      "answer": "じょさい",
      "meaning": "deacon (Catholic)"
    },
    {
      "question": "主翼",
      "answer": "しゅよく",
      "meaning": "main wings (of an aeroplane, airplane)"
    },
    {
      "question": "谺",
      "answer": "こだま",
      "meaning": "echo, reverberation, spirit of a tree, tree spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "女給",
      "answer": "じょきゅう",
      "meaning": "waitress, hostess"
    },
    {
      "question": "金粉",
      "answer": "きんぷん,きんこ",
      "meaning": "gold dust"
    },
    {
      "question": "下位互換",
      "answer": "かいごかん",
      "meaning": "upward compatible, forward compatible, compatible with input or components intended for higher tier"
    },
    {
      "question": "水攻め",
      "answer": "みずぜめ",
      "meaning": "inundating a castle, cutting off a castle's water supply"
    },
    {
      "question": "蟄居",
      "answer": "ちっきょ",
      "meaning": "keeping house, being confined to one's house"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹這い",
      "answer": "はらばい",
      "meaning": "lying on one's belly, crawling on one's belly, belly crawl"
    },
    {
      "question": "商機",
      "answer": "しょうき",
      "meaning": "business opportunity"
    },
    {
      "question": "図抜ける",
      "answer": "ずぬける",
      "meaning": "to tower above, to stand out"
    },
    {
      "question": "自愛",
      "answer": "じあい",
      "meaning": "taking care of oneself (esp. used as an epistolary imperative), self-love"
    },
    {
      "question": "狩り出す",
      "answer": "かりだす",
      "meaning": "to hunt out, to flush out, to round up, to impress, to recruit"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝御飯",
      "answer": "あさごはん",
      "meaning": "breakfast"
    },
    {
      "question": "減量",
      "answer": "げんりょう",
      "meaning": "loss in weight (esp. body weight), weight reduction, loss in quantity, reduction of quantity"
    },
    {
      "question": "血路",
      "answer": "けつろ",
      "meaning": "way out, means of escape"
    },
    {
      "question": "血糖値",
      "answer": "けっとうち",
      "meaning": "blood sugar level"
    },
    {
      "question": "金的",
      "answer": "きんてき",
      "meaning": "bull's-eye, object of desire, most-coveted goal, male crotch (as a target in fighting), the jewels ("
    },
    {
      "question": "柑橘類",
      "answer": "かんきつるい",
      "meaning": "citrus fruits"
    },
    {
      "question": "柔軟体操",
      "answer": "じゅうなんたいそう",
      "meaning": "calisthenics"
    },
    {
      "question": "突き倒す",
      "answer": "つきたおす",
      "meaning": "to push down, to knock down"
    },
    {
      "question": "細目",
      "answer": "さいもく,ほそめ",
      "meaning": "particulars, details, specified items, narrow eyes, fine texture, thinnish, somewhat narrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "舌の根",
      "answer": "したのね",
      "meaning": "base of the tongue, root of the tongue"
    },
    {
      "question": "一家言",
      "answer": "いっかげん,いっかごと",
      "meaning": "private opinion, personal view, personal opinion"
    },
    {
      "question": "降魔",
      "answer": "ごうま",
      "meaning": "conquering the devil"
    },
    {
      "question": "筏",
      "answer": "いかだ",
      "meaning": "raft, forearm protector, skewered baby-eel kabayaki"
    },
    {
      "question": "漏出",
      "answer": "ろうしゅつ",
      "meaning": "leaking out, leak"
    },
    {
      "question": "体技",
      "answer": "たいぎ",
      "meaning": "boxing and jujitsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "変事",
      "answer": "へんじ",
      "meaning": "accident, emergency, calamity"
    },
    {
      "question": "急流",
      "answer": "きゅうりゅう",
      "meaning": "swift current, rapids"
    },
    {
      "question": "扇形",
      "answer": "おうぎがた,せんけい",
      "meaning": "fan shape, sector"
    },
    {
      "question": "水揚げ",
      "answer": "みずあげ",
      "meaning": "landing, unloading (e.g. a ship), catch (of fish), takings, sales (of a shop), defloration (e.g. of"
    },
    {
      "question": "生ずる",
      "answer": "しょうずる",
      "meaning": "to produce, to yield, to cause, to result from, to arise, to be generated"
    },
    {
      "question": "施工",
      "answer": "せこう,しこう",
      "meaning": "construction, constructing, carrying out, work, formation, workmanship, execution"
    },
    {
      "question": "黎明期",
      "answer": "れいめいき",
      "meaning": "dawning (of a new era), dawn"
    },
    {
      "question": "国民性",
      "answer": "こくみんせい",
      "meaning": "national traits or character, nationality"
    },
    {
      "question": "字体",
      "answer": "じたい",
      "meaning": "form of a character (e.g. simplified, traditional), type, typeface, font"
    },
    {
      "question": "姫神",
      "answer": "ひめがみ,ひめかみ",
      "meaning": "goddess"
    },
    {
      "question": "東都",
      "answer": "とうと",
      "meaning": "the Eastern Capital (now Tokyo), Yedo, Edo"
    },
    {
      "question": "党首",
      "answer": "とうしゅ",
      "meaning": "party leader"
    },
    {
      "question": "横丁",
      "answer": "よこちょう",
      "meaning": "bystreet, side street, back street, alley, lane"
    },
    {
      "question": "寵姫",
      "answer": "ちょうき",
      "meaning": "one's favorite mistress, one's favourite mistress"
    },
    {
      "question": "保養地",
      "answer": "ほようち",
      "meaning": "health resort"
    },
    {
      "question": "胴着",
      "answer": "どうぎ",
      "meaning": "(sleeveless) undergarment, padded undershirt"
    },
    {
      "question": "告解",
      "answer": "こっかい",
      "meaning": "confession"
    },
    {
      "question": "車軸",
      "answer": "しゃじく",
      "meaning": "axle"
    },
    {
      "question": "淀",
      "answer": "よどみ,よど",
      "meaning": "stagnation, deposit, sediment, backwater, faltering, hesitation, pause, pool (in river)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小判",
      "answer": "こばん",
      "meaning": "koban, small oval gold coin used in the Edo period, oval, elliptical, oblong, small size (of paper)"
    },
    {
      "question": "水系",
      "answer": "すいけい",
      "meaning": "water system, river system, drainage system"
    },
    {
      "question": "公達",
      "answer": "きんだち,こうたつ",
      "meaning": "kings, children of nobles, young nobleman, official announcement"
    },
    {
      "question": "勅令",
      "answer": "ちょくれい",
      "meaning": "(imperial) edict"
    },
    {
      "question": "重婚",
      "answer": "じゅうこん",
      "meaning": "bigamy"
    },
    {
      "question": "技術屋",
      "answer": "ぎじゅつや",
      "meaning": "engineer, technician"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺ぐ",
      "answer": "そぐ",
      "meaning": "to chip (off), to shave (off), to slice (off), to sharpen, to dampen (e.g. enthusiasm), to discourag"
    },
    {
      "question": "積乱雲",
      "answer": "せきらんうん",
      "meaning": "cumulonimbus cloud"
    },
    {
      "question": "本線",
      "answer": "ほんせん",
      "meaning": "main line, trunk line"
    },
    {
      "question": "生木",
      "answer": "なまき",
      "meaning": "live tree, green wood, unseasoned wood"
    },
    {
      "question": "導線",
      "answer": "どうせん",
      "meaning": "conducting wire"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱気流",
      "answer": "らんきりゅう",
      "meaning": "(air) turbulence, turbulent air"
    },
    {
      "question": "本道",
      "answer": "ほんどう",
      "meaning": "highway, main road, the right road, internal medicine (in Chinese medical practice)"
    },
    {
      "question": "侵犯",
      "answer": "しんぱん",
      "meaning": "violation (of foreign territory, rights, etc.), invasion, infringement"
    },
    {
      "question": "噤む",
      "answer": "つぐむ",
      "meaning": "to shut one's mouth, to hold one's tongue, to keep silent"
    },
    {
      "question": "不成立",
      "answer": "ふせいりつ",
      "meaning": "failure, rejection, rupture"
    },
    {
      "question": "運が向く",
      "answer": "うんがむく",
      "meaning": "to be in luck's way, to get lucky"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛虎",
      "answer": "もうこ",
      "meaning": "fierce tiger, ferocious tiger, Hanshin Tigers (baseball team)"
    },
    {
      "question": "岡山",
      "answer": "おかやま",
      "meaning": "Okayama (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "銃把",
      "answer": "じゅうは",
      "meaning": "grip of a gun"
    },
    {
      "question": "零落",
      "answer": "れいらく",
      "meaning": "falling into straitened circumstances, downfall, ruin"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍閥",
      "answer": "ぐんばつ",
      "meaning": "military clique or party"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍需",
      "answer": "ぐんじゅ",
      "meaning": "munitions, military stores"
    },
    {
      "question": "ラム酒",
      "answer": "ラムしゅ",
      "meaning": "rum"
    },
    {
      "question": "三つ葉",
      "answer": "みつば",
      "meaning": "mitsuba (Cryptotaenia japonica), Japanese honewort, Japanese honeywort, Japanese chervil, Japanese p"
    },
    {
      "question": "宣教師",
      "answer": "せんきょうし",
      "meaning": "missionary"
    },
    {
      "question": "妾腹",
      "answer": "しょうふく,めかけばら",
      "meaning": "illegitimate (e.g. born to a mistress)"
    },
    {
      "question": "彫刻家",
      "answer": "ちょうこくか",
      "meaning": "engraver, carver, sculptor"
    },
    {
      "question": "風力",
      "answer": "ふうりょく",
      "meaning": "wind power, force (level on the Beaufort wind speed scale)"
    },
    {
      "question": "本読み",
      "answer": "ほんよみ",
      "meaning": "script reading, scenario reading, avid reader, bookworm, reading a book, reading books"
    },
    {
      "question": "旗を振る",
      "answer": "はたをふる",
      "meaning": "to wave a flag, to show the way"
    },
    {
      "question": "頑迷",
      "answer": "がんめい",
      "meaning": "bigoted, obstinate, stubborn, pigheaded"
    },
    {
      "question": "注ぎ足す",
      "answer": "つぎたす",
      "meaning": "to top up (drinks, water, rice, etc.), to replenish"
    },
    {
      "question": "眼科",
      "answer": "がんか",
      "meaning": "ophthalmology"
    },
    {
      "question": "出世払い",
      "answer": "しゅっせばらい",
      "meaning": "repaying a debt after achieving success, promise to repay a debt after achieving success"
    },
    {
      "question": "使い古し",
      "answer": "つかいふるし",
      "meaning": "worn-out"
    },
    {
      "question": "卯月",
      "answer": "うづき,うつき,うずき",
      "meaning": "fourth month of the lunar calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "筑波",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "徒花",
      "answer": "あだばな,むだばな",
      "meaning": "non-fruit-bearing flower, something that is flashy with no content, blossom which fails to produce f"
    },
    {
      "question": "不知火",
      "answer": "しらぬい,しらぬひ",
      "meaning": "phosphorescent light, mysterious lights on the sea, sea fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "午",
      "answer": "うま,ひる",
      "meaning": "the Horse (seventh sign of the Chinese zodiac), hour of the Horse (around noon, 11am-1pm, or 12 noon"
    },
    {
      "question": "諧謔",
      "answer": "かいぎゃく",
      "meaning": "joke, jest, banter"
    },
    {
      "question": "下生え",
      "answer": "したばえ",
      "meaning": "underbrush, undergrowth"
    },
    {
      "question": "選択科目",
      "answer": "せんたくかもく",
      "meaning": "elective subject or course"
    },
    {
      "question": "飾り棚",
      "answer": "かざりだな",
      "meaning": "display shelf or case"
    },
    {
      "question": "必修",
      "answer": "ひっしゅう",
      "meaning": "required (subject)"
    },
    {
      "question": "途中下車",
      "answer": "とちゅうげしゃ",
      "meaning": "stopover (during a train or bus journey)"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲面",
      "answer": "きょくめん",
      "meaning": "curved surface"
    },
    {
      "question": "着工",
      "answer": "ちゃっこう",
      "meaning": "starting (construction) work"
    },
    {
      "question": "記録的",
      "answer": "きろくてき",
      "meaning": "record(-setting)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一儲け",
      "answer": "ひともうけ",
      "meaning": "making money, making a profit"
    },
    {
      "question": "非業の死",
      "answer": "ひごうのし",
      "meaning": "unnatural death, violent death"
    },
    {
      "question": "底を突く",
      "answer": "そこをつく",
      "meaning": "to run out of, to dry up, to be depleted, to hit the bottom, to bottom out"
    },
    {
      "question": "少額",
      "answer": "しょうがく",
      "meaning": "small sum (e.g. of money), small denomination"
    },
    {
      "question": "大食漢",
      "answer": "たいしょくかん",
      "meaning": "great eater, glutton"
    },
    {
      "question": "憑代",
      "answer": "よりしろ",
      "meaning": "object representative of a divine spirit, object to which a spirit is drawn or summoned, object or a"
    },
    {
      "question": "事務次官",
      "answer": "じむじかん",
      "meaning": "permanent vice-president, undersecretary, vice-minister"
    },
    {
      "question": "鷺",
      "answer": "さぎ",
      "meaning": "heron (Ardeidae)"
    },
    {
      "question": "覚醒剤",
      "answer": "かくせいざい",
      "meaning": "stimulant (e.g. psychoactive drugs like methamphetamine, ritalin, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大旦那",
      "answer": "おおだんな",
      "meaning": "master, head of household, man of the house, principal supporter of a temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "検察官",
      "answer": "けんさつかん",
      "meaning": "public prosecutor"
    },
    {
      "question": "全天",
      "answer": "ぜんてん",
      "meaning": "all heaven"
    },
    {
      "question": "曇",
      "answer": "くもり",
      "meaning": "cloudiness, cloudy weather, fog (on a mirror, glasses, etc.), cloud (e.g. in marble), blur, mist, sh"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬券",
      "answer": "ばけん",
      "meaning": "(horse racing) betting ticket"
    },
    {
      "question": "執刀",
      "answer": "しっとう",
      "meaning": "performing a surgical operation"
    },
    {
      "question": "白無垢",
      "answer": "しろむく",
      "meaning": "white kimono"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉢巻き",
      "answer": "はちまき",
      "meaning": "headband"
    },
    {
      "question": "轟沈",
      "answer": "ごうちん",
      "meaning": "sinking a ship instantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "開陳",
      "answer": "かいちん",
      "meaning": "stating (one's views), expressing"
    },
    {
      "question": "胴元",
      "answer": "どうもと",
      "meaning": "banker (gambling), bookmaker, person who runs a gambling den, person who rents out space for gamblin"
    },
    {
      "question": "量子力学",
      "answer": "りょうしりきがく",
      "meaning": "quantum mechanics"
    },
    {
      "question": "称す",
      "answer": "しょうす",
      "meaning": "to take the name of, to call oneself, to pretend, to feign, to purport"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏物",
      "answer": "なつもの",
      "meaning": "summer goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "連鎖反応",
      "answer": "れんさはんのう",
      "meaning": "chain reaction, nuclear chain reaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "関東地方",
      "answer": "かんとうちほう",
      "meaning": "Kanto region (incl. Tokyo, Kanagawa, Saitama, Gunma, Tochigi, Ibaraki and Chiba prefectures)"
    },
    {
      "question": "家財",
      "answer": "かざい",
      "meaning": "household belongings, household goods, family fortune, family assets"
    },
    {
      "question": "照り",
      "answer": "てり",
      "meaning": "sunshine, dry weather, luster, lustre"
    },
    {
      "question": "部会",
      "answer": "ぶかい",
      "meaning": "section meeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "降霊",
      "answer": "こうれい",
      "meaning": "communication with the dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "縄梯子",
      "answer": "なわばしご",
      "meaning": "rope ladder"
    },
    {
      "question": "血の池",
      "answer": "ちのいけ",
      "meaning": "Blood Pond, pool of blood, pond of blood (in hell)"
    },
    {
      "question": "姦",
      "answer": "かん",
      "meaning": "cunning and wickedness, cunning and wicked person"
    },
    {
      "question": "持て成す",
      "answer": "もてなす",
      "meaning": "to entertain, to make welcome"
    },
    {
      "question": "速読",
      "answer": "そくどく",
      "meaning": "speed reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "凡",
      "answer": "おおよそ,ぼん",
      "meaning": "about, roughly, approximately, generally, on the whole, as a rule, completely, quite, entirely, alto"
    },
    {
      "question": "結納",
      "answer": "ゆいのう",
      "meaning": "engagement gift, (ceremonial) exchange of engagement gifts"
    },
    {
      "question": "去ぬ",
      "answer": "いぬ",
      "meaning": "to go home, to go, to leave, to pass (of time), to die, to go bad, to rot"
    },
    {
      "question": "一問",
      "answer": "いちもん",
      "meaning": "one question"
    },
    {
      "question": "名を売る",
      "answer": "なをうる",
      "meaning": "to gain a reputation, to make oneself famous"
    },
    {
      "question": "紀伊",
      "answer": "きい",
      "meaning": "Kii (former province located in present-day Wakayama and southern Mie prefectures)"
    },
    {
      "question": "卓袱台",
      "answer": "ちゃぶだい",
      "meaning": "low dining table, tea table"
    },
    {
      "question": "債権",
      "answer": "さいけん",
      "meaning": "credit, claim"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄色",
      "answer": "てついろ",
      "meaning": "reddish-black, iron blue"
    },
    {
      "question": "安全ピン",
      "answer": "あんぜんピン",
      "meaning": "safety pin"
    },
    {
      "question": "ひとり言",
      "answer": "ひとりごと",
      "meaning": "soliloquy, monologue, speaking to oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "一献",
      "answer": "いっこん",
      "meaning": "one cup (of sake), (going out for, treating someone to) a drink, small drinking party"
    },
    {
      "question": "霜降り",
      "answer": "しもふり",
      "meaning": "speckled with white, salt-and-pepper (pattern, fabric, etc.), marbling (of beef), (of fish, chicken,"
    },
    {
      "question": "遥々",
      "answer": "はるばる",
      "meaning": "from afar, over a great distance, all the way"
    },
    {
      "question": "老廃物",
      "answer": "ろうはいぶつ",
      "meaning": "waste products"
    },
    {
      "question": "肝心要",
      "answer": "かんじんかなめ",
      "meaning": "crucial, key, most important, main (point)"
    },
    {
      "question": "洗い出し",
      "answer": "あらいだし",
      "meaning": "exposure by washing away, washing out, washout, exposed aggregate (finish), exposed aggregate concre"
    },
    {
      "question": "評議員",
      "answer": "ひょうぎいん",
      "meaning": "trustee, councillor (councilor)"
    },
    {
      "question": "復活祭",
      "answer": "ふっかつさい",
      "meaning": "Easter"
    },
    {
      "question": "烏賊",
      "answer": "いか",
      "meaning": "cuttlefish, squid"
    },
    {
      "question": "組分け",
      "answer": "くみわけ",
      "meaning": "division into groups, separation into classes (e.g. of schoolchildren according to ability)"
    },
    {
      "question": "寿",
      "answer": "ことぶき,じゅ",
      "meaning": "congratulations, felicitations, best wishes, longevity, long life, age, years, congratulation, celeb"
    },
    {
      "question": "中庸",
      "answer": "ちゅうよう",
      "meaning": "middle way, (golden) mean, moderation, middle path, the Doctrine of the Mean (one of the Four Books)"
    },
    {
      "question": "車列",
      "answer": "しゃれつ",
      "meaning": "motorcade"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾着",
      "answer": "だんちゃく",
      "meaning": "hit (of a bullet, shell, etc.), impact"
    },
    {
      "question": "滓",
      "answer": "かす",
      "meaning": "dregs, sediment, grounds, meal, lees (esp. sake), leftovers, by-product, worthless item, junk, dregs"
    },
    {
      "question": "和歌",
      "answer": "わか",
      "meaning": "waka, classic Japanese poem, esp. a tanka, often 31 morae"
    },
    {
      "question": "番線",
      "answer": "ばんせん",
      "meaning": "track number"
    },
    {
      "question": "雄牛",
      "answer": "おうし",
      "meaning": "bull, ox, steer"
    },
    {
      "question": "誰得",
      "answer": "だれとく",
      "meaning": "meaningless, pointless"
    },
    {
      "question": "先頃",
      "answer": "さきごろ,せんころ",
      "meaning": "recently, the other day"
    },
    {
      "question": "巻末",
      "answer": "かんまつ",
      "meaning": "end of a book"
    },
    {
      "question": "兜を脱ぐ",
      "answer": "かぶとをぬぐ",
      "meaning": "to accept one's inferiority, to take one's hat off to someone, to give up, to surrender, to strike o"
    },
    {
      "question": "近日",
      "answer": "きんじつ",
      "meaning": "soon, in a few days"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ裸",
      "answer": "まっぱだか",
      "meaning": "nudity, stark naked"
    },
    {
      "question": "再検討",
      "answer": "さいけんとう",
      "meaning": "re-examination, review, reconsideration, reappraisal"
    },
    {
      "question": "医官",
      "answer": "いかん",
      "meaning": "medical officer"
    },
    {
      "question": "亡",
      "answer": "ぼう",
      "meaning": "death, the late, the deceased"
    },
    {
      "question": "白桃",
      "answer": "はくとう",
      "meaning": "white peach"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂山",
      "answer": "すなやま,さやま",
      "meaning": "sand hill, dune"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒙昧",
      "answer": "もうまい",
      "meaning": "ignorance, (lack of) enlightenment or civilization (civilisation), unenlightened, uncivilized, unciv"
    },
    {
      "question": "猟奇",
      "answer": "りょうき",
      "meaning": "seeking the bizarre (abnormal, grotesque, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "低気圧",
      "answer": "ていきあつ",
      "meaning": "low (atmospheric) pressure, low-pressure system, depression, cyclone, bad temper, foul mood, tense s"
    },
    {
      "question": "買い占め",
      "answer": "かいしめ",
      "meaning": "buying up of goods, cornering (market)"
    },
    {
      "question": "無き者",
      "answer": "なきもの",
      "meaning": "dead person"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱水",
      "answer": "だっすい",
      "meaning": "evaporation, dehydration, desiccation"
    },
    {
      "question": "出し渋る",
      "answer": "だししぶる",
      "meaning": "to grudge, to be stingy, to be unwilling to pay"
    },
    {
      "question": "食指",
      "answer": "しょくし,ひとさしゆび",
      "meaning": "index finger, forefinger"
    },
    {
      "question": "長生",
      "answer": "ちょうせい",
      "meaning": "longevity"
    },
    {
      "question": "六大",
      "answer": "ろくだい",
      "meaning": "the six elements (earth, water, fire, wind, void, and consciousness)"
    },
    {
      "question": "猫又",
      "answer": "ねこまた",
      "meaning": "mythical two-tailed monster cat"
    },
    {
      "question": "八八",
      "answer": "はちはち",
      "meaning": "two eights, hachi-hachi (type of hanafuda game)"
    },
    {
      "question": "全知",
      "answer": "ぜんち",
      "meaning": "omniscience"
    },
    {
      "question": "将棋盤",
      "answer": "しょうぎばん",
      "meaning": "shogi board"
    },
    {
      "question": "手桶",
      "answer": "ておけ",
      "meaning": "pail, bucket"
    },
    {
      "question": "近親",
      "answer": "きんしん",
      "meaning": "near relative"
    },
    {
      "question": "若草",
      "answer": "わかくさ",
      "meaning": "green grass, young (fresh) grass"
    },
    {
      "question": "相合い傘",
      "answer": "あいあいがさ",
      "meaning": "sharing an umbrella, under one umbrella"
    },
    {
      "question": "無生物",
      "answer": "むせいぶつ",
      "meaning": "inanimate object"
    },
    {
      "question": "入園",
      "answer": "にゅうえん",
      "meaning": "enrollment in kindergarten, enrolment in kindergarten, entering a park, garden, zoo, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "食べ物屋",
      "answer": "たべものや",
      "meaning": "eatery, restaurant"
    },
    {
      "question": "参り",
      "answer": "まいり",
      "meaning": "visit (to a religious site, e.g. shrine, temple, grave)"
    },
    {
      "question": "江戸っ子",
      "answer": "えどっこ",
      "meaning": "true Tokyoite, Edoite, person born and raised in Edo"
    },
    {
      "question": "税関",
      "answer": "ぜいかん",
      "meaning": "customs, customs house"
    },
    {
      "question": "四次元",
      "answer": "よじげん,しじげん",
      "meaning": "fourth dimension, four dimensions"
    },
    {
      "question": "急転",
      "answer": "きゅうてん",
      "meaning": "sudden change, sudden turn"
    },
    {
      "question": "親類縁者",
      "answer": "しんるいえんじゃ",
      "meaning": "one's relatives by blood and marriage (in blood and law), one's kith and kin"
    },
    {
      "question": "舞子",
      "answer": "まいこ",
      "meaning": "maiko, apprentice geisha, dancing girl"
    },
    {
      "question": "修験者",
      "answer": "しゅげんじゃ",
      "meaning": "mountain ascetic, practitioner of Shugendō"
    },
    {
      "question": "動的",
      "answer": "どうてき",
      "meaning": "dynamic, kinetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "防空壕",
      "answer": "ぼうくうごう",
      "meaning": "air-raid shelter, bomb shelter"
    },
    {
      "question": "油田",
      "answer": "ゆでん",
      "meaning": "oil field"
    },
    {
      "question": "語り手",
      "answer": "かたりて",
      "meaning": "narrator, storyteller, reciter"
    },
    {
      "question": "魚肉",
      "answer": "ぎょにく",
      "meaning": "fish meat"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉園",
      "answer": "へいえん",
      "meaning": "closing of a park (e.g. theme park, botanical garden, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "川下",
      "answer": "かわしも",
      "meaning": "downstream"
    },
    {
      "question": "声紋",
      "answer": "せいもん",
      "meaning": "voiceprint"
    },
    {
      "question": "傾聴",
      "answer": "けいちょう",
      "meaning": "listening closely"
    },
    {
      "question": "地声",
      "answer": "じごえ",
      "meaning": "one's natural voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "輝かす",
      "answer": "かがやかす",
      "meaning": "to light up, to brighten"
    },
    {
      "question": "煽てる",
      "answer": "おだてる",
      "meaning": "to flatter, to soft-soap, to sweet talk, to cajole, to instigate"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆風",
      "answer": "ぎゃくふう,さかかぜ",
      "meaning": "headwind, adverse wind, ascending vertical sword attack (kendo, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "入れ違う",
      "answer": "いれちがう",
      "meaning": "to pass each other, to cross paths"
    },
    {
      "question": "二番煎じ",
      "answer": "にばんせんじ",
      "meaning": "rehash, (boring) rerun, second brew of tea"
    },
    {
      "question": "出尽くす",
      "answer": "でつくす",
      "meaning": "to be all out, to exhaust"
    },
    {
      "question": "越中",
      "answer": "えっちゅう",
      "meaning": "Etchū (former province located in present-day Toyama Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "感謝祭",
      "answer": "かんしゃさい",
      "meaning": "Thanksgiving (US, Canada)"
    },
    {
      "question": "十手",
      "answer": "じって,じってい",
      "meaning": "jitte, short truncheon with a hook made of metal or wood (used by policemen and private thief-takers"
    },
    {
      "question": "司法解剖",
      "answer": "しほうかいぼう",
      "meaning": "legally ordered autopsy"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒星",
      "answer": "くろぼし",
      "meaning": "black spot, black dot, bull's-eye, mark indicating a defeat, loss, failure, mistake, faux pas"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ向",
      "answer": "まっこう",
      "meaning": "directly opposite, right in front, middle of the forehead, helmet front"
    },
    {
      "question": "噴出す",
      "answer": "ふきだす",
      "meaning": "to spout out, to spurt out, to gush out, to jet out, to sprout, to bud, to burst into laughter, to b"
    },
    {
      "question": "奴さん",
      "answer": "やっこさん",
      "meaning": "he, she, him, her, samurai's attendant (in a var. of origami), type of popular song accompanied by d"
    },
    {
      "question": "消印",
      "answer": "けしいん",
      "meaning": "postmark, (postal) cancellation mark"
    },
    {
      "question": "徐行",
      "answer": "じょこう",
      "meaning": "going slowly"
    },
    {
      "question": "凶報",
      "answer": "きょうほう",
      "meaning": "bad news, news of a death, death notice"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐変木",
      "answer": "とうへんぼく",
      "meaning": "oaf, bigot"
    },
    {
      "question": "売り歩く",
      "answer": "うりあるく",
      "meaning": "to peddle (goods), to hawk"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱燗",
      "answer": "あつかん",
      "meaning": "hot sake"
    },
    {
      "question": "万札",
      "answer": "まんさつ",
      "meaning": "10,000 yen bill"
    },
    {
      "question": "高卒",
      "answer": "こうそつ",
      "meaning": "high school graduate"
    },
    {
      "question": "文武",
      "answer": "ぶんぶ",
      "meaning": "literary and military arts, the pen and the sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "剛の者",
      "answer": "ごうのもの,こうのもの",
      "meaning": "very strong person, brave warrior, veteran"
    },
    {
      "question": "僻み",
      "answer": "ひがみ",
      "meaning": "prejudice, bias, warped view, jealousy, inferiority complex"
    },
    {
      "question": "日曜学校",
      "answer": "にちようがっこう",
      "meaning": "Sunday school"
    },
    {
      "question": "艦載",
      "answer": "かんさい",
      "meaning": "carrying aboard a warship"
    },
    {
      "question": "破魔",
      "answer": "はま",
      "meaning": "exorcism"
    },
    {
      "question": "無窮",
      "answer": "むきゅう",
      "meaning": "eternity, infinitude, immortality"
    },
    {
      "question": "共和制",
      "answer": "きょうわせい",
      "meaning": "republic, republicanism"
    },
    {
      "question": "婦警",
      "answer": "ふけい",
      "meaning": "policewoman"
    },
    {
      "question": "元妻",
      "answer": "もとつま",
      "meaning": "ex-wife, former wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "牧畜",
      "answer": "ぼくちく",
      "meaning": "stock-farming, livestock farming, cattle breeding"
    },
    {
      "question": "一句",
      "answer": "いっく",
      "meaning": "phrase (verse, line), one haiku-poem"
    },
    {
      "question": "綯い交ぜ",
      "answer": "ないまぜ",
      "meaning": "mixture, jumble, cord made by entwining threads of various colours"
    },
    {
      "question": "堪え忍ぶ",
      "answer": "たえしのぶ",
      "meaning": "to put up with, to endure, to bear patiently"
    },
    {
      "question": "申し立て",
      "answer": "もうしたて",
      "meaning": "statement, account (of something), declaration, allegation"
    },
    {
      "question": "出歯亀",
      "answer": "でばかめ,でばがめ",
      "meaning": "voyeur, Peeping Tom"
    },
    {
      "question": "緊密",
      "answer": "きんみつ",
      "meaning": "rigour, rigor, closeness, compactness, tightly knit"
    },
    {
      "question": "民意",
      "answer": "みんい",
      "meaning": "popular will, will of the people"
    },
    {
      "question": "大動脈",
      "answer": "だいどうみゃく",
      "meaning": "aorta, important traffic route"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛追",
      "answer": "もうつい",
      "meaning": "hot pursuit, hot chase"
    },
    {
      "question": "泥仕合",
      "answer": "どろじあい",
      "meaning": "mudslinging contest, mudslinging match"
    },
    {
      "question": "岩棚",
      "answer": "いわたな,いわだな",
      "meaning": "ledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "夢精",
      "answer": "むせい",
      "meaning": "wet dream, nocturnal emission"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻唄",
      "answer": "はなうた",
      "meaning": "humming, crooning"
    },
    {
      "question": "武名",
      "answer": "ぶめい",
      "meaning": "military fame"
    },
    {
      "question": "雉",
      "answer": "きじ,きぎす,きぎし",
      "meaning": "green pheasant (Phasianus versicolor), Japanese pheasant"
    },
    {
      "question": "産休",
      "answer": "さんきゅう",
      "meaning": "maternity leave, paternity leave"
    },
    {
      "question": "和牛",
      "answer": "わぎゅう",
      "meaning": "Wagyu beef, Japanese beef"
    },
    {
      "question": "掠り",
      "answer": "かすり",
      "meaning": "grazing, touching lightly, squeezing (someone for money), percentage, kickback"
    },
    {
      "question": "金運",
      "answer": "きんうん",
      "meaning": "economic fortune, luck with money"
    },
    {
      "question": "物干し竿",
      "answer": "ものほしざお",
      "meaning": "pole on which to hang laundry for drying, clothesline"
    },
    {
      "question": "円錐形",
      "answer": "えんすいけい",
      "meaning": "cone shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨戦",
      "answer": "りんせん",
      "meaning": "preparing for action or battle"
    },
    {
      "question": "濯ぐ",
      "answer": "すすぐ,そそぐ,ゆすぐ",
      "meaning": "to rinse, to wash out, to have one's revenge, to wipe out a disgrace"
    },
    {
      "question": "誹り",
      "answer": "そしり",
      "meaning": "censure, criticism, blame, disparagement, vilification"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り売り",
      "answer": "きりうり",
      "meaning": "selling by the piece"
    },
    {
      "question": "位置付け",
      "answer": "いちづけ,いちつけ",
      "meaning": "placement, fixed position, mapping out, location"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜なべ",
      "answer": "よなべ",
      "meaning": "night work"
    },
    {
      "question": "虫眼鏡",
      "answer": "むしめがね",
      "meaning": "magnifying glass, wrestler of the lowest rank"
    },
    {
      "question": "衝動買い",
      "answer": "しょうどうがい",
      "meaning": "impulse buying, impulse purchase"
    },
    {
      "question": "滅法",
      "answer": "めっぽう",
      "meaning": "extraordinarily, astonishingly, extremely, terribly, unreasonably, absurdly"
    },
    {
      "question": "恐怖政治",
      "answer": "きょうふせいじ",
      "meaning": "politics of fear, terrorism, reign of terror (esp. in the French revolution)"
    },
    {
      "question": "豪放磊落",
      "answer": "ごうほうらいらく",
      "meaning": "broadminded"
    },
    {
      "question": "住めば都",
      "answer": "すめばみやこ",
      "meaning": "you can get used to living anywhere, home is where you make it, wherever I lay my hat is home"
    },
    {
      "question": "一念発起",
      "answer": "いちねんほっき",
      "meaning": "being resolved to (do something), having a wholehearted intention"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯屋",
      "answer": "ゆや",
      "meaning": "public bathhouse, building with a bath (esp. in a shrine or temple)"
    },
    {
      "question": "山犬",
      "answer": "やまいぬ",
      "meaning": "Japanese wolf (Canis lupus hodophilax, extinct), wild dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "蔓草",
      "answer": "つるくさ",
      "meaning": "vine, creeper"
    },
    {
      "question": "維新",
      "answer": "いしん",
      "meaning": "reformation, revolution, renewal, Meiji Restoration"
    },
    {
      "question": "三一",
      "answer": "さんぴん",
      "meaning": "low-ranking samurai, rolling three and one (in a dice game)"
    },
    {
      "question": "素股",
      "answer": "すまた",
      "meaning": "bare thighs, inner thigh, intercrural sex"
    },
    {
      "question": "過日",
      "answer": "かじつ",
      "meaning": "the other day, some days ago, recently, a day in the past"
    },
    {
      "question": "印す",
      "answer": "しるす",
      "meaning": "to leave (a mark, trace, etc.), to print, to stamp, to be a sign of, to be an omen for"
    },
    {
      "question": "常態",
      "answer": "じょうたい",
      "meaning": "normal state (condition)"
    },
    {
      "question": "快眠",
      "answer": "かいみん",
      "meaning": "pleasant sleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "散会",
      "answer": "さんかい",
      "meaning": "adjournment"
    },
    {
      "question": "押し迫る",
      "answer": "おしせまる",
      "meaning": "to draw near"
    },
    {
      "question": "肩凝り",
      "answer": "かたこり",
      "meaning": "stiff neck, stiff shoulders"
    },
    {
      "question": "戻し",
      "answer": "もどし",
      "meaning": "returning, giving back"
    },
    {
      "question": "周期的",
      "answer": "しゅうきてき",
      "meaning": "periodic, cyclic"
    },
    {
      "question": "折れ",
      "answer": "おれ",
      "meaning": "fold, bend, broken part"
    },
    {
      "question": "手に乗る",
      "answer": "てにのる",
      "meaning": "to fall for a trick, to be taken in, to play into the hands (of)"
    },
    {
      "question": "七草",
      "answer": "ななくさ",
      "meaning": "the seven spring flowers, the seven fall flowers, the seven autumn flowers, the seventh of January,"
    },
    {
      "question": "棗",
      "answer": "なつめ",
      "meaning": "jujube (Ziziphus jujube), Chinese date, red date, small tea caddy (tea ceremony)"
    },
    {
      "question": "帝室",
      "answer": "ていしつ",
      "meaning": "Imperial Family, Imperial Household"
    },
    {
      "question": "府中",
      "answer": "ふちゅう",
      "meaning": "provincial capital (under the ritsuryo system), provincial office, public place of imperial rule"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉾",
      "answer": "ほこ",
      "meaning": "long-handled Chinese spear, lance, pike, weapon, arms, grip of a bow, parade float decorated with lo"
    },
    {
      "question": "蠱毒",
      "answer": "こどく",
      "meaning": "poisoning someone"
    },
    {
      "question": "前立腺",
      "answer": "ぜんりつせん",
      "meaning": "prostate gland"
    },
    {
      "question": "応ずる",
      "answer": "おうずる",
      "meaning": "to answer, to respond, to meet, to satisfy, to accept"
    },
    {
      "question": "遷都",
      "answer": "せんと",
      "meaning": "relocation of the capital, transfer of the capital"
    },
    {
      "question": "洋装",
      "answer": "ようそう",
      "meaning": "Western clothing, Western binding"
    },
    {
      "question": "議事",
      "answer": "ぎじ",
      "meaning": "proceedings (e.g. parliament, congress), business (of the day)"
    },
    {
      "question": "落城",
      "answer": "らくじょう",
      "meaning": "surrender (fall) of a castle"
    },
    {
      "question": "豆腐屋",
      "answer": "とうふや",
      "meaning": "tofu seller (maker)"
    },
    {
      "question": "原風景",
      "answer": "げんふうけい",
      "meaning": "indelible scene of one's childhood, earliest remembered scene"
    },
    {
      "question": "極薄",
      "answer": "きょくはく",
      "meaning": "ultrathinness"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱帯夜",
      "answer": "ねったいや",
      "meaning": "sultry night, sweltering night, night in which temperature doesn't fall below 25 degrees C"
    },
    {
      "question": "風来坊",
      "answer": "ふうらいぼう",
      "meaning": "wanderer, vagabond, capricious person, hobo"
    },
    {
      "question": "覗き窓",
      "answer": "のぞきまど",
      "meaning": "peephole (e.g. in a door), observation window, viewing window"
    },
    {
      "question": "心神喪失",
      "answer": "しんしんそうしつ",
      "meaning": "of unsound mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "実写",
      "answer": "じっしゃ",
      "meaning": "on-the-spot filming or photography, live filming (as opposed to animation), actual picture (as oppos"
    },
    {
      "question": "文無し",
      "answer": "もんなし",
      "meaning": "penniless, broke"
    },
    {
      "question": "刷新",
      "answer": "さっしん",
      "meaning": "reform, renovation"
    },
    {
      "question": "大根役者",
      "answer": "だいこんやくしゃ",
      "meaning": "ham actor"
    },
    {
      "question": "斥力",
      "answer": "せきりょく",
      "meaning": "repulsion, repulsive force"
    },
    {
      "question": "臣従",
      "answer": "しんじゅう",
      "meaning": "vassalage"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊郭",
      "answer": "ゆうかく",
      "meaning": "(licensed) red light district"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍装",
      "answer": "ぐんそう",
      "meaning": "soldier's equipment"
    },
    {
      "question": "原野",
      "answer": "げんや",
      "meaning": "waste land, wilderness, moor, field, plain"
    },
    {
      "question": "黙然",
      "answer": "もくねん,もくぜん",
      "meaning": "muteness, silence"
    },
    {
      "question": "綿飴",
      "answer": "わたあめ",
      "meaning": "cotton candy, fairy floss"
    },
    {
      "question": "根差す",
      "answer": "ねざす",
      "meaning": "to come from, to have roots in"
    },
    {
      "question": "非論理的",
      "answer": "ひろんりてき",
      "meaning": "illogical"
    },
    {
      "question": "星占い",
      "answer": "ほしうらない",
      "meaning": "astrology, horoscope"
    },
    {
      "question": "内政干渉",
      "answer": "ないせいかんしょう",
      "meaning": "interference in the domestic affairs of another country"
    },
    {
      "question": "嬢さん",
      "answer": "とうさん,じょうさん",
      "meaning": "daughter (of a good family), (another's) daughter, young lady (esp. of respectable upbringing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "入所",
      "answer": "にゅうしょ",
      "meaning": "admission (e.g. to a training institution, research establishment, social welfare facility, etc.), e"
    },
    {
      "question": "責め苛む",
      "answer": "せめさいなむ",
      "meaning": "to torture, to persecute, to excruciate"
    },
    {
      "question": "遮光",
      "answer": "しゃこう",
      "meaning": "shading, shielding from light"
    },
    {
      "question": "定数",
      "answer": "ていすう,じょうすう",
      "meaning": "fixed number, quorum (for an assembly), constant, invariable, literal, fate"
    },
    {
      "question": "粉薬",
      "answer": "こなぐすり,こぐすり",
      "meaning": "powdered medicine, powder"
    },
    {
      "question": "大勝",
      "answer": "たいしょう",
      "meaning": "great victory, crushing victory"
    },
    {
      "question": "名詞",
      "answer": "めいし,なことば",
      "meaning": "noun"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃品",
      "answer": "はいひん",
      "meaning": "waste, garbage"
    },
    {
      "question": "辛苦",
      "answer": "しんく",
      "meaning": "hardship, toil, trouble"
    },
    {
      "question": "端数",
      "answer": "はすう",
      "meaning": "fraction, odd amount, leftover amount"
    },
    {
      "question": "個人主義",
      "answer": "こじんしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "individualism, egoism, selfishness"
    },
    {
      "question": "付属品",
      "answer": "ふぞくひん",
      "meaning": "accessory, fittings, appurtenances"
    },
    {
      "question": "御魂",
      "answer": "みたま",
      "meaning": "spirit of a deceased person, the Holy Ghost, the Holy Spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "英明",
      "answer": "えいめい",
      "meaning": "intelligent, wise, bright, brilliant, clear-sighted"
    },
    {
      "question": "大乱",
      "answer": "たいらん",
      "meaning": "rebellion, great uprising"
    },
    {
      "question": "駅伝",
      "answer": "えきでん",
      "meaning": "long-distance relay race, stagecoach, post horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "白血球",
      "answer": "はっけっきゅう",
      "meaning": "leukocyte, leucocyte, white blood cell"
    },
    {
      "question": "御神体",
      "answer": "ごしんたい",
      "meaning": "shintai, object of worship believed to contain the spirit of a deity, typically housed in a shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "八卦",
      "answer": "はっけ,はっか",
      "meaning": "eight trigrams, divination signs, divination, fortune-telling"
    },
    {
      "question": "真赤",
      "answer": "まっか,まあか",
      "meaning": "bright red, deep red, flushed (of face), downright (e.g. lie), complete, utter"
    },
    {
      "question": "伊達男",
      "answer": "だておとこ",
      "meaning": "dandy, handsome and fashionable man, fop, chivalrous man"
    },
    {
      "question": "県立",
      "answer": "けんりつ",
      "meaning": "prefectural, managed by a prefectural government"
    },
    {
      "question": "一難",
      "answer": "いちなん",
      "meaning": "one difficulty, one danger"
    },
    {
      "question": "統計的",
      "answer": "とうけいてき",
      "meaning": "statistical"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂遊び",
      "answer": "すなあそび",
      "meaning": "playing in the sand"
    },
    {
      "question": "漢方",
      "answer": "かんぽう",
      "meaning": "traditional Chinese medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち食い",
      "answer": "たちぐい",
      "meaning": "eating while standing, eating at a (street) stall"
    },
    {
      "question": "知恵者",
      "answer": "ちえしゃ",
      "meaning": "wise man"
    },
    {
      "question": "右回り",
      "answer": "みぎまわり",
      "meaning": "clockwise rotation, CW, right-handed rotation"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯並び",
      "answer": "はならび",
      "meaning": "row of teeth, set of teeth, dentition"
    },
    {
      "question": "番狂わせ",
      "answer": "ばんくるわせ",
      "meaning": "unexpected result, upset, surprise"
    },
    {
      "question": "堪え性",
      "answer": "こらえしょう",
      "meaning": "endurance, perseverance, patience"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶食",
      "answer": "ぜっしょく",
      "meaning": "fasting"
    },
    {
      "question": "有給休暇",
      "answer": "ゆうきゅうきゅうか",
      "meaning": "paid vacation, leave"
    },
    {
      "question": "匙加減",
      "answer": "さじかげん",
      "meaning": "measured amount (esp. of medicine), dosing, quantity, prescription, manner of seasoning, making adju"
    },
    {
      "question": "破れ",
      "answer": "やぶれ,やれ",
      "meaning": "tear, rip, breach, break, hole, crack, breakdown, collapse, spoilage, waste, wastepaper"
    },
    {
      "question": "坂東",
      "answer": "ばんどう",
      "meaning": "Bandō, former name of the Kantō region"
    },
    {
      "question": "反物質",
      "answer": "はんぶっしつ",
      "meaning": "antimatter"
    },
    {
      "question": "月輪",
      "answer": "げつりん,がつりん,がちりん",
      "meaning": "(full) moon, moon when it's round"
    },
    {
      "question": "隊士",
      "answer": "たいし",
      "meaning": "regimental soldier"
    },
    {
      "question": "腐蝕",
      "answer": "ふしょく",
      "meaning": "corrosion, etching, action of acid, rot, rust, erosion"
    },
    {
      "question": "内務省",
      "answer": "ないむしょう",
      "meaning": "Home Ministry, Department of the Interior (US, etc.), Home Office (UK), Ministry of Home Affairs (Ja"
    },
    {
      "question": "絡繰り",
      "answer": "からくり",
      "meaning": "mechanism, machinery, contrivance, device, trick, dodge, mechanical doll, string puppet"
    },
    {
      "question": "顔料",
      "answer": "がんりょう",
      "meaning": "pigment, paint, colour, color"
    },
    {
      "question": "陥穽",
      "answer": "かんせい",
      "meaning": "trap, pitfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉱夫",
      "answer": "こうふ",
      "meaning": "miner"
    },
    {
      "question": "転任",
      "answer": "てんにん",
      "meaning": "change of post"
    },
    {
      "question": "生長",
      "answer": "せいちょう",
      "meaning": "growth (of a plant)"
    },
    {
      "question": "換気口",
      "answer": "かんきこう",
      "meaning": "vent, ventilation opening"
    },
    {
      "question": "器材",
      "answer": "きざい",
      "meaning": "tools and materials, equipment and materials"
    },
    {
      "question": "政情",
      "answer": "せいじょう",
      "meaning": "political situation, political affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "防刃",
      "answer": "ぼうじん",
      "meaning": "stab-proof, knife-proof"
    },
    {
      "question": "厭わしい",
      "answer": "いとわしい",
      "meaning": "detestable, disagreeable"
    },
    {
      "question": "痴呆",
      "answer": "ちほう",
      "meaning": "dementia"
    },
    {
      "question": "捺印",
      "answer": "なついん",
      "meaning": "affixing a seal"
    },
    {
      "question": "玉の汗",
      "answer": "たまのあせ",
      "meaning": "beads of sweat"
    },
    {
      "question": "揚げ足",
      "answer": "あげあし",
      "meaning": "raised leg, lifting a leg, sitting cross-legged"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝因",
      "answer": "しょういん",
      "meaning": "cause of victory"
    },
    {
      "question": "低周波",
      "answer": "ていしゅうは",
      "meaning": "low frequency"
    },
    {
      "question": "擽ったい",
      "answer": "くすぐったい",
      "meaning": "ticklish, embarrassing"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒白",
      "answer": "くろしろ,こくはく,こくびゃく",
      "meaning": "black and white, right and wrong"
    },
    {
      "question": "民俗学",
      "answer": "みんぞくがく",
      "meaning": "folklore studies, folkloristics"
    },
    {
      "question": "忠節",
      "answer": "ちゅうせつ",
      "meaning": "loyalty, allegiance, fidelity"
    },
    {
      "question": "側転",
      "answer": "そくてん",
      "meaning": "cartwheel"
    },
    {
      "question": "罪科",
      "answer": "ざいか",
      "meaning": "offense, offence, crime, guilt, punishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎮痛",
      "answer": "ちんつう",
      "meaning": "pain relief, killing pain"
    },
    {
      "question": "前頭葉",
      "answer": "ぜんとうよう",
      "meaning": "frontal lobe"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋空",
      "answer": "あきぞら",
      "meaning": "autumn sky, clear blue autumnal sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "稼働率",
      "answer": "かどうりつ",
      "meaning": "operating ratio, rate of operation, availability factor"
    },
    {
      "question": "臥す",
      "answer": "ふす,がす,こやす",
      "meaning": "to lie down (in bed), to take to one's bed, to lie down"
    },
    {
      "question": "息詰まる",
      "answer": "いきづまる",
      "meaning": "to be breathtaking, to be stifling"
    },
    {
      "question": "舵を取る",
      "answer": "かじをとる",
      "meaning": "to steer a ship, to manage, to take command, to take the helm"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り放題",
      "answer": "とりほうだい",
      "meaning": "as much as one can take or carry away"
    },
    {
      "question": "公害",
      "answer": "こうがい",
      "meaning": "pollution, public nuisance, contamination"
    },
    {
      "question": "品評",
      "answer": "ひんぴょう",
      "meaning": "estimation, criticism, comment"
    },
    {
      "question": "間口",
      "answer": "まぐち",
      "meaning": "frontage, width (of a building, plot of land, etc.), breadth (e.g. of one's knowledge), scope (e.g."
    },
    {
      "question": "使い回し",
      "answer": "つかいまわし",
      "meaning": "reuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "神化",
      "answer": "しんか",
      "meaning": "deification, apotheosis, wondrous change, great moral influence"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀翼",
      "answer": "ぎんよく",
      "meaning": "silvery wings"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊園",
      "answer": "れいえん",
      "meaning": "cemetery"
    },
    {
      "question": "過去問",
      "answer": "かこもん",
      "meaning": "past (exam) question collection"
    },
    {
      "question": "準々決勝",
      "answer": "じゅんじゅんけっしょう",
      "meaning": "quarterfinal"
    },
    {
      "question": "摂氏",
      "answer": "せっし",
      "meaning": "Celsius, centigrade"
    },
    {
      "question": "感覚器",
      "answer": "かんかくき",
      "meaning": "sense organ"
    },
    {
      "question": "海綿体",
      "answer": "かいめんたい",
      "meaning": "body of (genital) erectile tissue (incl. corpus cavernosum and corpus spongiosum)"
    },
    {
      "question": "胡坐",
      "answer": "あぐら,こざ",
      "meaning": "sitting cross-legged (i.e. Indian style)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鞭打ち",
      "answer": "むちうち",
      "meaning": "whipping, beating with a whip, whiplash"
    },
    {
      "question": "月間",
      "answer": "げっかん",
      "meaning": "month-long period, (during) month"
    },
    {
      "question": "搾り",
      "answer": "しぼり",
      "meaning": "tie-dye, tie-dyeing, aperture (e.g. camera, iris of the eye), aperture stop, stop, contraction, sque"
    },
    {
      "question": "地酒",
      "answer": "じざけ",
      "meaning": "local sake"
    },
    {
      "question": "届出",
      "answer": "とどけで",
      "meaning": "report, notification"
    },
    {
      "question": "婚前",
      "answer": "こんぜん",
      "meaning": "premarital, prenuptial"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚情",
      "answer": "こうじょう",
      "meaning": "kindness, favour, favor, hospitality"
    },
    {
      "question": "立て付け",
      "answer": "たてつけ",
      "meaning": "fitting (e.g. door, window), fit, succession, continuation, series, sequence"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘導弾",
      "answer": "ゆうどうだん",
      "meaning": "guided missile"
    },
    {
      "question": "県道",
      "answer": "けんどう",
      "meaning": "prefectural road"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本料理",
      "answer": "にほんりょうり",
      "meaning": "Japanese cooking"
    },
    {
      "question": "白布",
      "answer": "はくふ,しろぬの",
      "meaning": "white cloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "変転",
      "answer": "へんてん",
      "meaning": "mutation, change, transition"
    },
    {
      "question": "透徹",
      "answer": "とうてつ",
      "meaning": "penetration, absolutely clear, not dirty, clearness"
    },
    {
      "question": "上場",
      "answer": "じょうじょう",
      "meaning": "listing (on the stock exchange, etc.), taking a company public, presentation (e.g. of a play, opera)"
    },
    {
      "question": "君子",
      "answer": "くんし",
      "meaning": "man of virtue, wise man, (true) gentleman, person of high rank, the four gentlemen (plum, chrysanthe"
    },
    {
      "question": "正答",
      "answer": "せいとう",
      "meaning": "correct answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "常夜灯",
      "answer": "じょうやとう",
      "meaning": "light that stays on all night, lamp that is kept burning all night, nightlight"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮出す",
      "answer": "にだす",
      "meaning": "to extract essence by boiling, to extract flavor, to decoct"
    },
    {
      "question": "論ずる",
      "answer": "ろんずる",
      "meaning": "to discuss, to talk about, to deal with (a topic), to argue, to dispute, to take into consideration,"
    },
    {
      "question": "二乗",
      "answer": "にじょう,じじょう",
      "meaning": "squaring, multiplying (a number) by itself, second power"
    },
    {
      "question": "登校拒否",
      "answer": "とうこうきょひ",
      "meaning": "truancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "虚栄",
      "answer": "きょえい",
      "meaning": "vanity, vainglory"
    },
    {
      "question": "同量",
      "answer": "どうりょう",
      "meaning": "same amount"
    },
    {
      "question": "重め",
      "answer": "おもめ",
      "meaning": "slightly heavy, a little heavy"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘密警察",
      "answer": "ひみつけいさつ",
      "meaning": "secret police"
    },
    {
      "question": "基金",
      "answer": "ききん",
      "meaning": "fund, foundation"
    },
    {
      "question": "超合金",
      "answer": "ちょうごうきん",
      "meaning": "superalloy, Chogokin, line of die-cast metal robot and character toys sold by Popy"
    },
    {
      "question": "伸長",
      "answer": "しんちょう",
      "meaning": "expansion, extension, elongation, stretching, uncompression"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼き餅",
      "answer": "やきもち",
      "meaning": "jealousy, roasted rice cake"
    },
    {
      "question": "塗",
      "answer": "ぬり,みどろ",
      "meaning": "coating (esp. lacquering), covered with, stained, smeared"
    },
    {
      "question": "発奮",
      "answer": "はっぷん",
      "meaning": "being roused, being stimulated, being inspired, being spurred on"
    },
    {
      "question": "引導",
      "answer": "いんどう",
      "meaning": "last words recited to the newly departed, requiem, converting people to Buddhism"
    },
    {
      "question": "熟す",
      "answer": "じゅくす,こなす",
      "meaning": "to ripen, to mature, to be ready for action, to be the right time (to act), to be in common use, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "利かす",
      "answer": "きかす",
      "meaning": "to season, to enliven"
    },
    {
      "question": "形代",
      "answer": "かたしろ",
      "meaning": "paper, cloth, wood, etc. representation of a sacred object, paper doll used in purification rites"
    },
    {
      "question": "特賞",
      "answer": "とくしょう",
      "meaning": "special prize"
    },
    {
      "question": "自治領",
      "answer": "じちりょう",
      "meaning": "self-governing dominion"
    },
    {
      "question": "交合",
      "answer": "こうごう",
      "meaning": "sexual union, congress"
    },
    {
      "question": "翠色",
      "answer": "みどりいろ,すいしょく",
      "meaning": "green, emerald green, green color of new foliage, verdure"
    },
    {
      "question": "角煮",
      "answer": "かくに",
      "meaning": "stew of cubed meat or fish (esp. pork belly or tuna)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄柱",
      "answer": "てっちゅう",
      "meaning": "iron pole"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶店",
      "answer": "さてん,ちゃみせ",
      "meaning": "tea house"
    },
    {
      "question": "入選",
      "answer": "にゅうせん",
      "meaning": "being selected (for a prize, exhibition, etc.), being accepted, winning"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋭角的",
      "answer": "えいかくてき",
      "meaning": "angular, angular-shaped, sharp-pointed"
    },
    {
      "question": "拵え",
      "answer": "こしらえ",
      "meaning": "make, workmanship, preparation"
    },
    {
      "question": "危難",
      "answer": "きなん",
      "meaning": "peril, danger, hazard, distress"
    },
    {
      "question": "じり貧",
      "answer": "じりひん",
      "meaning": "gradually becoming poor, situation getting gradually worse and worse"
    },
    {
      "question": "潤滑剤",
      "answer": "じゅんかつざい",
      "meaning": "lubricant"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾力性",
      "answer": "だんりょくせい",
      "meaning": "elasticity, resilience, flexibility, adaptability"
    },
    {
      "question": "借用",
      "answer": "しゃくよう",
      "meaning": "borrowing, loan"
    },
    {
      "question": "伸び縮み",
      "answer": "のびちぢみ",
      "meaning": "expansion and contraction, elasticity, flexibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "見頃",
      "answer": "みごろ",
      "meaning": "best time to see"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛ぶ鳥",
      "answer": "とぶとり",
      "meaning": "flying bird, soaring bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "遜色",
      "answer": "そんしょく",
      "meaning": "inferiority"
    },
    {
      "question": "純一",
      "answer": "じゅんいつ",
      "meaning": "purity, homogeneity, unadorned"
    },
    {
      "question": "壜",
      "answer": "びん",
      "meaning": "bottle, jar, decanter, flagon, phial, vial"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧世界",
      "answer": "きゅうせかい",
      "meaning": "Old World (i.e., Asia, Africa, Europe)"
    },
    {
      "question": "流星雨",
      "answer": "りゅうせいう",
      "meaning": "meteor shower"
    },
    {
      "question": "三家",
      "answer": "さんけ",
      "meaning": "three noble families (Kan'in, Kazan'in, and Nakanoin or Koga), three branch Tokugawa families (Owari"
    },
    {
      "question": "牧羊犬",
      "answer": "ぼくようけん",
      "meaning": "sheepdog"
    },
    {
      "question": "渉外",
      "answer": "しょうがい",
      "meaning": "public relations, client liaison, client relations"
    },
    {
      "question": "螺子",
      "answer": "ねじ,らし",
      "meaning": "screw, key (of a clock, watch, etc.), spring (of a clock, watch, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小陰唇",
      "answer": "しょういんしん",
      "meaning": "labia minora"
    },
    {
      "question": "国元",
      "answer": "くにもと",
      "meaning": "one's home, hometown, native place, birthplace"
    },
    {
      "question": "御伽話",
      "answer": "おとぎばなし",
      "meaning": "fairy-tale, nursery-tale"
    },
    {
      "question": "市営",
      "answer": "しえい",
      "meaning": "(under) municipal management (transport, housing, etc.), city facility management"
    },
    {
      "question": "魚影",
      "answer": "ぎょえい",
      "meaning": "outline of a solitary fish (as seen through the water when fishing, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "追想",
      "answer": "ついそう",
      "meaning": "recollection, reminiscence"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯沸かし",
      "answer": "ゆわかし",
      "meaning": "teakettle, kettle"
    },
    {
      "question": "大写し",
      "answer": "おおうつし",
      "meaning": "close-up"
    },
    {
      "question": "犬種",
      "answer": "けんしゅ",
      "meaning": "breed of dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "思う様",
      "answer": "おもうさま",
      "meaning": "to one's heart's content"
    },
    {
      "question": "号砲",
      "answer": "ごうほう",
      "meaning": "signal gun, starting gun"
    },
    {
      "question": "教唆",
      "answer": "きょうさ",
      "meaning": "instigation, incitement"
    },
    {
      "question": "含有",
      "answer": "がんゆう",
      "meaning": "containing (an ingredient, mineral, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大卒",
      "answer": "だいそつ",
      "meaning": "university graduate, having graduated from university"
    },
    {
      "question": "福音書",
      "answer": "ふくいんしょ",
      "meaning": "the Gospels"
    },
    {
      "question": "居留地",
      "answer": "きょりゅうち",
      "meaning": "foreign settlement, concession, reservation (e.g. American Indian)"
    },
    {
      "question": "子狐",
      "answer": "こぎつね",
      "meaning": "fox cub, little fox, small fox, juvenile fox"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼印",
      "answer": "やきいん",
      "meaning": "brand (burnt-in mark of identification), branding iron"
    },
    {
      "question": "読モ",
      "answer": "どくモ",
      "meaning": "reader model, amateur model who appears in fashion magazines"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅客",
      "answer": "りょかく,りょきゃく",
      "meaning": "passenger, traveller, traveler, tourist"
    },
    {
      "question": "分銅",
      "answer": "ふんどう,ぶんどう,ふんどん",
      "meaning": "weight (for scales), counterweight"
    },
    {
      "question": "白球",
      "answer": "はっきゅう,はくきゅう",
      "meaning": "white ball (baseball, golf ball, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "殊の外",
      "answer": "ことのほか",
      "meaning": "exceedingly, extremely, exceptionally, unusually, unexpectedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷厳",
      "answer": "れいげん",
      "meaning": "grim, stern, stark, heartless"
    },
    {
      "question": "県境",
      "answer": "けんざかい,けんきょう",
      "meaning": "prefectural border, prefectural boundary"
    },
    {
      "question": "川遊び",
      "answer": "かわあそび",
      "meaning": "enjoying oneself on a river (e.g. boating, swimming, fishing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "加筆",
      "answer": "かひつ",
      "meaning": "correction, improvement, revision"
    },
    {
      "question": "繁茂",
      "answer": "はんも",
      "meaning": "luxuriant growth, rankness (of weeds)"
    },
    {
      "question": "喚き声",
      "answer": "わめきごえ",
      "meaning": "yell, shout, outcry"
    },
    {
      "question": "一山",
      "answer": "ひとやま,いっさん",
      "meaning": "one mountain, pile (of something), heap, lot (in sale), hump, worst part, large profit, killing, who"
    },
    {
      "question": "室外",
      "answer": "しつがい",
      "meaning": "outside (the room, building), outdoors"
    },
    {
      "question": "過剰防衛",
      "answer": "かじょうぼうえい",
      "meaning": "excessive or unjustifiable self-defense (defence)"
    },
    {
      "question": "前屈",
      "answer": "ぜんくつ",
      "meaning": "bend forward"
    },
    {
      "question": "度胸試し",
      "answer": "どきょうだめし",
      "meaning": "putting one's courage to the test"
    },
    {
      "question": "連日連夜",
      "answer": "れんじつれんや",
      "meaning": "every day and every night"
    },
    {
      "question": "死魔",
      "answer": "しま",
      "meaning": "demon of death"
    },
    {
      "question": "大系",
      "answer": "たいけい",
      "meaning": "outline, survey, compendium"
    },
    {
      "question": "壬",
      "answer": "じん,みずのえ",
      "meaning": "9th in rank, ninth sign of the Chinese calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "満州",
      "answer": "まんしゅう",
      "meaning": "Manchuria"
    },
    {
      "question": "水薬",
      "answer": "すいやく,みずぐすり",
      "meaning": "potion, liquid medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸し器",
      "answer": "むしき",
      "meaning": "steamer, steam cooker"
    },
    {
      "question": "喇叭",
      "answer": "らっぱ",
      "meaning": "trumpet, horn, bugle"
    },
    {
      "question": "餡子",
      "answer": "あんこ",
      "meaning": "red bean paste, red bean jam, anko, filling (e.g. of a manjū), stuffing, padding"
    },
    {
      "question": "都市計画",
      "answer": "としけいかく",
      "meaning": "city planning, urban planning, town planning"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄力粉",
      "answer": "はくりきこ",
      "meaning": "cake flour, pastry flour"
    },
    {
      "question": "討議",
      "answer": "とうぎ",
      "meaning": "debate, discussion"
    },
    {
      "question": "屠殺",
      "answer": "とさつ",
      "meaning": "slaughter (of animals for meat), butchery"
    },
    {
      "question": "専門医",
      "answer": "せんもんい",
      "meaning": "medical specialist"
    },
    {
      "question": "山麓",
      "answer": "さんろく",
      "meaning": "foot of a mountain, base of a mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "拝領",
      "answer": "はいりょう",
      "meaning": "receiving (from a superior), bestowed"
    },
    {
      "question": "下限",
      "answer": "かげん",
      "meaning": "lower limit, infimum"
    },
    {
      "question": "老年",
      "answer": "ろうねん",
      "meaning": "old age"
    },
    {
      "question": "離別",
      "answer": "りべつ",
      "meaning": "separation, divorce"
    },
    {
      "question": "悲報",
      "answer": "ひほう",
      "meaning": "sad news, news of a death, death notice"
    },
    {
      "question": "菊座",
      "answer": "きくざ",
      "meaning": "chrysanthemum-shaped metal fixture, chrysanthemum-shaped hemstitch, anus, anal intercourse"
    },
    {
      "question": "跳び退く",
      "answer": "とびのく",
      "meaning": "to jump (out of the way), to jump back, to jump aside"
    },
    {
      "question": "演台",
      "answer": "えんだい",
      "meaning": "desk for a speaker, lectern, rostrum, platform"
    },
    {
      "question": "名品",
      "answer": "めいひん",
      "meaning": "fine product, masterpiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "任地",
      "answer": "にんち",
      "meaning": "one's place of appointment, one's post"
    },
    {
      "question": "弟弟子",
      "answer": "おとうとでし",
      "meaning": "younger pupil (of the same master), younger disciple, junior member"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚顔",
      "answer": "こうがん",
      "meaning": "impudence, audacity, shamelessness, effrontery"
    },
    {
      "question": "木屑",
      "answer": "きくず,こけら",
      "meaning": "wood chips, wood offcuts, wood shavings, sawdust, chopped wood, thin shingles"
    },
    {
      "question": "局地",
      "answer": "きょくち",
      "meaning": "locality, local area, limited area"
    },
    {
      "question": "枕詞",
      "answer": "まくらことば",
      "meaning": "pillow word (decorative word used prefixally in classical Japanese literature), preface, introductio"
    },
    {
      "question": "低減",
      "answer": "ていげん",
      "meaning": "decrease, reduction, fall, depreciation, mitigation"
    },
    {
      "question": "ごった煮",
      "answer": "ごったに",
      "meaning": "various foods cooked together, hodgepodge, hotchpotch, mulligan stew"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸坊主",
      "answer": "まるぼうず",
      "meaning": "close-cropped head, bald hill"
    },
    {
      "question": "和洋折衷",
      "answer": "わようせっちゅう",
      "meaning": "blending of Japanese and Western styles"
    },
    {
      "question": "琢磨",
      "answer": "たくま",
      "meaning": "polish (jewels), cultivation"
    },
    {
      "question": "総督府",
      "answer": "そうとくふ",
      "meaning": "government-general"
    },
    {
      "question": "曽",
      "answer": "ひい,ひ,そう",
      "meaning": "great (i.e. great-grandson, great-grandmother)"
    },
    {
      "question": "棹",
      "answer": "さお",
      "meaning": "rod, pole, neck (of a shamisen, etc.), shamisen, beam (i.e. the crossbar of a balance), single line"
    },
    {
      "question": "碇",
      "answer": "いかり",
      "meaning": "anchor"
    },
    {
      "question": "自治会",
      "answer": "じちかい",
      "meaning": "neighborhood council, neighbourhood council, residents' association, student council"
    },
    {
      "question": "重奏",
      "answer": "じゅうそう",
      "meaning": "instrumental ensemble"
    },
    {
      "question": "姿態",
      "answer": "したい",
      "meaning": "figure, form, style"
    },
    {
      "question": "現人神",
      "answer": "あらひとがみ",
      "meaning": "emperor, living god, god incarnate, miracle-working god (who appears as the occasion demands)"
    },
    {
      "question": "干支",
      "answer": "えと,かんし",
      "meaning": "sexagenary cycle (60-year cycle of 12 animal zodiac and 5 elements in the traditional Chinese calend"
    },
    {
      "question": "墨色",
      "answer": "すみいろ",
      "meaning": "ink black"
    },
    {
      "question": "踏み切り",
      "answer": "ふみきり",
      "meaning": "railway crossing, railroad crossing, train crossing, level crossing, starting line, scratch, determi"
    },
    {
      "question": "卵黄",
      "answer": "らんおう",
      "meaning": "egg yolk"
    },
    {
      "question": "御機嫌",
      "answer": "ごきげん",
      "meaning": "humour, humor, temper, mood, spirits, safety, health, well-being, one's situation, in a good mood, i"
    },
    {
      "question": "手が無い",
      "answer": "てがない",
      "meaning": "not having enough workers, being understaffed, being undermanned, having nothing one can do about so"
    },
    {
      "question": "凡夫",
      "answer": "ぼんぷ,ぼんぶ",
      "meaning": "ordinary person, unenlightened person"
    },
    {
      "question": "継戦",
      "answer": "けいせん",
      "meaning": "continuation of war"
    },
    {
      "question": "後れ毛",
      "answer": "おくれげ",
      "meaning": "straggling hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "針山",
      "answer": "はりやま",
      "meaning": "pincushion"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘話",
      "answer": "ひわ",
      "meaning": "secret story, unknown episode"
    },
    {
      "question": "子宝",
      "answer": "こだから",
      "meaning": "the treasure that is children, children"
    },
    {
      "question": "年端",
      "answer": "としは",
      "meaning": "age, years (old)"
    },
    {
      "question": "叉",
      "answer": "また",
      "meaning": "crotch, crutch, groin, thigh, fork (in a tree, road, river, etc.), tines (of a fork)"
    },
    {
      "question": "竜骨",
      "answer": "りゅうこつ",
      "meaning": "keel"
    },
    {
      "question": "工作機械",
      "answer": "こうさくきかい",
      "meaning": "machine tools"
    },
    {
      "question": "朋友",
      "answer": "ほうゆう,ポンユー",
      "meaning": "friend, companion"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒船",
      "answer": "くろふね",
      "meaning": "black ships, Western ships that came to Japan between the 16th and 19th centuries, esp. those of the"
    },
    {
      "question": "寺社",
      "answer": "じしゃ",
      "meaning": "temples and shrines"
    },
    {
      "question": "二期",
      "answer": "にき",
      "meaning": "two periods, two terms"
    },
    {
      "question": "棄却",
      "answer": "ききゃく",
      "meaning": "rejection, dismissal, turning down, abandoning, renunciation"
    },
    {
      "question": "威風",
      "answer": "いふう",
      "meaning": "majesty, dignity"
    },
    {
      "question": "事典",
      "answer": "じてん,ことてん",
      "meaning": "encyclopedia, cyclopedia"
    },
    {
      "question": "伊達眼鏡",
      "answer": "だてめがね",
      "meaning": "glasses for show, fashionable eyeglasses worn for appearance's sake, glasses with no lenses or 'wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り出し",
      "answer": "きりだし",
      "meaning": "pointed knife, logging, cutting, (beef) scraps, starting to speak, extraction (of a portion of a med"
    },
    {
      "question": "掃き溜め",
      "answer": "はきだめ",
      "meaning": "rubbish heap, garbage dump"
    },
    {
      "question": "不適当",
      "answer": "ふてきとう",
      "meaning": "inadequacy, inappropriateness, unfitness, impropriety"
    },
    {
      "question": "水掛け論",
      "answer": "みずかけろん",
      "meaning": "endless argument, pointless argument, fruitless dispute, futile discussion, argument over whose fiel"
    },
    {
      "question": "脈がある",
      "answer": "みゃくがある",
      "meaning": "to have a pulse, to be alive, to have a chance, to be not altogether hopeless"
    },
    {
      "question": "紙製",
      "answer": "かみせい,しせい",
      "meaning": "made from paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "風前の灯",
      "answer": "ふうぜんのともしび",
      "meaning": "precarious situation, precarious state"
    },
    {
      "question": "食べ残す",
      "answer": "たべのこす",
      "meaning": "to leave a dish half-eaten"
    },
    {
      "question": "海道",
      "answer": "かいどう",
      "meaning": "sea route"
    },
    {
      "question": "渡辺",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "円卓会議",
      "answer": "えんたくかいぎ",
      "meaning": "round-table conference, roundtable, round-table, round-table meeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "総代",
      "answer": "そうだい",
      "meaning": "representative"
    },
    {
      "question": "門弟",
      "answer": "もんてい",
      "meaning": "disciple, pupil, follower"
    },
    {
      "question": "日食",
      "answer": "にっしょく",
      "meaning": "solar eclipse"
    },
    {
      "question": "生薬",
      "answer": "しょうやく,きぐすり,せいやく",
      "meaning": "natural drugs, natural remedy, herbal medicine, crude drugs, galenical"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨肉",
      "answer": "こつにく",
      "meaning": "one's own flesh and blood, blood relative, kinsman, flesh and bone, (one's) body"
    },
    {
      "question": "微速",
      "answer": "びそく",
      "meaning": "very slow speed"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶版",
      "answer": "ぜっぱん",
      "meaning": "out of print"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯煙",
      "answer": "ゆけむり",
      "meaning": "steam"
    },
    {
      "question": "担ぎ",
      "answer": "かつぎ",
      "meaning": "carrier"
    },
    {
      "question": "有休",
      "answer": "ゆうきゅう",
      "meaning": "paid vacation, paid holiday"
    },
    {
      "question": "靴跡",
      "answer": "くつあと",
      "meaning": "shoe mark, shoe print"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂糖水",
      "answer": "さとうみず",
      "meaning": "sugared water"
    },
    {
      "question": "課外活動",
      "answer": "かがいかつどう",
      "meaning": "extracurricular activities"
    },
    {
      "question": "半時",
      "answer": "はんとき,はんじ",
      "meaning": "little while, short time, an hour, half-hour, half an hour"
    },
    {
      "question": "特記",
      "answer": "とっき",
      "meaning": "special mention"
    },
    {
      "question": "文豪",
      "answer": "ぶんごう",
      "meaning": "literary master"
    },
    {
      "question": "日除け",
      "answer": "ひよけ",
      "meaning": "sunshade, blind"
    },
    {
      "question": "食い放題",
      "answer": "くいほうだい",
      "meaning": "all-you-can-eat"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹き出し",
      "answer": "ふきだし",
      "meaning": "speech balloon (in a comic strip), speech bubble, blowoff, effusion, blowing, venting, blowing (of a"
    },
    {
      "question": "僧正",
      "answer": "そうじょう",
      "meaning": "high Buddhist priest"
    },
    {
      "question": "灘",
      "answer": "なだ",
      "meaning": "open sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "檸檬",
      "answer": "れもん",
      "meaning": "lemon"
    },
    {
      "question": "自治区",
      "answer": "じちく",
      "meaning": "territory, autonomous region"
    },
    {
      "question": "何某",
      "answer": "なにがし,なにぼう",
      "meaning": "certain amount, some, certain person, Mr So-and-so, a certain ..., I, me"
    },
    {
      "question": "精髄",
      "answer": "せいずい",
      "meaning": "essence, kernel, spirit, pith"
    },
    {
      "question": "議事堂",
      "answer": "ぎじどう",
      "meaning": "assembly hall, parliament house, diet building, capitol, houses of parliament, congress hall"
    },
    {
      "question": "北海",
      "answer": "ほっかい",
      "meaning": "northern sea, North Sea, Hokkaido"
    },
    {
      "question": "住み処",
      "answer": "すみか",
      "meaning": "dwelling, house, residence, den, habitat"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝ち戦",
      "answer": "かちいくさ",
      "meaning": "victory"
    },
    {
      "question": "大回転",
      "answer": "だいかいてん",
      "meaning": "the giant slalom"
    },
    {
      "question": "地頭",
      "answer": "じとう,じあたま",
      "meaning": "lord of a manor, estate steward, wigless head, head of natural hair, intelligence, comprehension, sm"
    },
    {
      "question": "出世頭",
      "answer": "しゅっせがしら",
      "meaning": "most successful (of one's relatives, classmates, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏表紙",
      "answer": "うらびょうし",
      "meaning": "back cover"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮住まい",
      "answer": "かりずまい",
      "meaning": "temporary residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "儚む",
      "answer": "はかなむ",
      "meaning": "to despair of, to see the vanity of"
    },
    {
      "question": "雷竜",
      "answer": "らいりゅう",
      "meaning": "brontosaurus, apatosaurus (dinosaur)"
    },
    {
      "question": "末妹",
      "answer": "まつまい",
      "meaning": "youngest sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "有り難う",
      "answer": "ありがとう",
      "meaning": "thank you, thanks"
    },
    {
      "question": "財務省",
      "answer": "ざいむしょう",
      "meaning": "Ministry of Finance"
    },
    {
      "question": "外戚",
      "answer": "がいせき",
      "meaning": "maternal relative"
    },
    {
      "question": "偏在",
      "answer": "へんざい",
      "meaning": "uneven distribution, unfair distribution, maldistribution"
    },
    {
      "question": "家門",
      "answer": "かもん",
      "meaning": "one's family, one's clan"
    },
    {
      "question": "下拵え",
      "answer": "したごしらえ",
      "meaning": "preliminary arrangements, preparation, spadework, pre-cooking"
    },
    {
      "question": "改定",
      "answer": "かいてい,かいじょう",
      "meaning": "revision (of a rule, price, etc.), alteration, change"
    },
    {
      "question": "同時代",
      "answer": "どうじだい",
      "meaning": "the same age, same period"
    },
    {
      "question": "突き殺す",
      "answer": "つきころす",
      "meaning": "to stab to death"
    },
    {
      "question": "地獄の釜",
      "answer": "じごくのかま",
      "meaning": "the cauldron of Hell (in which sinners are boiled)"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋の病",
      "answer": "こいのやまい",
      "meaning": "lovesickness"
    },
    {
      "question": "興る",
      "answer": "おこる",
      "meaning": "to rise, to flourish"
    },
    {
      "question": "偏愛",
      "answer": "へんあい",
      "meaning": "favoritism, favouritism, partiality"
    },
    {
      "question": "無免許",
      "answer": "むめんきょ",
      "meaning": "unlicensed, without a license (licence)"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋口",
      "answer": "あきぐち",
      "meaning": "beginning of autumn, beginning of fall"
    },
    {
      "question": "猫の目",
      "answer": "ねこのめ",
      "meaning": "(something) fickle, (something) very changeable"
    },
    {
      "question": "防火",
      "answer": "ぼうか",
      "meaning": "fire prevention, fire fighting, fire proof"
    },
    {
      "question": "住み心地",
      "answer": "すみごこち",
      "meaning": "comfort (in living place)"
    },
    {
      "question": "叔父貴",
      "answer": "おじき",
      "meaning": "uncle (younger than one's parent)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鯛焼き",
      "answer": "たいやき",
      "meaning": "fish-shaped pancake filled with bean jam"
    },
    {
      "question": "私邸",
      "answer": "してい",
      "meaning": "private residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "近侍",
      "answer": "きんじ",
      "meaning": "attendant, attendance upon another"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪神",
      "answer": "あくじん",
      "meaning": "evil god"
    },
    {
      "question": "無尽",
      "answer": "むじん",
      "meaning": "inexhaustibility, mutual financing association"
    },
    {
      "question": "銃座",
      "answer": "じゅうざ",
      "meaning": "emplacement"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵日記",
      "answer": "えにっき",
      "meaning": "illustrated diary, picture diary"
    },
    {
      "question": "女殺し",
      "answer": "おんなごろし,おんなころし",
      "meaning": "ladykiller, ladies' man, murder of a woman, murderer of a woman, femicide"
    },
    {
      "question": "息を継ぐ",
      "answer": "いきをつぐ",
      "meaning": "to take a breath, to gather one's breath, to catch one's breath, to take a rest, to take a break"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮干し",
      "answer": "にぼし",
      "meaning": "(small crunchy) dried sardines"
    },
    {
      "question": "居住者",
      "answer": "きょじゅうしゃ",
      "meaning": "resident, inhabitant"
    },
    {
      "question": "別れ道",
      "answer": "わかれみち",
      "meaning": "branch, forked road, crossroads, branch road, parting of the ways, turning point"
    },
    {
      "question": "新素材",
      "answer": "しんそざい",
      "meaning": "advanced materials, new high-tech materials"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠し芸",
      "answer": "かくしげい",
      "meaning": "one's party piece, parlor trick, hidden talent"
    },
    {
      "question": "凍土",
      "answer": "とうど",
      "meaning": "frozen soil"
    },
    {
      "question": "漣",
      "answer": "さざなみ",
      "meaning": "ripple (on water), wavelets, ripple (e.g. of uneasiness), unrest, disturbance"
    },
    {
      "question": "残務",
      "answer": "ざんむ",
      "meaning": "remaining business"
    },
    {
      "question": "有刺鉄線",
      "answer": "ゆうしてっせん",
      "meaning": "barbed wire"
    },
    {
      "question": "無私",
      "answer": "むし",
      "meaning": "unselfish, selfless, disinterested"
    },
    {
      "question": "明か",
      "answer": "さやか",
      "meaning": "clear, fresh, bright"
    },
    {
      "question": "桟",
      "answer": "かけはし,さん,えつり",
      "meaning": "suspension bridge, viaduct, temporary bridge, mediation, go-between, frame (i.e. of a sliding door),"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵対行為",
      "answer": "てきたいこうい",
      "meaning": "hostile act"
    },
    {
      "question": "錚々",
      "answer": "そうそう",
      "meaning": "eminent, prominent, distinguished, first-rate, leading, ringing (of metal), resonant (of a musical i"
    },
    {
      "question": "一本釣り",
      "answer": "いっぽんづり,いっぽんずり",
      "meaning": "fishing with a pole"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫉み",
      "answer": "ねたみ,そねみ",
      "meaning": "jealousy, envy"
    },
    {
      "question": "終身刑",
      "answer": "しゅうしんけい",
      "meaning": "life imprisonment, life sentence"
    },
    {
      "question": "自費",
      "answer": "じひ",
      "meaning": "one's own expense, out-of-pocket expense"
    },
    {
      "question": "回転率",
      "answer": "かいてんりつ",
      "meaning": "turnover rate (merchandise, capital)"
    },
    {
      "question": "清濁",
      "answer": "せいだく",
      "meaning": "good and evil, purity and impurity, voiced and unvoiced consonants"
    },
    {
      "question": "亥",
      "answer": "い",
      "meaning": "the Boar (twelfth sign of the Chinese zodiac), the Pig, hour of the Boar (around 10pm, 9-11pm, or 10"
    },
    {
      "question": "篠原",
      "answer": "しのはら",
      "meaning": "field of bamboo grass"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜水艇",
      "answer": "せんすいてい",
      "meaning": "submarine, submersible vessel"
    },
    {
      "question": "原爆",
      "answer": "げんばく",
      "meaning": "atomic bomb, A-bomb"
    },
    {
      "question": "蝸牛",
      "answer": "かたつむり,かぎゅう,でんでんむし",
      "meaning": "snail, cochlea"
    },
    {
      "question": "豊臣秀吉",
      "answer": "とよとみひでよし",
      "meaning": "Toyotomi Hideyoshi"
    },
    {
      "question": "三千世界",
      "answer": "さんぜんせかい",
      "meaning": "the whole world, the universe"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪心",
      "answer": "あくしん,おしん",
      "meaning": "evil thought, malicious motive, nausea, urge to vomit"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬蹄",
      "answer": "ばてい",
      "meaning": "horse's hooves"
    },
    {
      "question": "皇居",
      "answer": "こうきょ,こうぎょ",
      "meaning": "Imperial Palace (of Japan), imperial residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "国際法",
      "answer": "こくさいほう",
      "meaning": "international law, law of nations"
    },
    {
      "question": "安楽椅子",
      "answer": "あんらくいす",
      "meaning": "easy chair, armchair"
    },
    {
      "question": "私人",
      "answer": "しじん,しにん",
      "meaning": "private individual"
    },
    {
      "question": "窒素",
      "answer": "ちっそ",
      "meaning": "nitrogen (N)"
    },
    {
      "question": "試し斬り",
      "answer": "ためしぎり",
      "meaning": "trying out a new sword or blade (originally on someone, but now on soaked straw targets)"
    },
    {
      "question": "亭主関白",
      "answer": "ていしゅかんぱく",
      "meaning": "domineering husband, hectoring husband, husband who rules the roost"
    },
    {
      "question": "空室",
      "answer": "あきしつ,くうしつ",
      "meaning": "vacant or unoccupied room"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱兎",
      "answer": "だっと",
      "meaning": "dashing away, bounding away, (with) lightning speed, startled hare"
    },
    {
      "question": "欲目",
      "answer": "よくめ",
      "meaning": "partiality, bias"
    },
    {
      "question": "閥",
      "answer": "ばつ",
      "meaning": "clique, clan, faction"
    },
    {
      "question": "小母さん",
      "answer": "おばさん",
      "meaning": "old lady, ma'am"
    },
    {
      "question": "特派員",
      "answer": "とくはいん",
      "meaning": "(special) correspondent (e.g. for a newspaper), representative, delegate"
    },
    {
      "question": "奉公人",
      "answer": "ほうこうにん",
      "meaning": "servant, employee"
    },
    {
      "question": "自由席",
      "answer": "じゆうせき",
      "meaning": "unreserved seat, non-reserved seat"
    },
    {
      "question": "内燃機関",
      "answer": "ないねんきかん",
      "meaning": "internal-combustion engine"
    },
    {
      "question": "送電",
      "answer": "そうでん",
      "meaning": "transmission of electricity, electricity supply, power supply"
    },
    {
      "question": "無所属",
      "answer": "むしょぞく",
      "meaning": "independent (esp. in politics), non-partisan"
    },
    {
      "question": "吸殻",
      "answer": "すいがら",
      "meaning": "cigarette end, cigarette butt, tobacco ashes"
    },
    {
      "question": "弛める",
      "answer": "ゆるめる,たるめる",
      "meaning": "to loosen, to slacken, to relax (attention, efforts, etc.), to let down (one's guard), to relieve (t"
    },
    {
      "question": "跳び箱",
      "answer": "とびばこ",
      "meaning": "vaulting horse, vaulting box, box horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "窶れる",
      "answer": "やつれる",
      "meaning": "to be haggard, to be gaunt, to be emaciated, to be worn out (e.g. illness, worry)"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲み薬",
      "answer": "のみぐすり",
      "meaning": "oral medicine, internal medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "寂寞",
      "answer": "せきばく,じゃくまく",
      "meaning": "lonely, lonesome, dreary, desolate, deserted, forlorn, loneliness, desolation"
    },
    {
      "question": "初秋",
      "answer": "しょしゅう,はつあき",
      "meaning": "early autumn (fall), seventh month of the lunar calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱演",
      "answer": "ねつえん",
      "meaning": "enthusiastic performance"
    },
    {
      "question": "実状",
      "answer": "じつじょう",
      "meaning": "real condition, actual circumstances, actual state of affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "量的",
      "answer": "りょうてき",
      "meaning": "quantitative, concerning the quantity"
    },
    {
      "question": "含蓄",
      "answer": "がんちく",
      "meaning": "implication, significance, connotation, depth of meaning, complications of a problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "性差",
      "answer": "せいさ",
      "meaning": "difference between the sexes, sexual difference"
    },
    {
      "question": "分刻み",
      "answer": "ふんきざみ",
      "meaning": "counting by the minute (of a schedule, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋の空",
      "answer": "あきのそら",
      "meaning": "clear autumn sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "時の運",
      "answer": "ときのうん",
      "meaning": "(a matter of) chance, fortune (of a given time), force of the times"
    },
    {
      "question": "手始め",
      "answer": "てはじめ",
      "meaning": "outset, start, beginning"
    },
    {
      "question": "真平",
      "answer": "まっぴら",
      "meaning": "(not) by any means, (not) for anything, wouldn't do for anything, had enough, flatly refusing"
    },
    {
      "question": "桑原",
      "answer": "くわばら",
      "meaning": "mulberry field"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍学",
      "answer": "ぐんがく",
      "meaning": "military science, strategy, tactics"
    },
    {
      "question": "官舎",
      "answer": "かんしゃ",
      "meaning": "official residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒造り",
      "answer": "さけづくり",
      "meaning": "sake brewing"
    },
    {
      "question": "平淡",
      "answer": "へいたん",
      "meaning": "simple, quiet"
    },
    {
      "question": "手番",
      "answer": "てつがい,てばん",
      "meaning": "plan, arrangements, one's turn (esp. in go, shogi, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "請願",
      "answer": "せいがん",
      "meaning": "petition"
    },
    {
      "question": "文字化け",
      "answer": "もじばけ",
      "meaning": "corruption (of text, e.g. in email, due to improper encoding), garbling, illegal character, corrupte"
    },
    {
      "question": "彼の人",
      "answer": "あのひと",
      "meaning": "he, she, that person, you"
    },
    {
      "question": "停船",
      "answer": "ていせん",
      "meaning": "stopping a ship, detention, quarantine"
    },
    {
      "question": "後攻",
      "answer": "こうこう",
      "meaning": "taking the field first, thus batting second"
    },
    {
      "question": "投げ槍",
      "answer": "なげやり",
      "meaning": "negligent, careless, slipshod, slovenly, reckless, irresponsible, offhand, javelin, lance"
    },
    {
      "question": "泊り込む",
      "answer": "とまりこむ",
      "meaning": "to stay overnight, to stop (e.g. at a hotel)"
    },
    {
      "question": "偉",
      "answer": "い,えら",
      "meaning": "greatness, tremendous, huge"
    },
    {
      "question": "素焼き",
      "answer": "すやき",
      "meaning": "unglazed pottery, bisque, bisque firing, biscuit ware, seafood grilled without seasoning"
    },
    {
      "question": "斉唱",
      "answer": "せいしょう",
      "meaning": "singing or chanting in unison"
    },
    {
      "question": "接見",
      "answer": "せっけん",
      "meaning": "interview"
    },
    {
      "question": "慕情",
      "answer": "ぼじょう",
      "meaning": "longing, yearning"
    },
    {
      "question": "試金石",
      "answer": "しきんせき",
      "meaning": "touchstone, Lydian stone, touchstone (e.g. of success), test, litmus test"
    },
    {
      "question": "緯度",
      "answer": "いど",
      "meaning": "latitude (nav.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "独創性",
      "answer": "どくそうせい",
      "meaning": "creativity, ingenuity"
    },
    {
      "question": "題目",
      "answer": "だいもく",
      "meaning": "book title, heading, topic, subject, theme, Nichiren Buddhist chant"
    },
    {
      "question": "考え違い",
      "answer": "かんがえちがい",
      "meaning": "mistaken idea, misunderstanding, wrong impression"
    },
    {
      "question": "僻む",
      "answer": "ひがむ",
      "meaning": "to have a warped view, to be jaundiced, to be prejudiced, to feel that one has been unfairly treated"
    },
    {
      "question": "茉莉",
      "answer": "まつり",
      "meaning": "Arabian jasmine (Jasminum sambac)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼬",
      "answer": "いたち",
      "meaning": "weasel (esp. the Japanese weasel, Mustela itatsi), mustelid (any other member of the weasel family,"
    },
    {
      "question": "年鑑",
      "answer": "ねんかん",
      "meaning": "yearbook, almanac, annual"
    },
    {
      "question": "親善",
      "answer": "しんぜん",
      "meaning": "friendship, goodwill, friendly relations, amity"
    },
    {
      "question": "皇位継承",
      "answer": "こういけいしょう",
      "meaning": "(Japanese) imperial succession"
    },
    {
      "question": "貪",
      "answer": "たん,とん,どん",
      "meaning": "coveting, raga (desire)"
    },
    {
      "question": "准教授",
      "answer": "じゅんきょうじゅ",
      "meaning": "associate professor"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊能者",
      "answer": "れいのうしゃ",
      "meaning": "medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "ビート板",
      "answer": "ビートばん",
      "meaning": "kickboard, flutterboard, float"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸刈り",
      "answer": "まるがり",
      "meaning": "buzz cut, close crop"
    },
    {
      "question": "疑義",
      "answer": "ぎぎ",
      "meaning": "doubt"
    },
    {
      "question": "前編",
      "answer": "ぜんぺん",
      "meaning": "first part, first volume, prequel"
    },
    {
      "question": "下り立つ",
      "answer": "おりたつ",
      "meaning": "to go down and stand, to alight, to get down"
    },
    {
      "question": "村八分",
      "answer": "むらはちぶ",
      "meaning": "ostracism"
    },
    {
      "question": "消防署",
      "answer": "しょうぼうしょ",
      "meaning": "fire station"
    },
    {
      "question": "自ずから",
      "answer": "おのずから",
      "meaning": "naturally, as a matter of course"
    },
    {
      "question": "漢方薬",
      "answer": "かんぽうやく",
      "meaning": "Chinese herbal medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "繁忙期",
      "answer": "はんぼうき",
      "meaning": "busy period, busy season"
    },
    {
      "question": "諳んじる",
      "answer": "そらんじる",
      "meaning": "to memorize, to memorise, to recite from memory"
    },
    {
      "question": "総重量",
      "answer": "そうじゅうりょう",
      "meaning": "gross weight"
    },
    {
      "question": "血税",
      "answer": "けつぜい",
      "meaning": "tax payers' money, hard-earned tax money, heavy taxation, conscription"
    },
    {
      "question": "後門",
      "answer": "こうもん",
      "meaning": "back gate"
    },
    {
      "question": "見始め",
      "answer": "みはじめ",
      "meaning": "seeing for the first time, first sight"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊亀",
      "answer": "れいき",
      "meaning": "mysterious turtle (an omen of good luck), Reiki era (715.9.2-717.11.17)"
    },
    {
      "question": "村雨",
      "answer": "むらさめ",
      "meaning": "passing shower"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤玉",
      "answer": "あかだま",
      "meaning": "red ball, amber, jasper, patent medicine, brand of sweet wine"
    },
    {
      "question": "支局",
      "answer": "しきょく",
      "meaning": "branch office"
    },
    {
      "question": "天守",
      "answer": "てんしゅ",
      "meaning": "castle tower"
    },
    {
      "question": "先帝",
      "answer": "せんてい",
      "meaning": "the late emperor"
    },
    {
      "question": "大逆",
      "answer": "たいぎゃく,だいぎゃく,おおさが",
      "meaning": "high treason, Sebastes iracundus (species of rockfish)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小口",
      "answer": "こぐち",
      "meaning": "cut end, edge (of a page, etc.), small amount, small quantity, small sum, beginning, clue, tiger's d"
    },
    {
      "question": "謂わば",
      "answer": "いわば",
      "meaning": "so to speak, so to call it, as it were"
    },
    {
      "question": "外貨",
      "answer": "がいか",
      "meaning": "foreign currency, foreign money, foreign exchange, foreign goods, imported goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "施政",
      "answer": "しせい",
      "meaning": "government, administration, statesmanship"
    },
    {
      "question": "仔牛",
      "answer": "こうし,こうじ",
      "meaning": "calf, small cow"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸がすく",
      "answer": "むねがすく",
      "meaning": "to feel relieved, to feel satisfied, to feel refreshed"
    },
    {
      "question": "生計",
      "answer": "せいけい",
      "meaning": "livelihood, living"
    },
    {
      "question": "律令",
      "answer": "りつりょう,りつれい",
      "meaning": "criminal, administrative and civil codes (forming the basis of ancient East Asian law; orig. Chinese"
    },
    {
      "question": "陸奥",
      "answer": "むつ,みちのく,りくおう",
      "meaning": "Mutsu (former province located in present-day Fukushima, Miyagi, Iwate, and Aomori prefectures), Rik"
    },
    {
      "question": "山門",
      "answer": "さんもん",
      "meaning": "main temple gate, temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "吟",
      "answer": "ぎん",
      "meaning": "recitation (of a poem), chanting, singing, composition (of a poem), composed poem, classical Chinese"
    },
    {
      "question": "廟",
      "answer": "たまや,びょう",
      "meaning": "mausoleum, (temporary) resting place of a corpse, shrine, the (imperial) court"
    },
    {
      "question": "南天",
      "answer": "なんてん",
      "meaning": "southern sky, heavenly bamboo (Nandina domestica), nandina"
    },
    {
      "question": "只管",
      "answer": "ひたすら",
      "meaning": "intently, single-mindedly, devotedly, solely, earnestly, with all one's heart"
    },
    {
      "question": "満塁",
      "answer": "まんるい",
      "meaning": "bases loaded"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰帯",
      "answer": "こしおび",
      "meaning": "waist band, girdle, sash"
    },
    {
      "question": "碗",
      "answer": "わん",
      "meaning": "bowl (ceramic, porcelain), counter for bowls of food or drink"
    },
    {
      "question": "非常勤",
      "answer": "ひじょうきん",
      "meaning": "part-time work"
    },
    {
      "question": "蘊蓄",
      "answer": "うんちく",
      "meaning": "great erudition, extensive knowledge, vast stock of knowledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "染め抜く",
      "answer": "そめぬく",
      "meaning": "to dye fast, to leave undyed"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱字",
      "answer": "だつじ",
      "meaning": "omitted character, omitted letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "啄",
      "answer": "たく",
      "meaning": "seventh principle of the Eight Principles of Yong, stroke that falls leftwards with slight curve"
    },
    {
      "question": "春巻き",
      "answer": "はるまき",
      "meaning": "spring roll"
    },
    {
      "question": "密生",
      "answer": "みっせい",
      "meaning": "growing thickly, growing densely"
    },
    {
      "question": "職分",
      "answer": "しょくぶん",
      "meaning": "one's duty, vocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳴り渡る",
      "answer": "なりわたる",
      "meaning": "to resound (echo) far and wide"
    },
    {
      "question": "錯誤",
      "answer": "さくご",
      "meaning": "mistake, error, discrepancy, discrepancy between one's actions and intentions"
    },
    {
      "question": "啓蒙",
      "answer": "けいもう",
      "meaning": "enlightenment, instruction"
    },
    {
      "question": "見せ所",
      "answer": "みせどころ",
      "meaning": "a place or opportunity to make a display of"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪見",
      "answer": "ゆきみ",
      "meaning": "snow viewing"
    },
    {
      "question": "無線通信",
      "answer": "むせんつうしん",
      "meaning": "radio communication"
    },
    {
      "question": "真打",
      "answer": "しんうち",
      "meaning": "main performer, star performer, headliner, rakugo storyteller of the highest rank"
    },
    {
      "question": "笛吹き",
      "answer": "ふえふき",
      "meaning": "flute player, flutist, flautist, piper"
    },
    {
      "question": "瑪瑙",
      "answer": "めのう",
      "meaning": "agate"
    },
    {
      "question": "密造",
      "answer": "みつぞう",
      "meaning": "illicit manufacturing, illicit distilling, moonshining"
    },
    {
      "question": "着メロ",
      "answer": "ちゃくメロ",
      "meaning": "melodic incoming call tones (esp. mobile telephones), ringtone, ring tone"
    },
    {
      "question": "竹槍",
      "answer": "たけやり,ちくそう",
      "meaning": "bamboo spear"
    },
    {
      "question": "殉教",
      "answer": "じゅんきょう",
      "meaning": "martyrdom"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒毛",
      "answer": "くろげ",
      "meaning": "black hair, black-haired horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い付け",
      "answer": "いいつけ",
      "meaning": "order, command, directions, instructions"
    },
    {
      "question": "玲瓏",
      "answer": "れいろう",
      "meaning": "clear, translucent, brilliant, sweetly ringing (as the tinklings of jade)"
    },
    {
      "question": "懸垂",
      "answer": "けんすい",
      "meaning": "pull-up (exercise), chin-up, chinning, suspension, dangling, hanging"
    },
    {
      "question": "回顧",
      "answer": "かいこ",
      "meaning": "recollecting, reminiscing, looking back, retrospection, review"
    },
    {
      "question": "元栓",
      "answer": "もとせん",
      "meaning": "stopcock (gas, water)"
    },
    {
      "question": "口臭",
      "answer": "こうしゅう",
      "meaning": "bad breath, halitosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧態依然",
      "answer": "きゅうたいいぜん",
      "meaning": "remaining unchanged (from the old state of things), none the better for the change (if at all)"
    },
    {
      "question": "七転八倒",
      "answer": "しちてんばっとう,しってんばっとう",
      "meaning": "tossing oneself about in great pain, writhing in agony"
    },
    {
      "question": "岩屋",
      "answer": "いわや",
      "meaning": "cavern, grotto"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮免",
      "answer": "かりめん",
      "meaning": "temporary licence, temporary license, provisional licence, provisional license"
    },
    {
      "question": "脇差",
      "answer": "わきざし",
      "meaning": "wakizashi, short sword worn by samurai"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸かす",
      "answer": "ふかす",
      "meaning": "to steam (food)"
    },
    {
      "question": "先年",
      "answer": "せんねん",
      "meaning": "former years, formerly, a few years ago"
    },
    {
      "question": "割り算",
      "answer": "わりざん",
      "meaning": "division"
    },
    {
      "question": "壮行会",
      "answer": "そうこうかい",
      "meaning": "farewell party, send-off party, motivational rally"
    },
    {
      "question": "酔客",
      "answer": "すいきゃく,すいかく",
      "meaning": "drunken person"
    },
    {
      "question": "驟雨",
      "answer": "しゅうう",
      "meaning": "sudden shower, sudden downpour"
    },
    {
      "question": "跳梁",
      "answer": "ちょうりょう",
      "meaning": "jumping about, rampancy, domination"
    },
    {
      "question": "陣頭",
      "answer": "じんとう",
      "meaning": "head of an army"
    },
    {
      "question": "置き時計",
      "answer": "おきどけい",
      "meaning": "clock to be placed on tables, bookshelves, etc. (as opposed to a watch)"
    },
    {
      "question": "不可分",
      "answer": "ふかぶん",
      "meaning": "atomic, indivisibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "両岸",
      "answer": "りょうがん,りょうぎし",
      "meaning": "both banks (of a river)"
    },
    {
      "question": "体付き",
      "answer": "からだつき",
      "meaning": "body build, figure"
    },
    {
      "question": "予防接種",
      "answer": "よぼうせっしゅ",
      "meaning": "vaccination, inoculation, immunization, immunisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "量販店",
      "answer": "りょうはんてん",
      "meaning": "volume retailer, mass marketer, emporium"
    },
    {
      "question": "揃い踏み",
      "answer": "そろいぶみ",
      "meaning": "ritual stamping in the ring, lineup, appearance together"
    },
    {
      "question": "一宿一飯",
      "answer": "いっしゅくいっぱん",
      "meaning": "(being beholden to someone for a favor of) a night's lodging and a meal"
    },
    {
      "question": "的場",
      "answer": "まとば",
      "meaning": "target area (e.g. archery), range (e.g. rifle, firing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "奉行所",
      "answer": "ぶぎょうしょ",
      "meaning": "magistrate's office"
    },
    {
      "question": "織機",
      "answer": "しょっき,おりき",
      "meaning": "loom, weaving machine"
    },
    {
      "question": "主計",
      "answer": "しゅけい",
      "meaning": "paymaster, accountant"
    },
    {
      "question": "周防",
      "answer": "すおう",
      "meaning": "Suō (former province located in the southeast of present-day Yamaguchi Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "高嶺",
      "answer": "たかね,こうれい",
      "meaning": "high peak"
    },
    {
      "question": "江戸城",
      "answer": "えどじょう",
      "meaning": "Edo Castle (residence of the Shogun during the Edo period, now the site of the Tokyo Imperial Palace"
    },
    {
      "question": "新歓",
      "answer": "しんかん",
      "meaning": "new members (e.g. club), new students, freshman, event to welcome new students, club members, etc. ("
    },
    {
      "question": "雷霆",
      "answer": "らいてい",
      "meaning": "thunder"
    },
    {
      "question": "大路",
      "answer": "おおじ,たいろ",
      "meaning": "main street (esp. in a capital), main thoroughfare, most important of the three classes of highway ("
    },
    {
      "question": "寿ぐ",
      "answer": "ことほぐ",
      "meaning": "to congratulate, to wish (someone) well, to celebrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "喀血",
      "answer": "かっけつ",
      "meaning": "hemoptysis, coughing up blood, lung hemorrhage (haemorrhage)"
    },
    {
      "question": "超自然",
      "answer": "ちょうしぜん",
      "meaning": "occult, transcendental, supernaturalness, supernaturalism, supernaturality"
    },
    {
      "question": "私鉄",
      "answer": "してつ",
      "meaning": "private railway"
    },
    {
      "question": "販促",
      "answer": "はんそく",
      "meaning": "sales promotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶海",
      "answer": "ぜっかい",
      "meaning": "distant seas"
    },
    {
      "question": "永久凍土",
      "answer": "えいきゅうとうど",
      "meaning": "permafrost"
    },
    {
      "question": "十指",
      "answer": "じっし,じゅっし",
      "meaning": "the ten fingers"
    },
    {
      "question": "初物",
      "answer": "はつもの",
      "meaning": "first of the season (e.g. produce, catch), virgin"
    },
    {
      "question": "記念碑",
      "answer": "きねんひ",
      "meaning": "commemorative plaque (usu. on a stone), stone monument (bearing an inscription)"
    },
    {
      "question": "徒競走",
      "answer": "ときょうそう",
      "meaning": "foot race"
    },
    {
      "question": "貰い物",
      "answer": "もらいもの",
      "meaning": "(received) present, gift"
    },
    {
      "question": "世慣れる",
      "answer": "よなれる",
      "meaning": "to become used to the (ways of the) world, to become worldly or sophisticated"
    },
    {
      "question": "低迷",
      "answer": "ていめい",
      "meaning": "hanging low (over), hovering around (price level), low hanging (e.g. clouds), sluggish (e.g. economy"
    },
    {
      "question": "歳差",
      "answer": "さいさ",
      "meaning": "(phenomenon of) precession of the equinoxes"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒癖",
      "answer": "さけぐせ,さけくせ,しゅへき",
      "meaning": "drinking habits, drunken behavior, drunken behaviour"
    },
    {
      "question": "鞍馬",
      "answer": "あんば",
      "meaning": "pommel horse, side horse, saddled horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "湊",
      "answer": "みなと",
      "meaning": "harbour, harbor, port"
    },
    {
      "question": "鱈",
      "answer": "たら",
      "meaning": "gadid (any fish of the family Gadidae, incl. cod, haddock, whiting and pollack), Pacific cod (Gadus"
    },
    {
      "question": "老公",
      "answer": "ろうこう",
      "meaning": "elderly nobleman"
    },
    {
      "question": "馭者",
      "answer": "ぎょしゃ",
      "meaning": "coachman, driver, cabman, postilion"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦史",
      "answer": "せんし",
      "meaning": "military history, military annals"
    },
    {
      "question": "無印",
      "answer": "むじるし",
      "meaning": "unlabeled, unbranded"
    },
    {
      "question": "金玉",
      "answer": "きんたま,きんぎょく",
      "meaning": "testicles, gold and jewels, precious object"
    },
    {
      "question": "辛子",
      "answer": "からし",
      "meaning": "mustard"
    },
    {
      "question": "所員",
      "answer": "しょいん",
      "meaning": "staff member, station employee, official"
    },
    {
      "question": "如何な",
      "answer": "いかな,いっかな",
      "meaning": "what kind of, whatever sort of, no matter what, however much"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦費",
      "answer": "せんぴ",
      "meaning": "war expenditures"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄冠",
      "answer": "えいかん",
      "meaning": "laurels, garland"
    },
    {
      "question": "平積み",
      "answer": "ひらづみ",
      "meaning": "stacking flat and face up (magazines, books, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "初冬",
      "answer": "しょとう,はつふゆ",
      "meaning": "early winter, tenth month of the lunar calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "円周率",
      "answer": "えんしゅうりつ",
      "meaning": "Pi (3.1415926..)"
    },
    {
      "question": "日干し",
      "answer": "ひぼし",
      "meaning": "sun-dried"
    },
    {
      "question": "万分の一",
      "answer": "まんぶんのいち",
      "meaning": "one ten-thousandth"
    },
    {
      "question": "梳る",
      "answer": "くしけずる,けずる",
      "meaning": "to comb"
    },
    {
      "question": "殿堂",
      "answer": "でんどう",
      "meaning": "palace, hall, shrine, temple, sanctuary, hall of fame"
    },
    {
      "question": "残念賞",
      "answer": "ざんねんしょう",
      "meaning": "consolation prize"
    },
    {
      "question": "蟠り",
      "answer": "わだかまり",
      "meaning": "cares, ill feeling, reserve"
    },
    {
      "question": "音質",
      "answer": "おんしつ",
      "meaning": "tone quality, sound quality"
    },
    {
      "question": "歩数",
      "answer": "ほすう",
      "meaning": "number of steps"
    },
    {
      "question": "時流",
      "answer": "じりゅう",
      "meaning": "fashion (current) of the times, general drift of affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "水仕事",
      "answer": "みずしごと",
      "meaning": "scrubbing and washing, kitchen work"
    },
    {
      "question": "千客万来",
      "answer": "せんきゃくばんらい,せんかくばんらい",
      "meaning": "flood of customers, roaring business"
    },
    {
      "question": "美名",
      "answer": "びめい",
      "meaning": "good name, high reputation"
    },
    {
      "question": "皇城",
      "answer": "こうじょう",
      "meaning": "imperial palace"
    },
    {
      "question": "還俗",
      "answer": "げんぞく",
      "meaning": "return to secular life, secularization, secularisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "高弟",
      "answer": "こうてい",
      "meaning": "best pupil, leading disciple"
    },
    {
      "question": "練馬",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "浄水",
      "answer": "じょうすい",
      "meaning": "clean water"
    },
    {
      "question": "精油",
      "answer": "せいゆ",
      "meaning": "essential oil, volatile oil, refined oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "流氷",
      "answer": "りゅうひょう",
      "meaning": "drift ice, ice floe"
    },
    {
      "question": "再誕",
      "answer": "さいたん",
      "meaning": "resurrection (of a company or school, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "温泉卵",
      "answer": "おんせんたまご",
      "meaning": "egg slow-boiled so that the yolk is hard but the white is still soft (traditionally cooked in a hot"
    },
    {
      "question": "王制",
      "answer": "おうせい",
      "meaning": "monarchical system"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼き印",
      "answer": "やきいん",
      "meaning": "brand (burnt-in mark of identification), branding iron"
    },
    {
      "question": "火炙り",
      "answer": "ひあぶり",
      "meaning": "burning at the stake, burning to death"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶する",
      "answer": "ぜっする",
      "meaning": "to be unspeakable, to be unimaginable"
    },
    {
      "question": "人的資源",
      "answer": "じんてきしげん",
      "meaning": "human resources, man-power resources"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄片",
      "answer": "てっぺん",
      "meaning": "iron scraps"
    },
    {
      "question": "精巣",
      "answer": "せいそう",
      "meaning": "testicle"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒豆",
      "answer": "くろまめ",
      "meaning": "black soybean"
    },
    {
      "question": "死生観",
      "answer": "しせいかん",
      "meaning": "one's opinion on (life and) death"
    },
    {
      "question": "残敵",
      "answer": "ざんてき",
      "meaning": "remnants of an enemy army"
    },
    {
      "question": "山腹",
      "answer": "さんぷく",
      "meaning": "hillside, mountainside"
    },
    {
      "question": "答弁",
      "answer": "とうべん",
      "meaning": "response, reply, answer, defence, defense"
    },
    {
      "question": "便宜的",
      "answer": "べんぎてき",
      "meaning": "convenient, expedient, makeshift"
    },
    {
      "question": "年輪",
      "answer": "ねんりん",
      "meaning": "annual tree ring, growth ring, experience in life"
    },
    {
      "question": "分捕る",
      "answer": "ぶんどる",
      "meaning": "to capture, to seize, to plunder"
    },
    {
      "question": "解かす",
      "answer": "とかす",
      "meaning": "to dissolve, to melt, to comb out, to brush, to untangle, to unravel"
    },
    {
      "question": "超弩級",
      "answer": "ちょうどきゅう",
      "meaning": "superlative, extraordinary, mega, outstanding, superdreadnought (class of warships)"
    },
    {
      "question": "打楽器",
      "answer": "だがっき",
      "meaning": "percussion instrument"
    },
    {
      "question": "民主的",
      "answer": "みんしゅてき",
      "meaning": "democratic"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪化粧",
      "answer": "ゆきげしょう",
      "meaning": "coating of snow, blanket of snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "通り一遍",
      "answer": "とおりいっぺん",
      "meaning": "perfunctory, cursory, passing, conventional, formal (greetings, compliments, etc.), casual (acquaint"
    },
    {
      "question": "体質的",
      "answer": "たいしつてき",
      "meaning": "constitutional, relating to character, structure, nature, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "舌鼓",
      "answer": "したつづみ,したづつみ",
      "meaning": "smacking one's lips"
    },
    {
      "question": "媛",
      "answer": "ひめ",
      "meaning": "young lady of noble birth, princess (esp. in Western contexts, tales, etc.), girl, small, cute, less"
    },
    {
      "question": "改稿",
      "answer": "かいこう",
      "meaning": "revising (e.g. manuscript), rewriting, revised manuscript"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛布団",
      "answer": "かけぶとん",
      "meaning": "duvet, bed cover, coverlet, quilt, comforter, eiderdown"
    },
    {
      "question": "興業",
      "answer": "こうぎょう",
      "meaning": "promotion of industry, inauguration of a new industrial enterprise"
    },
    {
      "question": "野球帽",
      "answer": "やきゅうぼう",
      "meaning": "baseball cap"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺陣",
      "answer": "たて,さつじん",
      "meaning": "sword battle (staged for television, etc.), sword fight"
    },
    {
      "question": "知恵の輪",
      "answer": "ちえのわ",
      "meaning": "puzzle ring, wire puzzle, exercise where students link crossed hands in a circle and try working tog"
    },
    {
      "question": "席次",
      "answer": "せきじ",
      "meaning": "order of seats, seating precedence, class standing"
    },
    {
      "question": "身嗜み",
      "answer": "みだしなみ",
      "meaning": "(personal) appearance, (personal) grooming, essential skill, required knowledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "闘牛",
      "answer": "とうぎゅう",
      "meaning": "bullfighting, bullfight, fighting bull"
    },
    {
      "question": "確率論",
      "answer": "かくりつろん",
      "meaning": "probability theory"
    },
    {
      "question": "猥談",
      "answer": "わいだん",
      "meaning": "indecent talk, dirty story"
    },
    {
      "question": "春夏秋冬",
      "answer": "しゅんかしゅうとう",
      "meaning": "spring, summer, autumn (fall) and winter, the four seasons"
    },
    {
      "question": "入り婿",
      "answer": "いりむこ",
      "meaning": "man who takes his wife's family name and marries into her family, man who is adopted by his wife's f"
    },
    {
      "question": "種馬",
      "answer": "たねうま",
      "meaning": "studhorse, stallion, breeding horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "豊潤",
      "answer": "ほうじゅん",
      "meaning": "abundant, rich, ripe, mellow"
    },
    {
      "question": "食い合う",
      "answer": "くいあう",
      "meaning": "to bite each other, to fit together, to mutually encroach, to eat together"
    },
    {
      "question": "大博打",
      "answer": "おおばくち",
      "meaning": "risky speculation, big gamble, large bet"
    },
    {
      "question": "板に付く",
      "answer": "いたにつく",
      "meaning": "to get used to, to become accustomed to, to be at home (on the stage)"
    },
    {
      "question": "場所柄",
      "answer": "ばしょがら",
      "meaning": "character of a place, situation, location, occasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "常習",
      "answer": "じょうしゅう",
      "meaning": "custom, common practice, habit"
    },
    {
      "question": "良人",
      "answer": "おっと,りょうじん,りょうにん",
      "meaning": "husband, good person"
    },
    {
      "question": "梶",
      "answer": "かじ",
      "meaning": "rudder, helm, paper mulberry (Broussonetia papyrifera)"
    },
    {
      "question": "変幻",
      "answer": "へんげん",
      "meaning": "transformation"
    },
    {
      "question": "階梯",
      "answer": "かいてい",
      "meaning": "stairs, rank, grade, gradations, step, guide, guidebook, slanted ladder (exercise equipment)"
    },
    {
      "question": "歓",
      "answer": "かん",
      "meaning": "joy, enjoyment, delight, pleasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "渦潮",
      "answer": "うずしお",
      "meaning": "whirling tides"
    },
    {
      "question": "手合",
      "answer": "てあい",
      "meaning": "that kind, competition, match"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼夷弾",
      "answer": "しょういだん",
      "meaning": "incendiary bomb, firebomb"
    },
    {
      "question": "剝奪",
      "answer": "はくだつ",
      "meaning": "stripping (of rights, office, etc.), deprivation, divestiture, forfeit, revocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "梅干",
      "answer": "うめぼし",
      "meaning": "umeboshi, pickled dried ume, pickled dried plum"
    },
    {
      "question": "仰角",
      "answer": "ぎょうかく",
      "meaning": "angle of elevation"
    },
    {
      "question": "寛恕",
      "answer": "かんじょ",
      "meaning": "magnanimity, forgiveness, generosity"
    },
    {
      "question": "父性",
      "answer": "ふせい",
      "meaning": "paternity"
    },
    {
      "question": "豆電球",
      "answer": "まめでんきゅう",
      "meaning": "miniature light bulb, midget lamp"
    },
    {
      "question": "家筋",
      "answer": "いえすじ",
      "meaning": "lineage, pedigree, family line"
    },
    {
      "question": "静止画",
      "answer": "せいしが",
      "meaning": "still image"
    },
    {
      "question": "水洗",
      "answer": "すいせん",
      "meaning": "washing with water, rinsing, flushing"
    },
    {
      "question": "四つ折り",
      "answer": "よつおり",
      "meaning": "folding into four, quarto"
    },
    {
      "question": "彼の娘",
      "answer": "あのこ",
      "meaning": "that girl, that kid, you (mainly used by a brothel owner or senior prostitutes when addressing serva"
    },
    {
      "question": "先々週",
      "answer": "せんせんしゅう",
      "meaning": "week before last"
    },
    {
      "question": "大人物",
      "answer": "だいじんぶつ",
      "meaning": "great man, magnanimous man"
    },
    {
      "question": "海里",
      "answer": "かいり",
      "meaning": "nautical mile"
    },
    {
      "question": "退団",
      "answer": "たいだん",
      "meaning": "leaving (a group, team, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "中絶",
      "answer": "ちゅうぜつ",
      "meaning": "abortion, to be interrupted, to be discontinued, to be suspended, to fall into abeyance"
    },
    {
      "question": "涅槃",
      "answer": "ねはん",
      "meaning": "nirvana, supreme enlightenment, death, death of Buddha"
    },
    {
      "question": "泡立て器",
      "answer": "あわだてき,あわたてき",
      "meaning": "eggbeater, whisk"
    },
    {
      "question": "言祝ぐ",
      "answer": "ことほぐ",
      "meaning": "to congratulate, to wish (someone) well, to celebrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "広葉樹",
      "answer": "こうようじゅ",
      "meaning": "broadleaf tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "自己否定",
      "answer": "じこひてい",
      "meaning": "self-denial"
    },
    {
      "question": "後れ",
      "answer": "おくれ",
      "meaning": "delay, lag, postponement, falling behind"
    },
    {
      "question": "受取人",
      "answer": "うけとりにん",
      "meaning": "recipient"
    },
    {
      "question": "策略家",
      "answer": "さくりゃくか",
      "meaning": "tactician, strategist, schemer, maneuverer"
    },
    {
      "question": "神仙",
      "answer": "しんせん",
      "meaning": "immortal mountain wizard (in Taoism), Taoist immortal, supernatural being, (in Japan) 11th note of t"
    },
    {
      "question": "海亀",
      "answer": "うみがめ",
      "meaning": "sea turtle"
    },
    {
      "question": "水道橋",
      "answer": "すいどうきょう",
      "meaning": "aqueduct, water bridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "陳",
      "answer": "ちん",
      "meaning": "Chen (ancient Chinese state, approx. 1045-479 BCE), Ch'en, Chen dynasty (China, 557-589 BCE), Ch'en"
    },
    {
      "question": "買取り",
      "answer": "かいとり",
      "meaning": "purchase, buying, buying out, buying used articles as a company, trade-in, buy back, purchase on a n"
    },
    {
      "question": "土器",
      "answer": "どき,かわらけ",
      "meaning": "earthenware, unglazed (bisque-fired) earthenware"
    },
    {
      "question": "メル友",
      "answer": "メルとも",
      "meaning": "email friend, email penpal"
    },
    {
      "question": "青信号",
      "answer": "あおしんごう",
      "meaning": "green light (traffic), green light, go-ahead signal, permission to go ahead (with something)"
    },
    {
      "question": "児童公園",
      "answer": "じどうこうえん",
      "meaning": "children's park, children's playground"
    },
    {
      "question": "年次",
      "answer": "ねんじ",
      "meaning": "annual, yearly, year (e.g. of graduation), nth year (e.g. student), order by year"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄砲水",
      "answer": "てっぽうみず",
      "meaning": "flash flood"
    },
    {
      "question": "草鞋",
      "answer": "わらじ",
      "meaning": "straw sandals"
    },
    {
      "question": "下剤",
      "answer": "げざい",
      "meaning": "laxative, purgative, evacuant"
    },
    {
      "question": "兼務",
      "answer": "けんむ",
      "meaning": "serving concurrently as, holding the additional post of, additional post"
    },
    {
      "question": "復職",
      "answer": "ふくしょく",
      "meaning": "reinstatement, reappointment"
    },
    {
      "question": "男役",
      "answer": "おとこやく",
      "meaning": "male part or role"
    },
    {
      "question": "功名心",
      "answer": "こうみょうしん",
      "meaning": "ambition, aspiration"
    },
    {
      "question": "物の数",
      "answer": "もののかず",
      "meaning": "something worth mentioning, something to count on, something problematic"
    },
    {
      "question": "心筋梗塞",
      "answer": "しんきんこうそく",
      "meaning": "heart attack, myocardial infarction"
    },
    {
      "question": "併発",
      "answer": "へいはつ",
      "meaning": "concurrence, coincidence, complication (in illness)"
    },
    {
      "question": "初号",
      "answer": "しょごう",
      "meaning": "first number (e.g. issue of a magazine), No. 1 type"
    },
    {
      "question": "史書",
      "answer": "ししょ",
      "meaning": "history book"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜警",
      "answer": "やけい",
      "meaning": "night watchman"
    },
    {
      "question": "浣腸",
      "answer": "かんちょう",
      "meaning": "(giving an) enema"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤線",
      "answer": "あかせん",
      "meaning": "red line, red-light district (marked by a red line on police maps), non-legal public road (denoted b"
    },
    {
      "question": "復路",
      "answer": "ふくろ",
      "meaning": "return path (of a signal, communication), return trip"
    },
    {
      "question": "ゴルフ場",
      "answer": "ゴルフじょう",
      "meaning": "golf course, golf links"
    },
    {
      "question": "渡米",
      "answer": "とべい",
      "meaning": "going to the United States"
    },
    {
      "question": "所得",
      "answer": "しょとく",
      "meaning": "income, earnings"
    },
    {
      "question": "現れ出る",
      "answer": "あらわれでる",
      "meaning": "to appear"
    },
    {
      "question": "反発力",
      "answer": "はんぱつりょく",
      "meaning": "repellent force, resiliency, elasticity"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨席",
      "answer": "りんせき",
      "meaning": "attendance, presence"
    },
    {
      "question": "傍流",
      "answer": "ぼうりゅう",
      "meaning": "branch, tributary"
    },
    {
      "question": "満ち欠け",
      "answer": "みちかけ",
      "meaning": "waxing and waning (of the Moon)"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠景",
      "answer": "えんけい",
      "meaning": "vista, background, perspective, distant view"
    },
    {
      "question": "条件付け",
      "answer": "じょうけんづけ",
      "meaning": "conditioning"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸潰れ",
      "answer": "まるつぶれ",
      "meaning": "complete ruin, collapse, losing (something) completely (e.g. face)"
    },
    {
      "question": "獄卒",
      "answer": "ごくそつ",
      "meaning": "low-ranking prison guard, hell's tormenting devils"
    },
    {
      "question": "印刷機",
      "answer": "いんさつき",
      "meaning": "printing press"
    },
    {
      "question": "通信士",
      "answer": "つうしんし",
      "meaning": "radio operator, telegraphist, telegraph operator, radio officer"
    },
    {
      "question": "白血病",
      "answer": "はっけつびょう",
      "meaning": "leukemia"
    },
    {
      "question": "建築士",
      "answer": "けんちくし",
      "meaning": "authorized architect and builder, licensed architect, registered architect"
    },
    {
      "question": "新春",
      "answer": "しんしゅん",
      "meaning": "New Year (Spring)"
    },
    {
      "question": "緑化",
      "answer": "りょっか,りょくか",
      "meaning": "greening (i.e. planting to increase greenery), tree planting, afforestation"
    },
    {
      "question": "根拠地",
      "answer": "こんきょち",
      "meaning": "base (of operations)"
    },
    {
      "question": "堤",
      "answer": "つつみ",
      "meaning": "bank, embankment, dike"
    },
    {
      "question": "精肉",
      "answer": "せいにく",
      "meaning": "(good quality) meat, processed meat, small goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "下馬",
      "answer": "げば",
      "meaning": "dismounting"
    },
    {
      "question": "言う所の",
      "answer": "いうところの",
      "meaning": "what is called, as it is called, the so-called, known as, so to speak"
    },
    {
      "question": "液化",
      "answer": "えきか",
      "meaning": "liquefaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "健診",
      "answer": "けんしん",
      "meaning": "physical examination, medical examination, health checkup, health screening"
    },
    {
      "question": "粘着力",
      "answer": "ねんちゃくりょく",
      "meaning": "adhesive power, viscosity"
    },
    {
      "question": "巣立ち",
      "answer": "すだち",
      "meaning": "leaving the nest, going out into the world, becoming independent"
    },
    {
      "question": "洋楽",
      "answer": "ようがく",
      "meaning": "Western music, European music"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗務員",
      "answer": "じょうむいん",
      "meaning": "transport staff (driver, conductor, etc.), crew member, crewman"
    },
    {
      "question": "咽ぶ",
      "answer": "むせぶ",
      "meaning": "to be choked, to be stifled, to be smothered"
    },
    {
      "question": "一纏め",
      "answer": "ひとまとめ",
      "meaning": "bundle, pack, bunch"
    },
    {
      "question": "火葬場",
      "answer": "かそうば",
      "meaning": "crematory, crematorium"
    },
    {
      "question": "輪唱",
      "answer": "りんしょう",
      "meaning": "trolling, singing in a circular canon, round"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳酸",
      "answer": "にゅうさん",
      "meaning": "lactic acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "冠婚葬祭",
      "answer": "かんこんそうさい",
      "meaning": "important ceremonial occasions in family relationships"
    },
    {
      "question": "和訳",
      "answer": "わやく",
      "meaning": "Japanese translation"
    },
    {
      "question": "市場調査",
      "answer": "しじょうちょうさ",
      "meaning": "market research"
    },
    {
      "question": "競り合い",
      "answer": "せりあい",
      "meaning": "competition"
    },
    {
      "question": "札付き",
      "answer": "ふだつき",
      "meaning": "tagged (esp. with a price), notorious, infamous, double-dyed, hardened"
    },
    {
      "question": "双肩",
      "answer": "そうけん",
      "meaning": "shoulders"
    },
    {
      "question": "代入",
      "answer": "だいにゅう",
      "meaning": "substitution, assignment"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘蔵っ子",
      "answer": "ひぞっこ,ひぞうっこ",
      "meaning": "favourite child, favourite student, apple of one's eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "早道",
      "answer": "はやみち",
      "meaning": "shortcut"
    },
    {
      "question": "胎教",
      "answer": "たいきょう",
      "meaning": "prenatal care, antenatal training"
    },
    {
      "question": "関ヶ原",
      "answer": "せきがはら",
      "meaning": "Sekigahara (battle site, 1600), decisive battle, critical battle"
    },
    {
      "question": "開運",
      "answer": "かいうん",
      "meaning": "better fortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "巣箱",
      "answer": "すばこ",
      "meaning": "birdhouse, nest box, bird box, beehive"
    },
    {
      "question": "古戦場",
      "answer": "こせんじょう",
      "meaning": "ancient battlefield"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜戦",
      "answer": "やせん",
      "meaning": "night warfare"
    },
    {
      "question": "世界記録",
      "answer": "せかいきろく",
      "meaning": "world record, establishing a world record (in)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大腸",
      "answer": "だいちょう,おおわた",
      "meaning": "large intestine, large bowel, colon"
    },
    {
      "question": "未発表",
      "answer": "みはっぴょう",
      "meaning": "unpublished, not yet announced"
    },
    {
      "question": "彷徨く",
      "answer": "うろつく",
      "meaning": "to loiter, to putter, to prowl, to wander aimlessly, to knock around, to hang around, to be confused"
    },
    {
      "question": "固着",
      "answer": "こちゃく",
      "meaning": "adherence, sticking (to), fixation"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺産相続",
      "answer": "いさんそうぞく",
      "meaning": "inheritance, succession to property"
    },
    {
      "question": "高等教育",
      "answer": "こうとうきょういく",
      "meaning": "higher education"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒類",
      "answer": "しゅるい",
      "meaning": "alcoholic drinks, liquor"
    },
    {
      "question": "世を忍ぶ",
      "answer": "よをしのぶ",
      "meaning": "to hide from society, to avoid the gaze of society, to keep out of the public eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "知らぬ顔",
      "answer": "しらぬかお",
      "meaning": "pretending not to know, feigning ignorance"
    },
    {
      "question": "安月給",
      "answer": "やすげっきゅう",
      "meaning": "low salary"
    },
    {
      "question": "移ろい",
      "answer": "うつろい",
      "meaning": "change, changing, vicissitudes, fading, waning"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧館",
      "answer": "きゅうかん",
      "meaning": "old building, older building"
    },
    {
      "question": "天眼",
      "answer": "てんげん,てんがん",
      "meaning": "the heavenly eye, rolling back one's eyes during convulsions"
    },
    {
      "question": "庭番",
      "answer": "にわばん",
      "meaning": "garden watchman, garden keeper, guard of the inner garden"
    },
    {
      "question": "杖術",
      "answer": "じょうじゅつ",
      "meaning": "jōjutsu, form of martial art using a cane staff"
    },
    {
      "question": "遣い手",
      "answer": "つかいて",
      "meaning": "user, consumer, employer, master (e.g. of swordsmanship), prodigal, spendthrift"
    },
    {
      "question": "革ジャン",
      "answer": "かわジャン",
      "meaning": "leather jacket"
    },
    {
      "question": "納涼",
      "answer": "のうりょう",
      "meaning": "(enjoying the) cool of the evening"
    },
    {
      "question": "謡う",
      "answer": "うたう",
      "meaning": "to sing, to sing (one's praises in a poem, etc.), to compose a poem, to recite a poem"
    },
    {
      "question": "同一化",
      "answer": "どういつか",
      "meaning": "identification (with)"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬首",
      "answer": "ばしゅ",
      "meaning": "neck of a horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "心持",
      "answer": "こころもち",
      "meaning": "feeling, mood, sensation, disposition, mental attitude, somewhat, slightly, just a little"
    },
    {
      "question": "大笑",
      "answer": "たいしょう",
      "meaning": "loud laughter, hearty laugh"
    },
    {
      "question": "血止め",
      "answer": "ちどめ",
      "meaning": "styptic, stopping of bleeding"
    },
    {
      "question": "媚態",
      "answer": "びたい",
      "meaning": "coquetry"
    },
    {
      "question": "這い蹲う",
      "answer": "はいつくばう",
      "meaning": "to grovel, to go down on one's hands and knees"
    },
    {
      "question": "化合物",
      "answer": "かごうぶつ",
      "meaning": "compound"
    },
    {
      "question": "実弟",
      "answer": "じってい",
      "meaning": "biological younger brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "割譲",
      "answer": "かつじょう",
      "meaning": "cession (of territory)"
    },
    {
      "question": "息吹く",
      "answer": "いぶく,いふく",
      "meaning": "to breathe"
    },
    {
      "question": "下命",
      "answer": "かめい",
      "meaning": "order, command"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪条件",
      "answer": "あくじょうけん",
      "meaning": "unfavorable conditions, unfavourable conditions"
    },
    {
      "question": "温度計",
      "answer": "おんどけい",
      "meaning": "thermometer"
    },
    {
      "question": "篝",
      "answer": "かがり",
      "meaning": "iron basket for torches, cresset, brazier, bonfire"
    },
    {
      "question": "神使",
      "answer": "しんし,じんし",
      "meaning": "messenger of god, divine messenger"
    },
    {
      "question": "親爺",
      "answer": "おやじ",
      "meaning": "one's father, old man, one's boss"
    },
    {
      "question": "挿む",
      "answer": "はさむ",
      "meaning": "to hold between (e.g. one's fingers, chopsticks), to grip (from both sides), to put between, to sand"
    },
    {
      "question": "安息日",
      "answer": "あんそくにち,あんそくじつ,あんそくび",
      "meaning": "(Judeo-Christian) Sabbath"
    },
    {
      "question": "音叉",
      "answer": "おんさ",
      "meaning": "tuning fork"
    },
    {
      "question": "痛苦",
      "answer": "つうく",
      "meaning": "anguish, (great) pain"
    },
    {
      "question": "ガス灯",
      "answer": "ガスとう",
      "meaning": "gas light, gas lamp"
    },
    {
      "question": "子馬",
      "answer": "こうま",
      "meaning": "small horse, pony, foal, colt, filly"
    },
    {
      "question": "稚気",
      "answer": "ちき",
      "meaning": "childishness, naivete"
    },
    {
      "question": "違和",
      "answer": "いわ",
      "meaning": "physical disorder"
    },
    {
      "question": "釈迦",
      "answer": "しゃか",
      "meaning": "Gautama Buddha, Shakyamuni, the historical Buddha"
    },
    {
      "question": "条文",
      "answer": "じょうぶん",
      "meaning": "text, provisions (act, treaty)"
    },
    {
      "question": "玉虫色",
      "answer": "たまむしいろ",
      "meaning": "iridescent colour, equivocal (reply, statement, etc.), ambiguous, vague"
    },
    {
      "question": "天日干し",
      "answer": "てんぴぼし",
      "meaning": "sun drying, solar drying"
    },
    {
      "question": "珍客",
      "answer": "ちんきゃく,ちんかく",
      "meaning": "unexpected (but welcome) visitor, rare guest"
    },
    {
      "question": "割を食う",
      "answer": "わりをくう",
      "meaning": "to be put at a disadvantage, to get the short end of the stick"
    },
    {
      "question": "麗らか",
      "answer": "うららか",
      "meaning": "bright (weather, mood, voice, etc.), clear, fine, beautiful, glorious, splendid, cheerful"
    },
    {
      "question": "艦載機",
      "answer": "かんさいき",
      "meaning": "ship-borne plane"
    },
    {
      "question": "組合員",
      "answer": "くみあいいん",
      "meaning": "unionist, union member"
    },
    {
      "question": "造船所",
      "answer": "ぞうせんじょ,ぞうせんしょ",
      "meaning": "shipyard, dock yard, shipbuilding yard"
    },
    {
      "question": "改行",
      "answer": "かいぎょう",
      "meaning": "new line, new paragraph, newline (e.g. LF, CR, CRLF)"
    },
    {
      "question": "法悦",
      "answer": "ほうえつ",
      "meaning": "religious exultation, ecstasy"
    },
    {
      "question": "確と",
      "answer": "しかと,しっかと",
      "meaning": "certainly, for sure, distinctly, clearly, exactly, firmly, tightly"
    },
    {
      "question": "賛歌",
      "answer": "さんか",
      "meaning": "song of praise, eulogy, paean, hymn"
    },
    {
      "question": "天の邪鬼",
      "answer": "あまのじゃく",
      "meaning": "perversity, perverse person, contrary person, contrarian, antagonistic demon in Japanese folklore, d"
    },
    {
      "question": "生白い",
      "answer": "なまじろい",
      "meaning": "pale, pallid, wan, pasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "負ぶう",
      "answer": "おぶう",
      "meaning": "to carry (a child) on one's back, to piggyback, to take on (a job, responsibility, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "身繕い",
      "answer": "みづくろい",
      "meaning": "dressing oneself, personal grooming"
    },
    {
      "question": "人事異動",
      "answer": "じんじいどう",
      "meaning": "personnel change, personnel shift, reshuffle, (annual) staff reassignment"
    },
    {
      "question": "笑い上戸",
      "answer": "わらいじょうご",
      "meaning": "merry drinker, one who laughs easily"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄養分",
      "answer": "えいようぶん",
      "meaning": "nutriment, nutritious substance, nourishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "品書き",
      "answer": "しながき",
      "meaning": "catalog, catalogue, inventory, menu"
    },
    {
      "question": "全文",
      "answer": "ぜんぶん",
      "meaning": "whole passage, full text, whole sentence, full paragraph"
    },
    {
      "question": "簡略",
      "answer": "かんりゃく",
      "meaning": "simple, brief"
    },
    {
      "question": "都会的",
      "answer": "とかいてき",
      "meaning": "urban, metropolitan"
    },
    {
      "question": "高給",
      "answer": "こうきゅう",
      "meaning": "high salary"
    },
    {
      "question": "野心的",
      "answer": "やしんてき",
      "meaning": "ambitious, enterprising"
    },
    {
      "question": "九重",
      "answer": "ここのえ,きゅうちょう,くじゅう",
      "meaning": "ninefold, imperial palace, the Court"
    },
    {
      "question": "雷火",
      "answer": "らいか",
      "meaning": "flash of lightning, fire caused by lightning"
    },
    {
      "question": "桜餅",
      "answer": "さくらもち",
      "meaning": "rice cake with bean paste wrapped in a preserved cherry leaf"
    },
    {
      "question": "直刀",
      "answer": "ちょくとう",
      "meaning": "straight sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "適性検査",
      "answer": "てきせいけんさ",
      "meaning": "aptitude test"
    },
    {
      "question": "風除け",
      "answer": "かざよけ,かぜよけ",
      "meaning": "windbreak"
    },
    {
      "question": "債務",
      "answer": "さいむ",
      "meaning": "debt, liabilities, obligation to a person or party (usu. legal or contractual)"
    },
    {
      "question": "打突",
      "answer": "だとつ",
      "meaning": "strike (kendo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "呵々",
      "answer": "かか",
      "meaning": "sound of laughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "船影",
      "answer": "せんえい,ふなかげ",
      "meaning": "sign of a ship (e.g. through fog, silhouette, etc.), outline of a ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠泳",
      "answer": "えんえい",
      "meaning": "long-distance swimming"
    },
    {
      "question": "管内",
      "answer": "かんない",
      "meaning": "within the jurisdiction of"
    },
    {
      "question": "四面",
      "answer": "しめん",
      "meaning": "four sides, all sides"
    },
    {
      "question": "地球儀",
      "answer": "ちきゅうぎ",
      "meaning": "globe (map)"
    },
    {
      "question": "落とし主",
      "answer": "おとしぬし",
      "meaning": "loser, owner of a lost article"
    },
    {
      "question": "黴臭い",
      "answer": "かびくさい",
      "meaning": "smelling of mold, musty, putrid, old-fashioned, stale, hackneyed, worn-out"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪解け水",
      "answer": "ゆきどけみず",
      "meaning": "snowmelt, meltwater, melted snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄暮",
      "answer": "はくぼ",
      "meaning": "dusk, nightfall, twilight"
    },
    {
      "question": "用水",
      "answer": "ようすい",
      "meaning": "irrigation water, water for fire, city water, cistern water"
    },
    {
      "question": "物干し",
      "answer": "ものほし",
      "meaning": "frame for drying clothes, clotheshorse"
    },
    {
      "question": "清聴",
      "answer": "せいちょう",
      "meaning": "attention, kind attention, courteous attention"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛しむ",
      "answer": "おしむ,いとしむ",
      "meaning": "to be frugal, to be sparing, to value, to hold dear, to regret (e.g. a loss), to feel sorry (for), t"
    },
    {
      "question": "暇を出す",
      "answer": "ひまをだす",
      "meaning": "to dismiss (an employee), to discharge, to let go, to fire, to divorce one's wife, to give a holiday"
    },
    {
      "question": "禅問答",
      "answer": "ぜんもんどう",
      "meaning": "Zen dialogue, Zen questions and answers"
    },
    {
      "question": "呆気",
      "answer": "あっけ",
      "meaning": "being taken aback, state of shock, dumbfoundedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "余念",
      "answer": "よねん",
      "meaning": "another idea"
    },
    {
      "question": "民生",
      "answer": "みんせい",
      "meaning": "public welfare, the people's livelihood"
    },
    {
      "question": "針葉樹林",
      "answer": "しんようじゅりん",
      "meaning": "conifer forest, coniferous forest, needle-leaved forest"
    },
    {
      "question": "目許",
      "answer": "めもと",
      "meaning": "eyes, expression of the eyes, area around the eyes, skin round one's eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "今迄",
      "answer": "いままで",
      "meaning": "until now, so far, up to the present"
    },
    {
      "question": "無痛",
      "answer": "むつう",
      "meaning": "painless"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍事基地",
      "answer": "ぐんじきち",
      "meaning": "military base"
    },
    {
      "question": "湧水",
      "answer": "ゆうすい",
      "meaning": "spring, welling of water"
    },
    {
      "question": "濡れ場",
      "answer": "ぬれば",
      "meaning": "love scene, bedroom scene, sex scene"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄火場",
      "answer": "てっかば",
      "meaning": "gambling den, gambling house"
    },
    {
      "question": "大過",
      "answer": "たいか",
      "meaning": "serious error, gross mistake"
    },
    {
      "question": "外洋",
      "answer": "がいよう",
      "meaning": "open sea, ocean"
    },
    {
      "question": "両生類",
      "answer": "りょうせいるい",
      "meaning": "amphibia, amphibian"
    },
    {
      "question": "温暖化",
      "answer": "おんだんか",
      "meaning": "warming, global warming"
    },
    {
      "question": "山並み",
      "answer": "やまなみ",
      "meaning": "mountain range, mountain belt"
    },
    {
      "question": "対向車",
      "answer": "たいこうしゃ",
      "meaning": "car (running) on the opposite lane, oncoming car"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨太",
      "answer": "ほねぶと",
      "meaning": "big-boned, sturdily built, stout, solid (plan, storyline, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り留め",
      "answer": "とりとめ",
      "meaning": "coherence, order, focus, point"
    },
    {
      "question": "左前",
      "answer": "ひだりまえ",
      "meaning": "wearing a kimono with the right side over the left (normally used only for the dead), going badly (o"
    },
    {
      "question": "杳として",
      "answer": "ようとして",
      "meaning": "no information, no clue, completely unknown"
    },
    {
      "question": "複雑骨折",
      "answer": "ふくざつこっせつ",
      "meaning": "compound fracture"
    },
    {
      "question": "早寝",
      "answer": "はやね",
      "meaning": "go to bed early"
    },
    {
      "question": "小唄",
      "answer": "こうた",
      "meaning": "kouta, traditional ballad accompanied by shamisen"
    },
    {
      "question": "名取",
      "answer": "なとり",
      "meaning": "accredited master (of a performing art), being famous, being popular, famous person"
    },
    {
      "question": "高等科",
      "answer": "こうとうか",
      "meaning": "advanced course"
    },
    {
      "question": "寅",
      "answer": "とら",
      "meaning": "the Tiger (third sign of the Chinese zodiac), hour of the Tiger (around 4am, 3-5am, or 4-6am), east-"
    },
    {
      "question": "呪物",
      "answer": "じゅぶつ",
      "meaning": "fetish"
    },
    {
      "question": "荘園",
      "answer": "しょうえん,そうえん",
      "meaning": "manor, demesne"
    },
    {
      "question": "大陰唇",
      "answer": "だいいんしん",
      "meaning": "labia majora"
    },
    {
      "question": "闇金",
      "answer": "やみきん",
      "meaning": "black-market lending, illegal loan"
    },
    {
      "question": "徳用",
      "answer": "とくよう",
      "meaning": "economical, economy size, family size (esp. of packaged food)"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄転",
      "answer": "えいてん",
      "meaning": "promotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "川縁",
      "answer": "かわぶち,かわべり",
      "meaning": "riverbank, riverside"
    },
    {
      "question": "反物",
      "answer": "たんもの",
      "meaning": "fabric, cloth, textiles, drapery, dry-goods, piece goods, measure of kimono material"
    },
    {
      "question": "嵩む",
      "answer": "かさむ",
      "meaning": "to mount up, to pile up, to accumulate, to increase"
    },
    {
      "question": "道義",
      "answer": "どうぎ",
      "meaning": "morality, moral principles"
    },
    {
      "question": "憤死",
      "answer": "ふんし",
      "meaning": "dying in a fit of anger or indignation"
    },
    {
      "question": "第一報",
      "answer": "だいいっぽう",
      "meaning": "first report (esp. of an incident, disaster, or news story), initial report"
    },
    {
      "question": "一般化",
      "answer": "いっぱんか",
      "meaning": "generalization, generalisation, popularization, popularisation, to generalize, to generalise, to pop"
    },
    {
      "question": "震う",
      "answer": "ふるう",
      "meaning": "to shake, to tremble, to vibrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "立身出世",
      "answer": "りっしんしゅっせ",
      "meaning": "success in life"
    },
    {
      "question": "地学",
      "answer": "ちがく",
      "meaning": "earth science, geoscience"
    },
    {
      "question": "必滅",
      "answer": "ひつめつ",
      "meaning": "mortality"
    },
    {
      "question": "多頭",
      "answer": "たとう",
      "meaning": "many-headed, hydra-headed, large-scale (e.g. breeding)"
    },
    {
      "question": "核爆発",
      "answer": "かくばくはつ",
      "meaning": "nuclear explosion"
    },
    {
      "question": "製鉄",
      "answer": "せいてつ",
      "meaning": "iron manufacture"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈎",
      "answer": "はり,ち,かぎ",
      "meaning": "needle, pin, hook, stinger, thorn, hand (e.g. clock, etc.), pointer, staple (for a stapler), needlew"
    },
    {
      "question": "将軍職",
      "answer": "しょうぐんしょく",
      "meaning": "the shogunate"
    },
    {
      "question": "受診",
      "answer": "じゅしん",
      "meaning": "having a medical examination, seeing a doctor"
    },
    {
      "question": "中立地帯",
      "answer": "ちゅうりつちたい",
      "meaning": "neutral zone, demilitarized zone"
    },
    {
      "question": "栃木",
      "answer": "とちぎ",
      "meaning": "Tochigi (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "人夫",
      "answer": "にんぷ",
      "meaning": "laborer (labourer), construction worker, coolie"
    },
    {
      "question": "晩夏",
      "answer": "ばんか",
      "meaning": "late summer, sixth month of the lunar calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "天運",
      "answer": "てんうん",
      "meaning": "destiny, will of Heaven, luck"
    },
    {
      "question": "興奮剤",
      "answer": "こうふんざい",
      "meaning": "stimulant"
    },
    {
      "question": "駿馬",
      "answer": "しゅんめ,しゅんば",
      "meaning": "swift horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "西端",
      "answer": "せいたん",
      "meaning": "western edge (e.g. of city), west side"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘中の秘",
      "answer": "ひちゅうのひ",
      "meaning": "top secret"
    },
    {
      "question": "洋室",
      "answer": "ようしつ",
      "meaning": "Western-style room"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹案",
      "answer": "ふくあん",
      "meaning": "one's plan"
    },
    {
      "question": "濡れ髪",
      "answer": "ぬれがみ",
      "meaning": "newly washed hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き回す",
      "answer": "ひきまわす",
      "meaning": "to draw around (e.g. a curtain), to drag around, to take (someone) around, to parade around, to orde"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮世",
      "answer": "うきよ,ふせい",
      "meaning": "fleeting life, this transient world, floating world, sad world, world of grief and worry, the world"
    },
    {
      "question": "横面",
      "answer": "よこつら",
      "meaning": "side of face"
    },
    {
      "question": "廷臣",
      "answer": "ていしん",
      "meaning": "courtier"
    },
    {
      "question": "益荒男",
      "answer": "ますらお",
      "meaning": "hero, manly person, warrior"
    },
    {
      "question": "人工島",
      "answer": "じんこうとう",
      "meaning": "artificial island, man-made island"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇将",
      "answer": "ゆうしょう",
      "meaning": "brave general, great soldier"
    },
    {
      "question": "夫君",
      "answer": "ふくん",
      "meaning": "(another's) husband"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪上",
      "answer": "せつじょう",
      "meaning": "on the snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "元夫",
      "answer": "もとおっと",
      "meaning": "ex-husband, former husband"
    },
    {
      "question": "卒業旅行",
      "answer": "そつぎょうりょこう",
      "meaning": "graduation trip"
    },
    {
      "question": "物売り",
      "answer": "ものうり",
      "meaning": "street vendor, peddler"
    },
    {
      "question": "定期試験",
      "answer": "ていきしけん",
      "meaning": "regular (periodic) examination"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛行機雲",
      "answer": "ひこうきぐも",
      "meaning": "vapor trail (vapour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "山裾",
      "answer": "やますそ",
      "meaning": "foot or base of a mountain, foothills"
    },
    {
      "question": "睦み合う",
      "answer": "むつみあう",
      "meaning": "to get along well together, to be close to each other"
    },
    {
      "question": "食前酒",
      "answer": "しょくぜんしゅ",
      "meaning": "aperitif"
    },
    {
      "question": "懲戒免職",
      "answer": "ちょうかいめんしょく",
      "meaning": "disciplinary dismissal (discharge)"
    },
    {
      "question": "慣わし",
      "answer": "ならわし",
      "meaning": "custom, habit, customary practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "一夫一妻",
      "answer": "いっぷいっさい",
      "meaning": "monogamy"
    },
    {
      "question": "端緒",
      "answer": "たんしょ,たんちょ",
      "meaning": "start, beginning, first step, clue"
    },
    {
      "question": "縦線",
      "answer": "じゅうせん,たてせん",
      "meaning": "vertical line, bar line (e.g. in music)"
    },
    {
      "question": "快気祝い",
      "answer": "かいきいわい",
      "meaning": "celebrating recovery from illness"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶飲み話",
      "answer": "ちゃのみばなし",
      "meaning": "chat over tea"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲み代",
      "answer": "のみしろ,のみだい",
      "meaning": "drink money, drinking money"
    },
    {
      "question": "懐が深い",
      "answer": "ふところがふかい",
      "meaning": "broad-minded, (of a rikishi) tall, with long reach, making it harder for their opponent to get a gri"
    },
    {
      "question": "見習",
      "answer": "みならい",
      "meaning": "apprenticeship, probation, learning by observation, apprentice, trainee, probationer"
    },
    {
      "question": "各校",
      "answer": "かくこう,かっこう",
      "meaning": "each school"
    },
    {
      "question": "湾内",
      "answer": "わんない",
      "meaning": "inside the bay"
    },
    {
      "question": "書名",
      "answer": "しょめい",
      "meaning": "book title"
    },
    {
      "question": "手淫",
      "answer": "しゅいん",
      "meaning": "masturbation, onanism"
    },
    {
      "question": "猫カフェ",
      "answer": "ねこカフェ",
      "meaning": "cat café, themed café where patrons can pet cats"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち振る",
      "answer": "うちふる",
      "meaning": "to brandish, to flourish, to wave, to swing, to shake at"
    },
    {
      "question": "聾する",
      "answer": "ろうする",
      "meaning": "to deafen"
    },
    {
      "question": "智謀",
      "answer": "ちぼう",
      "meaning": "ingenuity, resourcefulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "舌鋒",
      "answer": "ぜっぽう",
      "meaning": "sharp tongue, eloquence"
    },
    {
      "question": "取次",
      "answer": "とりつぎ",
      "meaning": "agency, commission, distributor, intermediation, reception (of guests), conveyance (of messages)"
    },
    {
      "question": "調査書",
      "answer": "ちょうさしょ",
      "meaning": "written investigation, report of an investigation, school record (on a student), transcript (of grad"
    },
    {
      "question": "囃す",
      "answer": "はやす",
      "meaning": "to play accompaniment, to keep time, to cheer, to applaud, to jeer, to mock, to banter"
    },
    {
      "question": "昔語り",
      "answer": "むかしがたり",
      "meaning": "old story, reminiscence"
    },
    {
      "question": "闖入",
      "answer": "ちんにゅう",
      "meaning": "intrusion, forced entry"
    },
    {
      "question": "分泌液",
      "answer": "ぶんぴつえき",
      "meaning": "secretion"
    },
    {
      "question": "霧吹き",
      "answer": "きりふき",
      "meaning": "spraying, sprayer, atomizer, atomiser, vaporizer"
    },
    {
      "question": "不調法",
      "answer": "ぶちょうほう",
      "meaning": "impoliteness, carelessness, misconduct, clumsiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "臆測",
      "answer": "おくそく",
      "meaning": "guess, speculation, supposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "出不精",
      "answer": "でぶしょう",
      "meaning": "stay-at-home, homebody"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬼灯",
      "answer": "ほおずき,ほおづき,ほうずき",
      "meaning": "ground cherry (Physalis alkekengi var. franchetii), husk tomato, Chinese lantern plant, children's n"
    },
    {
      "question": "芒",
      "answer": "すすき,のぎ",
      "meaning": "Japanese pampas grass (Miscanthus sinensis), maiden silvergrass, zebra grass, arista, awn, (grain) b"
    },
    {
      "question": "盗作",
      "answer": "とうさく",
      "meaning": "plagiarism, plagiarised work"
    },
    {
      "question": "翠玉",
      "answer": "すいぎょく",
      "meaning": "emerald, jade"
    },
    {
      "question": "老将",
      "answer": "ろうしょう",
      "meaning": "old or veteran army general"
    },
    {
      "question": "行幸",
      "answer": "ぎょうこう,みゆき,ぎょうごう",
      "meaning": "imperial visit"
    },
    {
      "question": "丑",
      "answer": "うし",
      "meaning": "the Ox (second sign of the Chinese zodiac), hour of the Ox (around 2am, 1-3am, or 2-4am), north-nort"
    },
    {
      "question": "五月雨",
      "answer": "さみだれ,さつきあめ",
      "meaning": "early-summer rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "投了",
      "answer": "とうりょう",
      "meaning": "resignation, giving up the game for lost"
    },
    {
      "question": "新聞屋",
      "answer": "しんぶんや",
      "meaning": "newspaper stand, newspaper seller, paper carrier, newspaper reporter"
    },
    {
      "question": "虫取り",
      "answer": "むしとり",
      "meaning": "insect catching, bug catching"
    },
    {
      "question": "小数点",
      "answer": "しょうすうてん",
      "meaning": "decimal point, radix point"
    },
    {
      "question": "銃床",
      "answer": "じゅうしょう",
      "meaning": "gunstock"
    },
    {
      "question": "父祖",
      "answer": "ふそ",
      "meaning": "ancestors"
    },
    {
      "question": "経済界",
      "answer": "けいざいかい",
      "meaning": "economic world, financial circles, business community"
    },
    {
      "question": "天上天下",
      "answer": "てんじょうてんげ",
      "meaning": "the whole world, throughout heaven and earth"
    },
    {
      "question": "損じる",
      "answer": "そんじる",
      "meaning": "to harm, to hurt, to injure, to damage"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛妻",
      "answer": "あいさい",
      "meaning": "beloved wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "背信行為",
      "answer": "はいしんこうい",
      "meaning": "breach of faith, breach of trust, act of disloyalty"
    },
    {
      "question": "狭霧",
      "answer": "さぎり",
      "meaning": "mist, fog"
    },
    {
      "question": "白面",
      "answer": "はくめん,しらふ",
      "meaning": "fair complexion, face without makeup, inexperience, sobriety, soberness, sober face"
    },
    {
      "question": "技官",
      "answer": "ぎかん",
      "meaning": "technical official, technical officer"
    },
    {
      "question": "九尾の狐",
      "answer": "きゅうびのきつね",
      "meaning": "nine-tailed kitsune (fox spirit, kitsune are said to be more powerful the more tails they have)"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨海学校",
      "answer": "りんかいがっこう",
      "meaning": "seaside school"
    },
    {
      "question": "大本営",
      "answer": "だいほんえい",
      "meaning": "Imperial General Headquarters (Japan)"
    },
    {
      "question": "蹄鉄",
      "answer": "ていてつ",
      "meaning": "horseshoe"
    },
    {
      "question": "金山",
      "answer": "きんざん,かなやま",
      "meaning": "gold mine, (metal) mine"
    },
    {
      "question": "一両",
      "answer": "いちりょう",
      "meaning": "one vehicle, one ryō (an old coin)"
    },
    {
      "question": "土手っ腹",
      "answer": "どてっぱら",
      "meaning": "guts"
    },
    {
      "question": "胃酸",
      "answer": "いさん",
      "meaning": "stomach acid, gastric acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "音楽会",
      "answer": "おんがくかい,おんがっかい",
      "meaning": "concert, recital"
    },
    {
      "question": "前歴",
      "answer": "ぜんれき",
      "meaning": "personal history"
    },
    {
      "question": "復",
      "answer": "また",
      "meaning": "again, once more, once again, another time, some other time, also, too, as well, likewise, on the ot"
    },
    {
      "question": "細波",
      "answer": "さざなみ,さざれなみ",
      "meaning": "ripple (on water), wavelets, ripple (e.g. of uneasiness), unrest, disturbance, ripple"
    },
    {
      "question": "泥人形",
      "answer": "どろにんぎょう",
      "meaning": "clay doll"
    },
    {
      "question": "畳敷き",
      "answer": "たたみじき",
      "meaning": "tatami-matted"
    },
    {
      "question": "移り気",
      "answer": "うつりぎ",
      "meaning": "fickle, capricious, inconstant, changeable, whimsical"
    },
    {
      "question": "多種",
      "answer": "たしゅ",
      "meaning": "many kinds, various"
    },
    {
      "question": "無知蒙昧",
      "answer": "むちもうまい",
      "meaning": "unenlightened, uneducated, ignorant"
    },
    {
      "question": "出足",
      "answer": "であし",
      "meaning": "turnout (of people), start (e.g. race, campaign, term of office), constant forward movement, initial"
    },
    {
      "question": "近世",
      "answer": "きんせい",
      "meaning": "recent past, recent times, early modern period (from the Azuchi-Momoyama period to the end of the Ed"
    },
    {
      "question": "芳香剤",
      "answer": "ほうこうざい",
      "meaning": "air freshener, fragrance, aromatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "概して",
      "answer": "がいして",
      "meaning": "generally, as a rule"
    },
    {
      "question": "化粧直し",
      "answer": "けしょうなおし",
      "meaning": "adjusting one's makeup, renovation, remodeling, redecoration"
    },
    {
      "question": "手垢",
      "answer": "てあか",
      "meaning": "finger marks, dirt from the hands"
    },
    {
      "question": "昇り",
      "answer": "のぼり",
      "meaning": "ascent, climbing, ascending (path), climb, upbound (esp. toward Tokyo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯が浮く",
      "answer": "はがうく",
      "meaning": "to have one's teeth set on edge, to get loose teeth"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き受け",
      "answer": "ひきうけ",
      "meaning": "undertaking, underwriting, acceptance"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち消え",
      "answer": "たちぎえ",
      "meaning": "going out (before burning completely), dying out, fizzling out (e.g. of a plan), falling through, co"
    },
    {
      "question": "怪死",
      "answer": "かいし",
      "meaning": "mysterious death"
    },
    {
      "question": "勅使",
      "answer": "ちょくし",
      "meaning": "imperial envoy, imperial messenger"
    },
    {
      "question": "田楽",
      "answer": "でんがく",
      "meaning": "ritual music and dancing in shrines and temples, rice dance, rice festival, tofu (or fish, etc.) bak"
    },
    {
      "question": "交叉",
      "answer": "こうさ",
      "meaning": "crossing, intersection, (genetic) crossing over"
    },
    {
      "question": "社宅",
      "answer": "しゃたく",
      "meaning": "company housing, housing provided by one's company"
    },
    {
      "question": "痛撃",
      "answer": "つうげき",
      "meaning": "severe attack, hard blow"
    },
    {
      "question": "王将",
      "answer": "おうしょう",
      "meaning": "king (of the senior player)"
    },
    {
      "question": "槍先",
      "answer": "やりさき",
      "meaning": "spearhead"
    },
    {
      "question": "誹謗",
      "answer": "ひぼう",
      "meaning": "slander, abuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷上",
      "answer": "ひょうじょう",
      "meaning": "on ice"
    },
    {
      "question": "水域",
      "answer": "すいいき",
      "meaning": "waters, water area"
    },
    {
      "question": "万民",
      "answer": "ばんみん",
      "meaning": "all people, the whole nation"
    },
    {
      "question": "円運動",
      "answer": "えんうんどう",
      "meaning": "circular motion"
    },
    {
      "question": "散逸",
      "answer": "さんいつ",
      "meaning": "being scattered and ultimately lost, dissipation"
    },
    {
      "question": "反骨",
      "answer": "はんこつ",
      "meaning": "rebellious spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "昨年度",
      "answer": "さくねんど",
      "meaning": "previous year (fiscal, academic, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "理想主義",
      "answer": "りそうしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "idealism"
    },
    {
      "question": "労働時間",
      "answer": "ろうどうじかん",
      "meaning": "working hours, man-hours"
    },
    {
      "question": "粉砂糖",
      "answer": "こなざとう",
      "meaning": "powdered sugar"
    },
    {
      "question": "少食",
      "answer": "しょうしょく",
      "meaning": "light eating, spare diet, not eating much"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗食",
      "answer": "そしょく,そじき",
      "meaning": "simple diet, plain food, simple food, frugal meal"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒死病",
      "answer": "こくしびょう",
      "meaning": "plague, Black Death"
    },
    {
      "question": "阿片",
      "answer": "あへん",
      "meaning": "opium"
    },
    {
      "question": "艦上",
      "answer": "かんじょう",
      "meaning": "aboard a warship"
    },
    {
      "question": "精兵",
      "answer": "せいびょう,せいへい",
      "meaning": "picked troops, elite soldiers, crack troops"
    },
    {
      "question": "変種",
      "answer": "へんしゅ",
      "meaning": "variant, variation, variety, mutation, freak, novelty, exception, (taxonomical) variety"
    },
    {
      "question": "科学捜査",
      "answer": "かがくそうさ",
      "meaning": "scientific crime detection, forensic investigation"
    },
    {
      "question": "免",
      "answer": "めん",
      "meaning": "dismissal, discharge"
    },
    {
      "question": "倒立",
      "answer": "とうりつ",
      "meaning": "handstand"
    },
    {
      "question": "上下動",
      "answer": "じょうげどう",
      "meaning": "vertical motion (in earthquakes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "共同墓地",
      "answer": "きょうどうぼち",
      "meaning": "public cemetery"
    },
    {
      "question": "性病",
      "answer": "せいびょう",
      "meaning": "venereal disease, sexually transmitted infection, sexually transmitted disease, VD, STI, STD"
    },
    {
      "question": "遍",
      "answer": "へん",
      "meaning": "number of times"
    },
    {
      "question": "酸鼻",
      "answer": "さんび",
      "meaning": "appalling, awful, extreme pain, deep sorrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "占星術",
      "answer": "せんせいじゅつ",
      "meaning": "astrology"
    },
    {
      "question": "文化財",
      "answer": "ぶんかざい",
      "meaning": "cultural assets, cultural property"
    },
    {
      "question": "照覧",
      "answer": "しょうらん",
      "meaning": "seeing clearly"
    },
    {
      "question": "開校",
      "answer": "かいこう",
      "meaning": "opening a school"
    },
    {
      "question": "早口言葉",
      "answer": "はやくちことば",
      "meaning": "tongue twister"
    },
    {
      "question": "空気感染",
      "answer": "くうきかんせん",
      "meaning": "airborne infection"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び降り",
      "answer": "とびおり",
      "meaning": "jumping off"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳幼児",
      "answer": "にゅうようじ",
      "meaning": "infants, babies and very young children"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘蛾灯",
      "answer": "ゆうがとう",
      "meaning": "light trap (for killing insects)"
    },
    {
      "question": "茉莉花",
      "answer": "まつりか",
      "meaning": "Arabian jasmine (Jasminum sambac)"
    },
    {
      "question": "十三階段",
      "answer": "じゅうさんかいだん",
      "meaning": "gallows"
    },
    {
      "question": "本間",
      "answer": "ほんま,ほんけん",
      "meaning": "truth, reality, official size of a tatami mat for measuring room size (esp. a Kyoto-size tatami mat)"
    },
    {
      "question": "近傍",
      "answer": "きんぼう",
      "meaning": "neighborhood, neighbourhood, vicinity, surrounding area"
    },
    {
      "question": "重力波",
      "answer": "じゅうりょくは",
      "meaning": "gravitational wave, gravity wave"
    },
    {
      "question": "注連縄",
      "answer": "しめなわ",
      "meaning": "rope used to cordon off consecrated areas or as a talisman against evil"
    },
    {
      "question": "食い縛る",
      "answer": "くいしばる",
      "meaning": "to set one's teeth, to clench one's teeth, to grit one's teeth"
    },
    {
      "question": "首切り",
      "answer": "くびきり",
      "meaning": "decapitation, beheading, firings, dismissals, layoffs, downsizing, small samurai sword used for deca"
    },
    {
      "question": "屍肉",
      "answer": "しにく",
      "meaning": "dead flesh, carrion"
    },
    {
      "question": "私生児",
      "answer": "しせいじ",
      "meaning": "illegitimate child, bastard, love child"
    },
    {
      "question": "三つ星",
      "answer": "みつぼし",
      "meaning": "three stars (shape), three stars (for quality, e.g. Michelin stars), Orion's belt, Chinese 'Three St"
    },
    {
      "question": "検品",
      "answer": "けんぴん",
      "meaning": "inspection, checking (goods, products)"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰巣本能",
      "answer": "きそうほんのう",
      "meaning": "homing instinct"
    },
    {
      "question": "腐り",
      "answer": "くさり",
      "meaning": "rottenness, decay, corruption"
    },
    {
      "question": "偏重",
      "answer": "へんちょう,へんじゅう",
      "meaning": "attaching too much importance to, placing disproportionate emphasis on, making too much of"
    },
    {
      "question": "高利貸し",
      "answer": "こうりがし,こうりかし",
      "meaning": "usurer, usury, loansharking"
    },
    {
      "question": "解脱",
      "answer": "げだつ",
      "meaning": "liberation from earthly desires and the woes of man, deliverance of one's soul, moksha, mukti, vimuk"
    },
    {
      "question": "積極",
      "answer": "せっきょく,しゃっきょく",
      "meaning": "active, positive, progressive"
    },
    {
      "question": "床に就く",
      "answer": "とこにつく",
      "meaning": "to go to bed, to be sick in bed, to be laid up"
    },
    {
      "question": "懐古",
      "answer": "かいこ",
      "meaning": "reminiscence, nostalgia, thinking fondly of the past, recalling the old days"
    },
    {
      "question": "叩き殺す",
      "answer": "たたきころす",
      "meaning": "to beat to death"
    },
    {
      "question": "再来月",
      "answer": "さらいげつ",
      "meaning": "month after next"
    },
    {
      "question": "意中の人",
      "answer": "いちゅうのひと",
      "meaning": "sweetheart, person in one's thoughts (heart)"
    },
    {
      "question": "成年",
      "answer": "せいねん",
      "meaning": "adult age, majority"
    },
    {
      "question": "群像",
      "answer": "ぐんぞう",
      "meaning": "lively group (usu. young people), dynamic bunch, group (art)"
    },
    {
      "question": "練成",
      "answer": "れんせい",
      "meaning": "training, drilling"
    },
    {
      "question": "綺羅星",
      "answer": "きらぼし",
      "meaning": "glittering stars"
    },
    {
      "question": "此の",
      "answer": "この",
      "meaning": "this, last (couple of years, etc.), these, past, you (as in 'you liar')"
    },
    {
      "question": "後脚",
      "answer": "あとあし,こうきゃく",
      "meaning": "hind legs, rear legs"
    },
    {
      "question": "社屋",
      "answer": "しゃおく",
      "meaning": "company office building"
    },
    {
      "question": "ライ麦",
      "answer": "ライむぎ",
      "meaning": "rye (Secale cereale)"
    },
    {
      "question": "事物",
      "answer": "じぶつ",
      "meaning": "things, affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺失物",
      "answer": "いしつぶつ",
      "meaning": "lost article, lost property"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄せ書き",
      "answer": "よせがき",
      "meaning": "write jointly, collection of autographs"
    },
    {
      "question": "貫頭衣",
      "answer": "かんとうい",
      "meaning": "simple type of clothing consisting of a large piece of cloth with a hole in the middle for the head"
    },
    {
      "question": "ビル街",
      "answer": "ビルがい",
      "meaning": "downtown high-rise area, street of office buildings, area of medium to tall business buildings"
    },
    {
      "question": "最北",
      "answer": "さいほく",
      "meaning": "northernmost"
    },
    {
      "question": "凝結",
      "answer": "ぎょうけつ",
      "meaning": "coagulation, freezing, solidification, curdling, setting, congealing"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪崩れる",
      "answer": "なだれる",
      "meaning": "to slope, to descend, to slide (snow, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "委任状",
      "answer": "いにんじょう",
      "meaning": "commission, proxy, power of attorney, authorization"
    },
    {
      "question": "敗軍",
      "answer": "はいぐん",
      "meaning": "defeat, lost battle, defeated army"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗鬱",
      "answer": "あんうつ",
      "meaning": "gloom, melancholy"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆ナン",
      "answer": "ぎゃくナン",
      "meaning": "women picking up men"
    },
    {
      "question": "就業",
      "answer": "しゅうぎょう",
      "meaning": "employment, starting work"
    },
    {
      "question": "怖気付く",
      "answer": "おじけづく,おじけつく",
      "meaning": "to be seized with fear, to be intimidated, to lose one's nerve, to be frightened, to get cold feet,"
    },
    {
      "question": "画一的",
      "answer": "かくいつてき",
      "meaning": "uniform, standard"
    },
    {
      "question": "結び付き",
      "answer": "むすびつき",
      "meaning": "connection, relation"
    },
    {
      "question": "油分",
      "answer": "ゆぶん",
      "meaning": "oil content"
    },
    {
      "question": "交通網",
      "answer": "こうつうもう",
      "meaning": "transportation network, transport network, traffic network"
    },
    {
      "question": "大負け",
      "answer": "おおまけ",
      "meaning": "major loss, crushing defeat, big discount"
    },
    {
      "question": "目分量",
      "answer": "めぶんりょう",
      "meaning": "measuring by eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "追い出し",
      "answer": "おいだし",
      "meaning": "expulsion, dismissal, ejection, eviction, drum beat at the end of a day's performance (in the theatr"
    },
    {
      "question": "花鳥風月",
      "answer": "かちょうふうげつ",
      "meaning": "beauties of nature, the traditional themes of natural beauty in Japanese aesthetics, artistic pursui"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄鎖",
      "answer": "てっさ",
      "meaning": "iron chain"
    },
    {
      "question": "情況",
      "answer": "じょうきょう",
      "meaning": "state of affairs (around you), situation, circumstances"
    },
    {
      "question": "国歌",
      "answer": "こっか",
      "meaning": "national anthem"
    },
    {
      "question": "鍾乳石",
      "answer": "しょうにゅうせき",
      "meaning": "stalactite"
    },
    {
      "question": "算盤",
      "answer": "そろばん",
      "meaning": "abacus"
    },
    {
      "question": "祭具",
      "answer": "さいぐ",
      "meaning": "equipment used in a ritual, ritual implement"
    },
    {
      "question": "遮音",
      "answer": "しゃおん",
      "meaning": "soundproofing, sound insulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "映写機",
      "answer": "えいしゃき",
      "meaning": "movie projector, film projector, cine projector"
    },
    {
      "question": "撓む",
      "answer": "たわむ",
      "meaning": "to bend, to warp, to lose heart"
    },
    {
      "question": "西日本",
      "answer": "にしにほん,にしにっぽん",
      "meaning": "western Japan, Japan west of the Itoigawa-Shizuoka Tectonic Line, i.e. the Chūbu region and westward"
    },
    {
      "question": "叙事詩",
      "answer": "じょじし",
      "meaning": "descriptive poetry, epic poem"
    },
    {
      "question": "灰汁",
      "answer": "あく",
      "meaning": "lye, harsh taste, bitter taste, alkaline taste, astringency, scum (on a soup, broth etc.), (excessiv"
    },
    {
      "question": "衒い",
      "answer": "てらい",
      "meaning": "affectation, pretension"
    },
    {
      "question": "出生率",
      "answer": "しゅっしょうりつ,しゅっせいりつ",
      "meaning": "birth rate"
    },
    {
      "question": "商取引",
      "answer": "しょうとりひき",
      "meaning": "business transaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "地金",
      "answer": "じがね,じきん",
      "meaning": "ore, unprocessed metal, ground metal, (one's) true character"
    },
    {
      "question": "全国区",
      "answer": "ぜんこくく",
      "meaning": "national constituency"
    },
    {
      "question": "繰り言",
      "answer": "くりごと",
      "meaning": "tedious talk, repetition, complaint, tongue-twister"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒浸り",
      "answer": "さけびたり,さかびたり",
      "meaning": "liquor-soaked, continuous drinking, daily drinking, binge drinking"
    },
    {
      "question": "保護色",
      "answer": "ほごしょく",
      "meaning": "protective coloration, protective colouration, camouflage"
    },
    {
      "question": "論拠",
      "answer": "ろんきょ",
      "meaning": "grounds of an argument"
    },
    {
      "question": "捜索願い",
      "answer": "そうさくねがい",
      "meaning": "request for a police search, application to the police to search for a missing person"
    },
    {
      "question": "跳び回る",
      "answer": "とびまわる",
      "meaning": "to fly about, to skip about, to bustle about"
    },
    {
      "question": "脚線美",
      "answer": "きゃくせんび",
      "meaning": "beauty of slender female legs"
    },
    {
      "question": "除け者",
      "answer": "のけもの",
      "meaning": "outcast, odd man out, pariah"
    },
    {
      "question": "発色",
      "answer": "はっしょく",
      "meaning": "coloring, colouring, colour development, production of colour"
    },
    {
      "question": "生産的",
      "answer": "せいさんてき",
      "meaning": "productive, constructive, meaningful"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳴き真似",
      "answer": "なきまね",
      "meaning": "mimicking a bird or animal call, imitating a call or a sound"
    },
    {
      "question": "気の無い",
      "answer": "きのない",
      "meaning": "indifferent, half-hearted, dispirited, listless"
    },
    {
      "question": "天地神明",
      "answer": "てんちしんめい",
      "meaning": "the gods of heaven and earth"
    },
    {
      "question": "宵の口",
      "answer": "よいのくち",
      "meaning": "nightfall, early evening"
    },
    {
      "question": "下ろし",
      "answer": "おろし",
      "meaning": "dropping, unloading, removing, grated vegetables, fruit, etc., grater, using new tools (or clothes,"
    },
    {
      "question": "物入り",
      "answer": "ものいり",
      "meaning": "expenses, costly, expensive"
    },
    {
      "question": "分け隔て",
      "answer": "わけへだて",
      "meaning": "distinction, favoritism, favouritism, discrimination"
    },
    {
      "question": "元老",
      "answer": "げんろう",
      "meaning": "elder statesman, doyen, old-timer, authority, Genro (member of a pre-WWII body that informally advis"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠山",
      "answer": "えんざん,とおやま",
      "meaning": "distant mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "原告",
      "answer": "げんこく",
      "meaning": "plaintiff, accuser, prosecutor"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑穀",
      "answer": "ざっこく",
      "meaning": "assorted grains, cereals, millet"
    },
    {
      "question": "鰯",
      "answer": "いわし",
      "meaning": "pilchard (esp. Japanese pilchard, Sardinops melanostictus), sardine"
    },
    {
      "question": "濃緑",
      "answer": "こみどり,のうりょく",
      "meaning": "dark green, deep green"
    },
    {
      "question": "水産",
      "answer": "すいさん",
      "meaning": "aquatic products, fisheries"
    },
    {
      "question": "先述",
      "answer": "せんじゅつ",
      "meaning": "aforementioned, above-mentioned"
    },
    {
      "question": "女難",
      "answer": "じょなん",
      "meaning": "trouble with women"
    },
    {
      "question": "量感",
      "answer": "りょうかん",
      "meaning": "voluminous, massive, bulky"
    },
    {
      "question": "振幅",
      "answer": "しんぷく,ふりはば",
      "meaning": "amplitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨具",
      "answer": "あまぐ",
      "meaning": "rain gear"
    },
    {
      "question": "理数",
      "answer": "りすう",
      "meaning": "science and mathematics"
    },
    {
      "question": "洗濯板",
      "answer": "せんたくいた",
      "meaning": "washboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "日射病",
      "answer": "にっしゃびょう",
      "meaning": "heatstroke, sunstroke"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯煎",
      "answer": "ゆせん",
      "meaning": "warming (something) in a vessel placed in hot water"
    },
    {
      "question": "上澄み",
      "answer": "うわずみ",
      "meaning": "clear layer of fluid (at the top of a mixture), supernatant liquid, supernate"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄弱",
      "answer": "はくじゃく",
      "meaning": "feebleness, weakness, weak"
    },
    {
      "question": "悲運",
      "answer": "ひうん",
      "meaning": "sad fate, tragic doom, ill fate"
    },
    {
      "question": "昼日中",
      "answer": "ひるひなか",
      "meaning": "daytime, noon, broad daylight"
    },
    {
      "question": "商売女",
      "answer": "しょうばいおんな",
      "meaning": "woman working in the nightlife business (bar or nightclub hostess, geisha, etc.), woman who works in"
    },
    {
      "question": "表面積",
      "answer": "ひょうめんせき",
      "meaning": "surface area"
    },
    {
      "question": "冴え冴え",
      "answer": "さえざえ",
      "meaning": "clearly, brightly, crisply"
    },
    {
      "question": "片道切符",
      "answer": "かたみちきっぷ",
      "meaning": "one-way ticket"
    },
    {
      "question": "今際の際",
      "answer": "いまわのきわ",
      "meaning": "verge of death, dying moments"
    },
    {
      "question": "黙礼",
      "answer": "もくれい",
      "meaning": "silent bow"
    },
    {
      "question": "進駐軍",
      "answer": "しんちゅうぐん",
      "meaning": "occupying forces (esp. of the Allies in Japan after World War II)"
    },
    {
      "question": "神体",
      "answer": "しんたい",
      "meaning": "shintai, object of worship believed to contain the spirit of a deity, typically housed in a shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "或る",
      "answer": "ある",
      "meaning": "a certain ..., some ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "猿人",
      "answer": "えんじん",
      "meaning": "ape man"
    },
    {
      "question": "写真機",
      "answer": "しゃしんき",
      "meaning": "(photographic) camera"
    },
    {
      "question": "孫子",
      "answer": "まごこ,そんし",
      "meaning": "children and grandchildren, posterity, descendants, Sun Tzu (Chinese military strategist, 544?-496 B"
    },
    {
      "question": "列島",
      "answer": "れっとう",
      "meaning": "archipelago, chain of islands"
    },
    {
      "question": "身形",
      "answer": "みなり",
      "meaning": "dress, attire, clothing, getup, outfit, personal appearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "特選",
      "answer": "とくせん",
      "meaning": "special selection, special approval, special prize, highest honours"
    },
    {
      "question": "加圧",
      "answer": "かあつ",
      "meaning": "increasing pressure"
    },
    {
      "question": "金物",
      "answer": "かなもの",
      "meaning": "metal utensil, ironware, metal fittings, hardware"
    },
    {
      "question": "一遍に",
      "answer": "いっぺんに",
      "meaning": "(all) at once, at the same time, in one go, in one sitting, right away, in an instant"
    },
    {
      "question": "油性",
      "answer": "ゆせい",
      "meaning": "oil-based"
    },
    {
      "question": "経口",
      "answer": "けいこう",
      "meaning": "taken by mouth, oral"
    },
    {
      "question": "芸達者",
      "answer": "げいだっしゃ,げいたっしゃ",
      "meaning": "versatile entertainer, all-round performer, person skilled in their craft"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽天家",
      "answer": "らくてんか",
      "meaning": "optimist, easy-going person"
    },
    {
      "question": "実生活",
      "answer": "じっせいかつ",
      "meaning": "real life, actual life, everyday life"
    },
    {
      "question": "月足らず",
      "answer": "つきたらず",
      "meaning": "premature birth"
    },
    {
      "question": "間道",
      "answer": "かんどう",
      "meaning": "side road, shortcut"
    },
    {
      "question": "御札",
      "answer": "おさつ,おふだ",
      "meaning": "bill, note (currency), type of household amulet or talisman, issued by a Shinto shrine, hung in the"
    },
    {
      "question": "穿孔",
      "answer": "せんこう",
      "meaning": "perforation, punching, boring, drilling"
    },
    {
      "question": "武家屋敷",
      "answer": "ぶけやしき",
      "meaning": "samurai residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "曳航",
      "answer": "えいこう",
      "meaning": "towing (a ship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "ママ友",
      "answer": "ママとも",
      "meaning": "friend of a mother who is also a mother, mothers who are friends"
    },
    {
      "question": "衿",
      "answer": "えり",
      "meaning": "collar, lapel, neckband, neck, nape of the neck, scruff of the neck"
    },
    {
      "question": "一所",
      "answer": "いっしょ,ひとところ",
      "meaning": "one place, the same place, one person, together"
    },
    {
      "question": "果断",
      "answer": "かだん",
      "meaning": "decisive, resolute, drastic"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄泉の国",
      "answer": "よみのくに",
      "meaning": "hades, realm of the dead, the next world"
    },
    {
      "question": "交響曲",
      "answer": "こうきょうきょく",
      "meaning": "symphony"
    },
    {
      "question": "躍り込む",
      "answer": "おどりこむ",
      "meaning": "to jump into, to rush into"
    },
    {
      "question": "師走",
      "answer": "しわす,しはす",
      "meaning": "twelfth month (esp. of the lunar calendar), December"
    },
    {
      "question": "天鵞絨",
      "answer": "びろうど,てんがじゅう",
      "meaning": "velvet"
    },
    {
      "question": "糖尿病",
      "answer": "とうにょうびょう",
      "meaning": "diabetes, diabetes mellitus"
    },
    {
      "question": "故い",
      "answer": "ふるい",
      "meaning": "old, aged, ancient, antiquated, antique, timeworn, long, since long ago, time-honored, of the distan"
    },
    {
      "question": "厘",
      "answer": "りん,り",
      "meaning": "one-hundredth, 0.3 mm (one-hundredth of a sun), 0.1 percent (one-hundredth of a wari), 0.0375 grams"
    },
    {
      "question": "図工",
      "answer": "ずこう",
      "meaning": "drawing and manual arts (school subject)"
    },
    {
      "question": "化学変化",
      "answer": "かがくへんか",
      "meaning": "chemical change"
    },
    {
      "question": "是非是非",
      "answer": "ぜひぜひ",
      "meaning": "certainly, by all means"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳聡い",
      "answer": "みみざとい",
      "meaning": "sharp-eared, have sharp ears, picks things up fast"
    },
    {
      "question": "働き盛り",
      "answer": "はたらきざかり",
      "meaning": "prime of one's working life"
    },
    {
      "question": "个",
      "answer": "か",
      "meaning": "counter for the ichi-ni-san counting system (usu. directly preceding the item being counted), a noun"
    },
    {
      "question": "早耳",
      "answer": "はやみみ",
      "meaning": "insider, keen of hearing, quick-eared, sharp-eared"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋歌",
      "answer": "こいうた,れんか,こいか",
      "meaning": "love song, love poem"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵図面",
      "answer": "えずめん",
      "meaning": "a plan"
    },
    {
      "question": "殿達",
      "answer": "とのたち",
      "meaning": "the nobility, visitors"
    },
    {
      "question": "球団",
      "answer": "きゅうだん",
      "meaning": "baseball team"
    },
    {
      "question": "手続",
      "answer": "てつづき",
      "meaning": "procedure, process, proceedings, formalities"
    },
    {
      "question": "接舷",
      "answer": "せつげん",
      "meaning": "coming alongside (a boat, pier, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "石工",
      "answer": "いしく,せっこう",
      "meaning": "mason, stonemason"
    },
    {
      "question": "私立探偵",
      "answer": "しりつたんてい",
      "meaning": "private detective"
    },
    {
      "question": "博覧会",
      "answer": "はくらんかい",
      "meaning": "fair, exhibition, exposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "昔日",
      "answer": "せきじつ",
      "meaning": "old days"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗降",
      "answer": "じょうこう",
      "meaning": "getting on and off, embarking and disembarking"
    },
    {
      "question": "巡業",
      "answer": "じゅんぎょう",
      "meaning": "provincial tour"
    },
    {
      "question": "胡麻",
      "answer": "ごま",
      "meaning": "sesame seeds, sesame (Sesamum indicum)"
    },
    {
      "question": "青緑",
      "answer": "あおみどろ,あおみどり",
      "meaning": "spirogyra, algae forming pond scum, blue-green, turquoise, aqua"
    },
    {
      "question": "殊に",
      "answer": "ことに",
      "meaning": "especially, particularly, unusually, above all, additionally"
    },
    {
      "question": "玄米",
      "answer": "げんまい,くろごめ",
      "meaning": "unpolished rice, unmilled rice, brown rice, black rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "送り狼",
      "answer": "おくりおおかみ",
      "meaning": "'gentleman' who escorts a woman home, only to make a pass at her"
    },
    {
      "question": "石造",
      "answer": "せきぞう",
      "meaning": "stone-built"
    },
    {
      "question": "情報機関",
      "answer": "じょうほうきかん",
      "meaning": "intelligence agency"
    },
    {
      "question": "筑前煮",
      "answer": "ちくぜんに",
      "meaning": "chikuzenni, simmered chicken and vegetables, chicken stew with taro, carrot, burdock, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "再発見",
      "answer": "さいはっけん",
      "meaning": "rediscovery"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣り出す",
      "answer": "つりだす",
      "meaning": "to pull out a fish, to lure"
    },
    {
      "question": "空位",
      "answer": "くうい",
      "meaning": "vacant post, vacancy, post in name only"
    },
    {
      "question": "犬畜生",
      "answer": "いぬちくしょう",
      "meaning": "mangy cur, low animal, beast"
    },
    {
      "question": "良案",
      "answer": "りょうあん",
      "meaning": "good idea, good plan"
    },
    {
      "question": "劇物",
      "answer": "げきぶつ",
      "meaning": "deleterious substance, toxic substance"
    },
    {
      "question": "店仕舞い",
      "answer": "みせじまい",
      "meaning": "closing up shop (for the day), stopping business, going out of business"
    },
    {
      "question": "主菜",
      "answer": "しゅさい",
      "meaning": "main dish (e.g. meat, fish, but not rice), principal dish"
    },
    {
      "question": "観光資源",
      "answer": "かんこうしげん",
      "meaning": "tourist attractions"
    },
    {
      "question": "形振り",
      "answer": "なりふり",
      "meaning": "one's appearance, clothing, costume, dress"
    },
    {
      "question": "浴する",
      "answer": "よくする",
      "meaning": "to bathe, to receive (an honor, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "疑似体験",
      "answer": "ぎじたいけん",
      "meaning": "simulated experience, simulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "八面六臂",
      "answer": "はちめんろっぴ",
      "meaning": "competent in all fields, jack of all trades, very active in many fields, versatile, all-round, 8 fac"
    },
    {
      "question": "即効",
      "answer": "そっこう",
      "meaning": "immediate effect, instant effect"
    },
    {
      "question": "良策",
      "answer": "りょうさく",
      "meaning": "good plan or policy"
    },
    {
      "question": "伊予",
      "answer": "いよ",
      "meaning": "Iyo (former province located in present-day Ehime Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "調剤",
      "answer": "ちょうざい",
      "meaning": "making up a prescription, dispensing medicine, preparing medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "除草剤",
      "answer": "じょそうざい",
      "meaning": "herbicide"
    },
    {
      "question": "加速器",
      "answer": "かそくき",
      "meaning": "(particle) accelerator"
    },
    {
      "question": "天王",
      "answer": "てんのう",
      "meaning": "heavenly king, Gozu Tenno (deity said to be the Indian god Gavagriva)"
    },
    {
      "question": "塁",
      "answer": "とりで,るい",
      "meaning": "fort, fortress, stronghold, fortification, base, bag, sack"
    },
    {
      "question": "思惟",
      "answer": "しい,しゆい",
      "meaning": "thought, thinking, contemplation, consideration, using wisdom to get to the bottom of things, focusi"
    },
    {
      "question": "延滞",
      "answer": "えんたい",
      "meaning": "arrears, (being) overdue, delay (e.g. in payment), procrastination"
    },
    {
      "question": "制帽",
      "answer": "せいぼう",
      "meaning": "regulation cap, school cap"
    },
    {
      "question": "工員",
      "answer": "こういん",
      "meaning": "factory worker"
    },
    {
      "question": "百人一首",
      "answer": "ひゃくにんいっしゅ",
      "meaning": "(Ogura) Hyakunin Isshu, classical Japanese anthology of one hundred Japanese waka by one hundred poe"
    },
    {
      "question": "沈思",
      "answer": "ちんし",
      "meaning": "contemplation, meditation"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒蜜",
      "answer": "くろみつ",
      "meaning": "brown sugar syrup"
    },
    {
      "question": "懲戒",
      "answer": "ちょうかい",
      "meaning": "discipline, punishment, reprimand"
    },
    {
      "question": "多層",
      "answer": "たそう",
      "meaning": "multilayer"
    },
    {
      "question": "酌む",
      "answer": "くむ",
      "meaning": "to pour (sake), to serve, to drink together"
    },
    {
      "question": "溶き卵",
      "answer": "ときたまご",
      "meaning": "beaten egg, eggwash"
    },
    {
      "question": "小鍋",
      "answer": "こなべ",
      "meaning": "small saucepan, small pot"
    },
    {
      "question": "煎る",
      "answer": "いる",
      "meaning": "to roast, to parch, to toast, to boil down"
    },
    {
      "question": "近眼",
      "answer": "きんがん,ちかめ",
      "meaning": "nearsightedness, shortsightedness, myopia"
    },
    {
      "question": "客観",
      "answer": "きゃっかん,かっかん,かくかん",
      "meaning": "objectivity, objective, object (philosophical)"
    },
    {
      "question": "載っける",
      "answer": "のっける",
      "meaning": "to place on (something), to give (someone) a ride, to give a lift, to pick up, to help on board"
    },
    {
      "question": "分乗",
      "answer": "ぶんじょう",
      "meaning": "riding separately"
    },
    {
      "question": "諸行無常",
      "answer": "しょぎょうむじょう",
      "meaning": "all things must pass, all worldly things are impermanent"
    },
    {
      "question": "物的",
      "answer": "ぶってき",
      "meaning": "material, physical"
    },
    {
      "question": "涙を誘う",
      "answer": "なみだをさそう",
      "meaning": "to move to tears, to draw tears, to evoke tears"
    },
    {
      "question": "深化",
      "answer": "しんか",
      "meaning": "deepening"
    },
    {
      "question": "邑",
      "answer": "おおざと,おおざる",
      "meaning": "kanji 'large village' radical at right (radical 163)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄扇",
      "answer": "てっせん",
      "meaning": "iron-ribbed fan"
    },
    {
      "question": "勅",
      "answer": "みことのり,ちょく",
      "meaning": "imperial decree, imperial edict"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳許",
      "answer": "みみもと",
      "meaning": "close to the ear"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋刀魚",
      "answer": "さんま",
      "meaning": "Pacific saury (Cololabis saira), mackerel pike"
    },
    {
      "question": "錆色",
      "answer": "さびいろ",
      "meaning": "rust (colour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "承",
      "answer": "しょう",
      "meaning": "second line of a four-line Chinese poem"
    },
    {
      "question": "庭仕事",
      "answer": "にわしごと",
      "meaning": "gardening"
    },
    {
      "question": "零細",
      "answer": "れいさい",
      "meaning": "insignificant, trifling, paltry, cottage (industry), tiny (company)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大瓶",
      "answer": "おおびん",
      "meaning": "large bottle"
    },
    {
      "question": "銅製",
      "answer": "どうせい",
      "meaning": "made of copper"
    },
    {
      "question": "迷い子",
      "answer": "まよいご",
      "meaning": "lost child, stray child"
    },
    {
      "question": "毎分",
      "answer": "まいふん",
      "meaning": "every minute, per minute"
    },
    {
      "question": "地質",
      "answer": "ちしつ,じしつ",
      "meaning": "geological features, quality of a fabric or cloth, texture of a fabric"
    },
    {
      "question": "周回遅れ",
      "answer": "しゅうかいおくれ",
      "meaning": "being one or more laps behind (in a race), being behind the times"
    },
    {
      "question": "芽吹き",
      "answer": "めぶき",
      "meaning": "bud, sprout, shoot, opening of a bud"
    },
    {
      "question": "南向き",
      "answer": "みなみむき",
      "meaning": "facing south, southern exposure"
    },
    {
      "question": "多難",
      "answer": "たなん",
      "meaning": "full of troubles, difficulties"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り殺す",
      "answer": "きりころす",
      "meaning": "to kill with a sword (knife, dagger, etc.), to slay, to put to the sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "早弁",
      "answer": "はやべん",
      "meaning": "eating one's lunch box before lunchtime (e.g. of a student)"
    },
    {
      "question": "舟を漕ぐ",
      "answer": "ふねをこぐ",
      "meaning": "to row a boat, to nod off, to doze off"
    },
    {
      "question": "勧善懲悪",
      "answer": "かんぜんちょうあく",
      "meaning": "rewarding good and punishing evil, novel or drama with a rewarding-good-and-punishing-evil theme, mo"
    },
    {
      "question": "所帯",
      "answer": "しょたい",
      "meaning": "household, home, family, housekeeping"
    },
    {
      "question": "清涼剤",
      "answer": "せいりょうざい",
      "meaning": "refreshment, something refreshing, welcome relief, breath of fresh air, tonic, refreshing medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "弓張",
      "answer": "ゆみはり",
      "meaning": "stringing a bow, person who strings bows, crescent moon, paper lantern with a bow-shaped handle"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒海",
      "answer": "こっかい",
      "meaning": "Black Sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "烏丸",
      "answer": "うがん",
      "meaning": "Wuhuan (proto-Mongolic nomadic people)"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺言書",
      "answer": "ゆいごんしょ,いごんしょ",
      "meaning": "will, testament"
    },
    {
      "question": "一等星",
      "answer": "いっとうせい",
      "meaning": "first magnitude star"
    },
    {
      "question": "竹箒",
      "answer": "たけぼうき,たかぼうき",
      "meaning": "bamboo broom"
    },
    {
      "question": "混ぜ物",
      "answer": "まぜもの",
      "meaning": "mixture, adulteration"
    },
    {
      "question": "健常者",
      "answer": "けんじょうしゃ",
      "meaning": "person with no physical or mental disability, able-bodied person"
    },
    {
      "question": "車寄せ",
      "answer": "くるまよせ",
      "meaning": "carriage porch, entranceway, porte cochere"
    },
    {
      "question": "主命",
      "answer": "しゅめい",
      "meaning": "ruler's orders, master's orders"
    },
    {
      "question": "怯懦",
      "answer": "きょうだ",
      "meaning": "cowardice"
    },
    {
      "question": "可燃性",
      "answer": "かねんせい",
      "meaning": "combustibility, inflammability, combustible, inflammable"
    },
    {
      "question": "本年",
      "answer": "ほんねん",
      "meaning": "this (current) year"
    },
    {
      "question": "漆塗り",
      "answer": "うるしぬり",
      "meaning": "lacquering, lacquer ware"
    },
    {
      "question": "取次ぎ",
      "answer": "とりつぎ",
      "meaning": "agency, commission, distributor, intermediation, reception (of guests), conveyance (of messages)"
    },
    {
      "question": "交う",
      "answer": "かう",
      "meaning": "to take turns, to mingle together"
    },
    {
      "question": "悔し紛れ",
      "answer": "くやしまぎれ",
      "meaning": "spite, frustration, vexation"
    },
    {
      "question": "据え置く",
      "answer": "すえおく",
      "meaning": "to leave as it is, to defer"
    },
    {
      "question": "初音",
      "answer": "はつね",
      "meaning": "first warbling heard in a New Year"
    },
    {
      "question": "送辞",
      "answer": "そうじ",
      "meaning": "farewell address"
    },
    {
      "question": "電機",
      "answer": "でんき",
      "meaning": "electrical machinery, appliances"
    },
    {
      "question": "荷電粒子",
      "answer": "かでんりゅうし",
      "meaning": "charged particle"
    },
    {
      "question": "口吻",
      "answer": "こうふん",
      "meaning": "way of speaking, intimation, lips, mouth, snout, proboscis"
    },
    {
      "question": "路面電車",
      "answer": "ろめんでんしゃ",
      "meaning": "tram, streetcar, trolley, tramcar"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶漬け",
      "answer": "ちゃづけ",
      "meaning": "chazuke, cooked rice with green tea poured on it"
    },
    {
      "question": "滅却",
      "answer": "めっきゃく",
      "meaning": "extinguishment, destruction, effacement"
    },
    {
      "question": "西南",
      "answer": "せいなん,にしみなみ",
      "meaning": "south-west"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭骨",
      "answer": "とうこつ,かしらぼね,ずこつ",
      "meaning": "skull"
    },
    {
      "question": "若夫婦",
      "answer": "わかふうふ",
      "meaning": "young couple"
    },
    {
      "question": "輸出入",
      "answer": "ゆしゅつにゅう",
      "meaning": "export and import"
    },
    {
      "question": "裸踊り",
      "answer": "はだかおどり",
      "meaning": "naked dance, dancing naked, striptease, strip show"
    },
    {
      "question": "染め直す",
      "answer": "そめなおす",
      "meaning": "to dye again"
    },
    {
      "question": "営利",
      "answer": "えいり",
      "meaning": "money-making, commercialized, commercialised"
    },
    {
      "question": "命の水",
      "answer": "いのちのみず",
      "meaning": "water of life, life-giving water, distilled liquor (brandy, whisky, etc.), spirits, semen"
    },
    {
      "question": "実刑",
      "answer": "じっけい",
      "meaning": "prison sentence (without a stay of execution)"
    },
    {
      "question": "生ビール",
      "answer": "なまビール",
      "meaning": "unpasteurized beer, draft beer, draught beer"
    },
    {
      "question": "空き箱",
      "answer": "あきばこ",
      "meaning": "empty box"
    },
    {
      "question": "洩れ",
      "answer": "もれ",
      "meaning": "leakage, omission, oversight, I, me"
    },
    {
      "question": "神兵",
      "answer": "しんぺい",
      "meaning": "soldier dispatched by a god, soldier under the protection of the gods"
    },
    {
      "question": "高松",
      "answer": "たかまつ",
      "meaning": "Takamatsu (city in Kagawa)"
    },
    {
      "question": "日蝕",
      "answer": "にっしょく",
      "meaning": "solar eclipse"
    },
    {
      "question": "岐",
      "answer": "ちまた",
      "meaning": "the public, the street (e.g. 'word on the street'), street, district, quarters, location (e.g. of a"
    },
    {
      "question": "然様",
      "answer": "さよう",
      "meaning": "so, like that, that's right, indeed, let me see..."
    },
    {
      "question": "三軍",
      "answer": "さんぐん",
      "meaning": "great army, mighty host, whole army"
    },
    {
      "question": "艦尾",
      "answer": "かんび",
      "meaning": "stern (of a warship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲府",
      "answer": "こうふ",
      "meaning": "Kōfu (city in Yamanashi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大川",
      "answer": "おおかわ,たいせん",
      "meaning": "big river"
    },
    {
      "question": "月収",
      "answer": "げっしゅう",
      "meaning": "monthly income"
    },
    {
      "question": "営業所",
      "answer": "えいぎょうしょ",
      "meaning": "business office, place of business"
    },
    {
      "question": "通信簿",
      "answer": "つうしんぼ",
      "meaning": "report card"
    },
    {
      "question": "巻紙",
      "answer": "まきがみ",
      "meaning": "rolled letter paper, roll of paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "飼い葉",
      "answer": "かいば",
      "meaning": "fodder"
    },
    {
      "question": "描画",
      "answer": "びょうが",
      "meaning": "drawing, painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "中州",
      "answer": "なかす",
      "meaning": "sandbank (in a river), sandbar"
    },
    {
      "question": "信州",
      "answer": "しんしゅう",
      "meaning": "Shinshū (alt. name of former Shinano province)"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り花",
      "answer": "きりばな",
      "meaning": "cut flowers"
    },
    {
      "question": "番茶",
      "answer": "ばんちゃ",
      "meaning": "coarse tea"
    },
    {
      "question": "貧乏神",
      "answer": "びんぼうがみ",
      "meaning": "god of poverty"
    },
    {
      "question": "成型",
      "answer": "せいけい",
      "meaning": "cast, mold, mould, casting, molding, moulding, compacting (e.g. in metallurgy), forming, shaping, fa"
    },
    {
      "question": "弔問",
      "answer": "ちょうもん",
      "meaning": "condolence call"
    },
    {
      "question": "迫り出す",
      "answer": "せりだす",
      "meaning": "to push (a thing) out, to jut out (can have a negative nuance), to protrude, to rise out the trap do"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍事費",
      "answer": "ぐんじひ",
      "meaning": "war funds, war expenditures, military spending"
    },
    {
      "question": "経営学",
      "answer": "けいえいがく",
      "meaning": "management studies, business administration (study of)"
    },
    {
      "question": "脆弱性",
      "answer": "ぜいじゃくせい",
      "meaning": "vulnerability, weakness, fragility"
    },
    {
      "question": "副音声",
      "answer": "ふくおんせい",
      "meaning": "second (supplementary) sound channel"
    },
    {
      "question": "小児",
      "answer": "しょうに,しょうじ",
      "meaning": "young child, infant"
    },
    {
      "question": "国難",
      "answer": "こくなん",
      "meaning": "national crisis, national disaster"
    },
    {
      "question": "断熱",
      "answer": "だんねつ",
      "meaning": "insulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "博士号",
      "answer": "はかせごう,はくしごう",
      "meaning": "doctor's degree, doctorate, PhD"
    },
    {
      "question": "思い遣る",
      "answer": "おもいやる",
      "meaning": "to be considerate, to sympathize with, to sympathise with"
    },
    {
      "question": "倍額",
      "answer": "ばいがく",
      "meaning": "double amount"
    },
    {
      "question": "虫がつく",
      "answer": "むしがつく",
      "meaning": "to become verminous, to be infested with insects, to begin to keep bad company, to have an (unfavora"
    },
    {
      "question": "特価",
      "answer": "とっか",
      "meaning": "special price, bargain price"
    },
    {
      "question": "贅沢三昧",
      "answer": "ぜいたくざんまい",
      "meaning": "indulging in every possible luxury"
    },
    {
      "question": "蘇芳",
      "answer": "すおう",
      "meaning": "sappanwood (Caesalpinia sappan), sappanwood dye (red in colour), layered colour (light brown on the"
    },
    {
      "question": "白狐",
      "answer": "しろぎつね,びゃっこ",
      "meaning": "albino fox, white (spiritual) fox"
    },
    {
      "question": "変成",
      "answer": "へんせい",
      "meaning": "metamorphosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "御膳",
      "answer": "ごぜん",
      "meaning": "meal, Emperor's meal, meal of a noble, high-quality (of a food or drink), premium"
    },
    {
      "question": "地の文",
      "answer": "じのぶん",
      "meaning": "descriptive (narrative) part"
    },
    {
      "question": "宝島",
      "answer": "たからじま",
      "meaning": "treasure island"
    },
    {
      "question": "極点",
      "answer": "きょくてん",
      "meaning": "pole (north, south), climax, extreme (point)"
    },
    {
      "question": "協奏曲",
      "answer": "きょうそうきょく",
      "meaning": "concerto"
    },
    {
      "question": "霧消",
      "answer": "むしょう",
      "meaning": "vanishing like mist"
    },
    {
      "question": "戯画",
      "answer": "ぎが",
      "meaning": "caricature, cartoon, comics"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬糞",
      "answer": "ばふん,まぐそ",
      "meaning": "horse dung"
    },
    {
      "question": "打合せ",
      "answer": "うちあわせ",
      "meaning": "advance arrangements, preparatory meeting, briefing session, overlap (of a coat, etc.), making somet"
    },
    {
      "question": "降す",
      "answer": "くだす",
      "meaning": "to make a decision, to draw a conclusion, to give a judgement, to hand down a verdict, to pass a sen"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠視",
      "answer": "えんし",
      "meaning": "farsightedness, far-sightedness, hyperopia, hypermetropia, long-sightedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "所縁",
      "answer": "ゆかり,しょえん",
      "meaning": "connection (to a person, place, etc.), relation, affinity"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈴虫",
      "answer": "すずむし",
      "meaning": "bell cricket (Meloimorpha japonicus), pine cricket (Xenogryllus marmoratus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "日の丸",
      "answer": "ひのまる",
      "meaning": "outline of the Sun (esp. represented as a red circle), the Japanese flag"
    },
    {
      "question": "予告編",
      "answer": "よこくへん",
      "meaning": "trailer (film, TV), preview"
    },
    {
      "question": "縁切り",
      "answer": "えんきり",
      "meaning": "separation, divorce, severing of connections"
    },
    {
      "question": "特長",
      "answer": "とくちょう",
      "meaning": "forte, merit"
    },
    {
      "question": "着座",
      "answer": "ちゃくざ",
      "meaning": "taking a seat"
    },
    {
      "question": "活火山",
      "answer": "かっかざん,かつかざん",
      "meaning": "active volcano"
    },
    {
      "question": "日曜大工",
      "answer": "にちようだいく",
      "meaning": "weekend carpenter, do-it-yourselfer"
    },
    {
      "question": "前口上",
      "answer": "まえこうじょう",
      "meaning": "introductory remarks"
    },
    {
      "question": "自立心",
      "answer": "じりつしん",
      "meaning": "spirit of self-reliance, feeling of independence"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹を下す",
      "answer": "はらをくだす",
      "meaning": "to have diarrhea"
    },
    {
      "question": "居住まい",
      "answer": "いずまい",
      "meaning": "(one's) seated posture"
    },
    {
      "question": "曹",
      "answer": "そう",
      "meaning": "palace room for government officials, fellow, set (of people), clan, family"
    },
    {
      "question": "雷獣",
      "answer": "らいじゅう",
      "meaning": "(in Chinese mythology) beast which descends from the sky with a thunderbolt"
    },
    {
      "question": "利根",
      "answer": "りこん",
      "meaning": "intelligence, cleverness, innate aptitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "経済圏",
      "answer": "けいざいけん",
      "meaning": "economic bloc"
    },
    {
      "question": "甚平",
      "answer": "じんべい",
      "meaning": "informal summer clothes for men (short jacket and trousers)"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄宿",
      "answer": "きしゅく",
      "meaning": "lodging, boarding, boarding house, school dormitory"
    },
    {
      "question": "掠",
      "answer": "りゃく",
      "meaning": "sixth principle of the Eight Principles of Yong, tapering thinning curve, usually concave left"
    },
    {
      "question": "宮司",
      "answer": "ぐうじ",
      "meaning": "chief priest"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍司令部",
      "answer": "ぐんしれいぶ",
      "meaning": "military headquarters"
    },
    {
      "question": "空ろ",
      "answer": "うつろ",
      "meaning": "cavity, hollow, void, hollow (voice, smile, etc.), blank (eyes, look, etc.), vacant (expression, sta"
    },
    {
      "question": "迫撃砲",
      "answer": "はくげきほう",
      "meaning": "mortar"
    },
    {
      "question": "怖じる",
      "answer": "おじる",
      "meaning": "to be scared"
    },
    {
      "question": "隔意",
      "answer": "かくい",
      "meaning": "reserve, reticence, unfriendliness, estrangement"
    },
    {
      "question": "予備役",
      "answer": "よびえき",
      "meaning": "service in the first reserve"
    },
    {
      "question": "今尚",
      "answer": "いまなお",
      "meaning": "still, even now"
    },
    {
      "question": "公衆便所",
      "answer": "こうしゅうべんじょ",
      "meaning": "public lavatory, slut, whore, floozy, tramp, trollop"
    },
    {
      "question": "大車輪",
      "answer": "だいしゃりん",
      "meaning": "(gymnastical) giant swing, all-out effort, frenzied activity"
    },
    {
      "question": "遅番",
      "answer": "おそばん",
      "meaning": "late shift, second shift, afternoon shift"
    },
    {
      "question": "援交",
      "answer": "えんこう",
      "meaning": "paid dating (esp. with an underage girl; oft. involving selling of sex), compensated dating"
    },
    {
      "question": "斉",
      "answer": "せい",
      "meaning": "Qi (kingdom in China during the Spring and Autumn Period and the Period of the Warring States), Ch'i"
    },
    {
      "question": "参集",
      "answer": "さんしゅう",
      "meaning": "assembling (of people)"
    },
    {
      "question": "非合理",
      "answer": "ひごうり",
      "meaning": "illogicality"
    },
    {
      "question": "勾留",
      "answer": "こうりゅう",
      "meaning": "detention pending trial, confinement, custody"
    },
    {
      "question": "矢尻",
      "answer": "やじり",
      "meaning": "arrowhead"
    },
    {
      "question": "流刑",
      "answer": "りゅうけい,るけい",
      "meaning": "exile, banishment, deportation"
    },
    {
      "question": "名馬",
      "answer": "めいば",
      "meaning": "fine horse, famous horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "手解き",
      "answer": "てほどき",
      "meaning": "teaching the basics, initiation, introduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "試験場",
      "answer": "しけんじょう",
      "meaning": "examination hall, examination room, laboratory, experimental station, testing ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "スポ根",
      "answer": "スポこん",
      "meaning": "fighting spirit (in sport), tenacity"
    },
    {
      "question": "賭す",
      "answer": "とす",
      "meaning": "to stake, to risk, to bet, to wager"
    },
    {
      "question": "策定",
      "answer": "さくてい",
      "meaning": "formulation (of a plan, policy, etc.), decision, settling on"
    },
    {
      "question": "内向き",
      "answer": "うちむき",
      "meaning": "facing inward"
    },
    {
      "question": "肩先",
      "answer": "かたさき",
      "meaning": "(top of) shoulder"
    },
    {
      "question": "対症療法",
      "answer": "たいしょうりょうほう",
      "meaning": "symptomatic therapy, makeshift solution"
    },
    {
      "question": "手取り",
      "answer": "てどり,てとり",
      "meaning": "after tax income, net income, talented wrestler, good at manipulating (others), crafty person"
    },
    {
      "question": "刑事事件",
      "answer": "けいじじけん",
      "meaning": "criminal case"
    },
    {
      "question": "危険思想",
      "answer": "きけんしそう",
      "meaning": "dangerous thoughts"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦節",
      "answer": "くせつ",
      "meaning": "unremitting effort, dogged perseverance, unswerving loyalty"
    },
    {
      "question": "目の敵",
      "answer": "めのかたき",
      "meaning": "enemy"
    },
    {
      "question": "大奥",
      "answer": "おおおく",
      "meaning": "inner palace (in Edo Castle), palace's ladies chambers, shogun's harem"
    },
    {
      "question": "与太",
      "answer": "よた",
      "meaning": "idle talk, nonsense, rubbish, humbug, fool, idiot, good-for-nothing fellow, irresponsible, nonsensic"
    },
    {
      "question": "歓楽",
      "answer": "かんらく",
      "meaning": "pleasure, merriment"
    },
    {
      "question": "閻魔大王",
      "answer": "えんまだいおう",
      "meaning": "Yama, judge of the afterlife"
    },
    {
      "question": "本山",
      "answer": "ほんざん",
      "meaning": "head temple, this temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "何時しか",
      "answer": "いつしか",
      "meaning": "before one knows, unnoticed, unawares"
    },
    {
      "question": "巻頭",
      "answer": "かんとう",
      "meaning": "beginning (of a book, magazine, etc.), opening page, beginning (of a matter), start"
    },
    {
      "question": "国賊",
      "answer": "こくぞく",
      "meaning": "traitor, rebel"
    },
    {
      "question": "冗句",
      "answer": "じょうく",
      "meaning": "redundant phrase, joke"
    },
    {
      "question": "外線",
      "answer": "がいせん",
      "meaning": "outside telephone line, outer circle"
    },
    {
      "question": "要害",
      "answer": "ようがい",
      "meaning": "stronghold, fortress, strategic position, key position"
    },
    {
      "question": "非行",
      "answer": "ひこう",
      "meaning": "delinquency, misconduct"
    },
    {
      "question": "皮膚感覚",
      "answer": "ひふかんかく",
      "meaning": "cutaneous sensation"
    },
    {
      "question": "傘立て",
      "answer": "かさたて",
      "meaning": "umbrella stand"
    },
    {
      "question": "売国奴",
      "answer": "ばいこくど",
      "meaning": "traitor (to one's country), quisling"
    },
    {
      "question": "無菌",
      "answer": "むきん",
      "meaning": "sterilised, sterilized, sterile, pasteurised, pasteurized, germ-free, aseptic"
    },
    {
      "question": "多弁",
      "answer": "たべん",
      "meaning": "talkativeness, loquacity, garrulousness, volubility, polypetalous, multivalve"
    },
    {
      "question": "手洗い場",
      "answer": "てあらいば",
      "meaning": "area for washing one's hands and face, washroom, bathroom, toilet"
    },
    {
      "question": "急落",
      "answer": "きゅうらく",
      "meaning": "sudden fall, sharp fall, sudden drop, sharp drop"
    },
    {
      "question": "登竜門",
      "answer": "とうりゅうもん",
      "meaning": "gateway to success, opening to honours, opening to honors"
    },
    {
      "question": "痩せ型",
      "answer": "やせがた",
      "meaning": "slender build, slender figure, leptosome, leptosomatic habit, waifish, leptosomaic, leptosomatic, ec"
    },
    {
      "question": "穏健",
      "answer": "おんけん",
      "meaning": "quiet, dependable, uniform, (politically) moderate"
    },
    {
      "question": "虎猫",
      "answer": "とらねこ",
      "meaning": "tabby cat, tiger cat, striped cat"
    },
    {
      "question": "原木",
      "answer": "げんぼく",
      "meaning": "pulpwood, raw timber, unprocessed timber, logs, original (or ancestor) of a tree cultivar"
    },
    {
      "question": "松茸",
      "answer": "まつたけ,まったけ",
      "meaning": "matsutake mushroom (Tricholoma matsutake)"
    },
    {
      "question": "蓄音機",
      "answer": "ちくおんき",
      "meaning": "gramophone, phonograph"
    },
    {
      "question": "監督官",
      "answer": "かんとくかん",
      "meaning": "inspector"
    },
    {
      "question": "被災者",
      "answer": "ひさいしゃ",
      "meaning": "victim of (a disaster)"
    },
    {
      "question": "変数",
      "answer": "へんすう",
      "meaning": "variable"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑煮",
      "answer": "ぞうに",
      "meaning": "soup containing rice cakes and vegetables (New Year's dish)"
    },
    {
      "question": "舅",
      "answer": "しゅうと,しうと,しいと",
      "meaning": "father-in-law"
    },
    {
      "question": "内奥",
      "answer": "ないおう",
      "meaning": "inner part, depths"
    },
    {
      "question": "ガチ勢",
      "answer": "ガチぜい",
      "meaning": "hardcore crowd, people who take their hobby or interest very seriously"
    },
    {
      "question": "改訂",
      "answer": "かいてい",
      "meaning": "revision (of text), alteration, change"
    },
    {
      "question": "七味",
      "answer": "しちみ",
      "meaning": "seven delicious flavors (flavours), blend of seven spices (cayenne, sesame, Japanese pepper, citrus"
    },
    {
      "question": "突然死",
      "answer": "とつぜんし",
      "meaning": "sudden death"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛犬",
      "answer": "もうけん",
      "meaning": "savage dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "川向こう",
      "answer": "かわむこう",
      "meaning": "the other side of a river, the other side of the tracks, place where lower class people live"
    },
    {
      "question": "植樹",
      "answer": "しょくじゅ",
      "meaning": "tree-planting"
    },
    {
      "question": "国体",
      "answer": "こくたい",
      "meaning": "national polity, National Athletic Meet"
    },
    {
      "question": "石投げ",
      "answer": "いしなげ",
      "meaning": "throwing stones, slingshot, sling"
    },
    {
      "question": "識者",
      "answer": "しきしゃ",
      "meaning": "well-informed person, thinking person, intelligent person"
    },
    {
      "question": "古強者",
      "answer": "ふるつわもの",
      "meaning": "old soldier, veteran, old hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "回遊",
      "answer": "かいゆう",
      "meaning": "excursion, round trip, seasonal migration (of fish, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "地価",
      "answer": "ちか",
      "meaning": "the price of land"
    },
    {
      "question": "一揃い",
      "answer": "ひとそろい",
      "meaning": "a set, a suit"
    },
    {
      "question": "放免",
      "answer": "ほうめん,ほうべん",
      "meaning": "release (from custody), discharge, liberation, setting free, letting go, letting off, acquittal"
    },
    {
      "question": "生活様式",
      "answer": "せいかつようしき",
      "meaning": "one's lifestyle"
    },
    {
      "question": "略奪愛",
      "answer": "りゃくだつあい",
      "meaning": "stealing another's romantic partner"
    },
    {
      "question": "本決まり",
      "answer": "ほんぎまり",
      "meaning": "definite decision, final decision"
    },
    {
      "question": "遭わす",
      "answer": "あわす",
      "meaning": "to make (someone) to meet, to let (someone) meet, to expose to, to subject to"
    },
    {
      "question": "増幅器",
      "answer": "ぞうふくき",
      "meaning": "amplifier"
    },
    {
      "question": "充溢",
      "answer": "じゅういつ",
      "meaning": "overflow, abundance, exuberance"
    },
    {
      "question": "真珠色",
      "answer": "しんじゅいろ",
      "meaning": "pearl gray, pearl grey"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵糧攻め",
      "answer": "ひょうろうぜめ",
      "meaning": "starvation tactics"
    },
    {
      "question": "肩当て",
      "answer": "かたあて",
      "meaning": "shoulder pad, shoulder reinforcement, epaulet, cloak worn in bed"
    },
    {
      "question": "鍋料理",
      "answer": "なべりょうり",
      "meaning": "hot pot cooking"
    },
    {
      "question": "課税",
      "answer": "かぜい",
      "meaning": "taxation"
    },
    {
      "question": "落日",
      "answer": "らくじつ",
      "meaning": "setting sun"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛装",
      "answer": "せいそう",
      "meaning": "dressing up in fine clothes, splendid clothes, one's best clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "漏斗",
      "answer": "じょうご,ろうと",
      "meaning": "funnel"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋭気",
      "answer": "えいき",
      "meaning": "courage, ardour, high spirits"
    },
    {
      "question": "沈下",
      "answer": "ちんか",
      "meaning": "sinking, subsidence"
    },
    {
      "question": "心因",
      "answer": "しんいん",
      "meaning": "psychogenesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "契る",
      "answer": "ちぎる",
      "meaning": "to pledge, to vow, to promise, to swear, to have sexual intercourse (esp. between husband and wife),"
    },
    {
      "question": "色情",
      "answer": "しきじょう",
      "meaning": "sexual passion, lust"
    },
    {
      "question": "心肺停止",
      "answer": "しんぱいていし",
      "meaning": "cardiopulmonary arrest, showing no vital signs"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕儀",
      "answer": "しぎ",
      "meaning": "situation, developments, outcome"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び地",
      "answer": "とびち",
      "meaning": "detached territory, enclave, exclave, scattered landholdings"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾性",
      "answer": "だんせい",
      "meaning": "elasticity"
    },
    {
      "question": "手縫い",
      "answer": "てぬい",
      "meaning": "hand-tailored, hand-sewn"
    },
    {
      "question": "減俸",
      "answer": "げんぽう",
      "meaning": "salary reduction, salary cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "表彰状",
      "answer": "ひょうしょうじょう",
      "meaning": "testimonial, certificate of commendation"
    },
    {
      "question": "誌面",
      "answer": "しめん",
      "meaning": "page of a magazine"
    },
    {
      "question": "司法取引",
      "answer": "しほうとりひき",
      "meaning": "plea bargaining"
    },
    {
      "question": "製造元",
      "answer": "せいぞうもと",
      "meaning": "manufacturer, maker"
    },
    {
      "question": "最高値",
      "answer": "さいたかね",
      "meaning": "all-time high (price, in trading), record high, new high"
    },
    {
      "question": "老眼",
      "answer": "ろうがん",
      "meaning": "presbyopia, age-related longsightedness, farsightedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪む",
      "answer": "にくむ",
      "meaning": "to hate, to detest"
    },
    {
      "question": "金持",
      "answer": "かねもち",
      "meaning": "rich person"
    },
    {
      "question": "白い物",
      "answer": "しろいもの",
      "meaning": "something white, snow, gray hair, grey hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "不正確",
      "answer": "ふせいかく",
      "meaning": "uncertainty, inaccuracy, incorrectness"
    },
    {
      "question": "高血圧",
      "answer": "こうけつあつ",
      "meaning": "high blood pressure, hypertension"
    },
    {
      "question": "多岐",
      "answer": "たき",
      "meaning": "digression, many divergences"
    },
    {
      "question": "着装",
      "answer": "ちゃくそう",
      "meaning": "putting on, fixing"
    },
    {
      "question": "烏帽子",
      "answer": "えぼし",
      "meaning": "eboshi, black-lacquered headgear (made of silk, cloth or paper) originally worn by court nobles in a"
    },
    {
      "question": "難波",
      "answer": "なにわ",
      "meaning": "Naniwa (former name for Osaka region)"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍機",
      "answer": "ぐんき",
      "meaning": "military secret, classified military material"
    },
    {
      "question": "書生",
      "answer": "しょせい",
      "meaning": "student, student who performs housework in exchange for meals and lodging, houseboy (attending schoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "獅子舞",
      "answer": "ししまい",
      "meaning": "lion dance, traditional dance performed by one or more dancers wearing a guardian lion costume"
    },
    {
      "question": "帝王切開",
      "answer": "ていおうせっかい",
      "meaning": "Caesarean section (Cesarean), C-section"
    },
    {
      "question": "模擬試験",
      "answer": "もぎしけん",
      "meaning": "mock exam, practice exam, practice test"
    },
    {
      "question": "保護観察",
      "answer": "ほごかんさつ",
      "meaning": "probation"
    },
    {
      "question": "忽ち",
      "answer": "たちまち",
      "meaning": "in an instant, in a moment, immediately, right away, at once, suddenly, all of a sudden, all at once"
    },
    {
      "question": "講",
      "answer": "こう",
      "meaning": "(Buddhist) lecture meeting, religious association, mutual assistance association (i.e. for financial"
    },
    {
      "question": "石組み",
      "answer": "いしぐみ",
      "meaning": "arrangement of stones in a garden"
    },
    {
      "question": "連む",
      "answer": "つるむ",
      "meaning": "to go with (a companion), to hang out with, to do together"
    },
    {
      "question": "洋式",
      "answer": "ようしき",
      "meaning": "Western-style, foreign, Western-style toilet, flush toilet, water closet"
    },
    {
      "question": "参画",
      "answer": "さんかく",
      "meaning": "taking part (in planning), participation"
    },
    {
      "question": "楊枝",
      "answer": "ようじ",
      "meaning": "toothpick, skewer for eating moist wagashi (steel, bamboo, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "午睡",
      "answer": "ごすい",
      "meaning": "nap, siesta"
    },
    {
      "question": "否決",
      "answer": "ひけつ",
      "meaning": "rejection, negation, voting down"
    },
    {
      "question": "異母兄弟",
      "answer": "いぼきょうだい",
      "meaning": "half-sibling (with a different mother)"
    },
    {
      "question": "油圧",
      "answer": "ゆあつ",
      "meaning": "oil pressure, hydraulics"
    },
    {
      "question": "山深い",
      "answer": "やまぶかい",
      "meaning": "situated deep in the mountains"
    },
    {
      "question": "ずる休み",
      "answer": "ずるやすみ",
      "meaning": "skipping school or work without a good reason, playing truant, playing hooky"
    },
    {
      "question": "失業者",
      "answer": "しつぎょうしゃ",
      "meaning": "unemployed person"
    },
    {
      "question": "市井の人",
      "answer": "しせいのひと",
      "meaning": "townspeople"
    },
    {
      "question": "風合い",
      "answer": "ふうあい",
      "meaning": "texture (cloth, fabric, paper), feel, appearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "期限付き",
      "answer": "きげんつき",
      "meaning": "with a fixed time, with a deadline"
    },
    {
      "question": "崑崙",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "朧月",
      "answer": "おぼろづき",
      "meaning": "hazy moon (esp. on a spring night)"
    },
    {
      "question": "上甲板",
      "answer": "じょうかんぱん",
      "meaning": "upper deck"
    },
    {
      "question": "脳裡",
      "answer": "のうり",
      "meaning": "one's mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "山鳥",
      "answer": "やまどり,さんちょう",
      "meaning": "copper pheasant (Syrmaticus soemmerringii), mountain bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "要塞都市",
      "answer": "ようさいとし",
      "meaning": "fortified city, bastide"
    },
    {
      "question": "防人",
      "answer": "さきもり,ぼうじん",
      "meaning": "soldiers garrisoned at strategic posts in Kyushu in ancient times, Chinese soldiers stationed to pro"
    },
    {
      "question": "醍醐",
      "answer": "だいご",
      "meaning": "ghee (held to be the greatest of all flavours), the ultimate truth of Buddhism, nirvana"
    },
    {
      "question": "代返",
      "answer": "だいへん",
      "meaning": "answer a roll call for another"
    },
    {
      "question": "作務衣",
      "answer": "さむえ,さむい",
      "meaning": "samue, monk's working clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "柿の種",
      "answer": "かきのたね",
      "meaning": "kaki (Japanese persimmon) seed, spicy baked or fried mochi chips in this shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "手押し",
      "answer": "ておし",
      "meaning": "pushing by hand, hand gilding"
    },
    {
      "question": "偏向",
      "answer": "へんこう",
      "meaning": "propensity, tendency, inclination, deflection"
    },
    {
      "question": "専業",
      "answer": "せんぎょう",
      "meaning": "special occupation, principal occupation, specialty, monopoly"
    },
    {
      "question": "端金",
      "answer": "はしたがね",
      "meaning": "paltry sum of money, small change, odd money, pittance, chicken feed"
    },
    {
      "question": "金一封",
      "answer": "きんいっぷう",
      "meaning": "gift of money (contained in an envelope), money reward (for services rendered)"
    },
    {
      "question": "支配的",
      "answer": "しはいてき",
      "meaning": "dominant, ruling"
    },
    {
      "question": "先々月",
      "answer": "せんせんげつ",
      "meaning": "month before last"
    },
    {
      "question": "入れ歯",
      "answer": "いれば",
      "meaning": "false tooth, denture"
    },
    {
      "question": "芸風",
      "answer": "げいふう",
      "meaning": "style of acting"
    },
    {
      "question": "防水布",
      "answer": "ぼうすいふ",
      "meaning": "waterproof cloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "矢弾",
      "answer": "やだま",
      "meaning": "ammunition, arrows and bullets, missile, projectile"
    },
    {
      "question": "大奥様",
      "answer": "おおおくさま",
      "meaning": "lady of the house"
    },
    {
      "question": "青年団",
      "answer": "せいねんだん",
      "meaning": "young persons' association"
    },
    {
      "question": "大叔母",
      "answer": "おおおば",
      "meaning": "grandaunt, great-aunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "駱駝",
      "answer": "らくだ",
      "meaning": "camel, camel (cloth), cloth made from camel hair, camel (color), light yellowish brown"
    },
    {
      "question": "西国",
      "answer": "さいごく,さいこく",
      "meaning": "the western part of Japan (esp. Kyushu, but ranging as far east as Kinki), western nations (esp. Ind"
    },
    {
      "question": "試薬",
      "answer": "しやく",
      "meaning": "reagent"
    },
    {
      "question": "残影",
      "answer": "ざんえい",
      "meaning": "traces, remnants"
    },
    {
      "question": "天晴",
      "answer": "あっぱれ",
      "meaning": "splendid, praiseworthy, admirable, brilliant, well done!, bravo!"
    },
    {
      "question": "精神病",
      "answer": "せいしんびょう",
      "meaning": "mental illness, psychosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "底光り",
      "answer": "そこびかり",
      "meaning": "inner glow or light, deep gloss or luster (lustre)"
    },
    {
      "question": "利益率",
      "answer": "りえきりつ",
      "meaning": "profit ratio"
    },
    {
      "question": "三叉路",
      "answer": "さんさろ",
      "meaning": "three-forked road, junction of three roads"
    },
    {
      "question": "常在戦場",
      "answer": "じょうざいせんじょう",
      "meaning": "always conducting oneself as though one were on a battlefield, being combat ready at all times (of a"
    },
    {
      "question": "人頭",
      "answer": "じんとう,にんとう,ひとがしら",
      "meaning": "number of people, population, human head, skull, cranium, kanji 'person' radical at top"
    },
    {
      "question": "半紙",
      "answer": "はんし",
      "meaning": "Japanese calligraphy paper (approx. 25cm by 35cm)"
    },
    {
      "question": "広範",
      "answer": "こうはん",
      "meaning": "wide, extensive, comprehensive, far-reaching, widespread"
    },
    {
      "question": "伸す",
      "answer": "のす",
      "meaning": "to stretch, to extend, to lengthen, to spread, to gain influence, to become stronger, to increase (e"
    },
    {
      "question": "自画像",
      "answer": "じがぞう",
      "meaning": "self-portrait"
    },
    {
      "question": "穴ぼこ",
      "answer": "あなぼこ",
      "meaning": "hole, hollow, pothole (road, pavement, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "百獣の王",
      "answer": "ひゃくじゅうのおう",
      "meaning": "king of beasts (i.e. lion)"
    },
    {
      "question": "意気軒昂",
      "answer": "いきけんこう",
      "meaning": "in high spirits, elated"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊興",
      "answer": "ゆうきょう",
      "meaning": "merrymaking (esp. wine and women), pleasures"
    },
    {
      "question": "間仕切り",
      "answer": "まじきり",
      "meaning": "partition between two rooms, room divider, partition wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "今季",
      "answer": "こんき",
      "meaning": "this season"
    },
    {
      "question": "木組み",
      "answer": "きぐみ",
      "meaning": "wooden framework"
    },
    {
      "question": "笑い種",
      "answer": "わらいぐさ",
      "meaning": "laughingstock"
    },
    {
      "question": "割り引く",
      "answer": "わりびく",
      "meaning": "to discount"
    },
    {
      "question": "恵みの雨",
      "answer": "めぐみのあめ",
      "meaning": "welcome rain, merciful rain, blessed rain, rain after a long dry period"
    },
    {
      "question": "記紀",
      "answer": "きき",
      "meaning": "the Kojiki and Nihon-shoki"
    },
    {
      "question": "猩々",
      "answer": "しょうじょう",
      "meaning": "orangutan, heavy drinker"
    },
    {
      "question": "西風",
      "answer": "にしかぜ,せいふう",
      "meaning": "west wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍兵",
      "answer": "ぐんぴょう,ぐんぺい,ぐんびょう",
      "meaning": "armed forces, battle troops"
    },
    {
      "question": "修羅道",
      "answer": "しゅらどう",
      "meaning": "Asura realm, scene of carnage"
    },
    {
      "question": "母船",
      "answer": "ぼせん",
      "meaning": "depot ship, mother ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "宮内",
      "answer": "くない",
      "meaning": "inside the Imperial Palace, Department of the Imperial Household"
    },
    {
      "question": "箱馬車",
      "answer": "はこばしゃ",
      "meaning": "box-shaped (horse-drawn) carriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊学",
      "answer": "ゆうがく",
      "meaning": "studying abroad, travelling to study, traveling to study"
    },
    {
      "question": "克己",
      "answer": "こっき",
      "meaning": "self denial, self control"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛礫",
      "answer": "つぶて",
      "meaning": "stone (used for throwing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "志士",
      "answer": "しし",
      "meaning": "imperial loyalist samurai of the Bakumatsu-era, patriots, idealists willing to sacrifice themselves"
    },
    {
      "question": "轟然",
      "answer": "ごうぜん",
      "meaning": "roaring"
    },
    {
      "question": "浄い",
      "answer": "きよい",
      "meaning": "clear, pure, noble"
    },
    {
      "question": "中卒",
      "answer": "ちゅうそつ",
      "meaning": "junior high school graduate, middle school graduate"
    },
    {
      "question": "生き霊",
      "answer": "いきりょう,いきすだま",
      "meaning": "vengeful spirit (spawned from a person's hate), doppelgänger, co-walker, wraith"
    },
    {
      "question": "頤",
      "answer": "あご,おとがい",
      "meaning": "jaw, chin, barb (of a fishhook), (lower) jaw, chatterbox"
    },
    {
      "question": "長ズボン",
      "answer": "ながズボン",
      "meaning": "long (i.e. full-length) pants (as opposed to shorts)"
    },
    {
      "question": "中華鍋",
      "answer": "ちゅうかなべ",
      "meaning": "wok, Chinese frying pan"
    },
    {
      "question": "収奪",
      "answer": "しゅうだつ",
      "meaning": "plundering, exploitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "変哲",
      "answer": "へんてつ",
      "meaning": "something unusual, something odd, something out of the ordinary"
    },
    {
      "question": "玉突き",
      "answer": "たまつき",
      "meaning": "billiards, pool, serial collisions (of cars)"
    },
    {
      "question": "生皮",
      "answer": "なまかわ",
      "meaning": "rawhide"
    },
    {
      "question": "無駄飯",
      "answer": "むだめし",
      "meaning": "living idly"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒乱",
      "answer": "しゅらん",
      "meaning": "drunken frenzy, drunken violence, person who is prone to violence when drunk"
    },
    {
      "question": "先細り",
      "answer": "さきぼそり",
      "meaning": "dwindling, declining, diminishing, tapering off, tapering (to a point)"
    },
    {
      "question": "左回り",
      "answer": "ひだりまわり",
      "meaning": "counterclockwise rotation, anti-clockwise rotation, CCW"
    },
    {
      "question": "二頭立て",
      "answer": "にとうだて",
      "meaning": "two-horse cart"
    },
    {
      "question": "博学",
      "answer": "はくがく",
      "meaning": "erudition, extensive learning"
    },
    {
      "question": "一工夫",
      "answer": "ひとくふう",
      "meaning": "contrivance, bit of fiddling, little ingenuity, bit more (e.g. food)"
    },
    {
      "question": "祭殿",
      "answer": "さいでん",
      "meaning": "shrine, sanctuary"
    },
    {
      "question": "真帆",
      "answer": "まほ",
      "meaning": "spread-out sail, full sail, (sailing) downwind"
    },
    {
      "question": "上長",
      "answer": "じょうちょう",
      "meaning": "one's superior, senior, elder"
    },
    {
      "question": "无",
      "answer": "む",
      "meaning": "nothing, naught, nought, nil, zero, un-, non-"
    },
    {
      "question": "張り付け",
      "answer": "はりつけ",
      "meaning": "affixing, pasting, sticking"
    },
    {
      "question": "宝冠",
      "answer": "ほうかん",
      "meaning": "diadem, jeweled crown"
    },
    {
      "question": "人力車",
      "answer": "じんりきしゃ",
      "meaning": "rickshaw, jinrikisha"
    },
    {
      "question": "気狂い",
      "answer": "きちがい",
      "meaning": "madness, madman, enthusiast, freak, junkie"
    },
    {
      "question": "拘禁",
      "answer": "こうきん",
      "meaning": "detention, custody, confinement, internment"
    },
    {
      "question": "合理",
      "answer": "ごうり",
      "meaning": "rationality"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍籍",
      "answer": "ぐんせき",
      "meaning": "military or naval register, muster roll"
    },
    {
      "question": "動静",
      "answer": "どうせい",
      "meaning": "state (of affairs), condition, developments, movements"
    },
    {
      "question": "被災",
      "answer": "ひさい",
      "meaning": "being a victim of (some disaster), suffering from"
    },
    {
      "question": "生母",
      "answer": "せいぼ",
      "meaning": "one's real mother"
    },
    {
      "question": "箍",
      "answer": "たが",
      "meaning": "hoop (of a barrel, bucket, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "精神病院",
      "answer": "せいしんびょういん",
      "meaning": "mental hospital"
    },
    {
      "question": "酪農",
      "answer": "らくのう",
      "meaning": "dairy farming"
    },
    {
      "question": "神経細胞",
      "answer": "しんけいさいぼう",
      "meaning": "nerve cell, neuron"
    },
    {
      "question": "煩",
      "answer": "はん",
      "meaning": "trouble"
    },
    {
      "question": "覚え書き",
      "answer": "おぼえがき",
      "meaning": "memo, memorandum, note, (diplomatic) memorandum"
    },
    {
      "question": "寡兵",
      "answer": "かへい",
      "meaning": "small army force"
    },
    {
      "question": "情報公開",
      "answer": "じょうほうこうかい",
      "meaning": "freedom of information, access to information, disclosure of information (e.g. by the government)"
    },
    {
      "question": "争点",
      "answer": "そうてん",
      "meaning": "point at issue"
    },
    {
      "question": "只事",
      "answer": "ただごと",
      "meaning": "trivial matter"
    },
    {
      "question": "勤続",
      "answer": "きんぞく",
      "meaning": "continuous service"
    },
    {
      "question": "前科者",
      "answer": "ぜんかしゃ,ぜんかもの",
      "meaning": "former convict, old offender, ex-convict, person with a criminal record"
    },
    {
      "question": "前奏",
      "answer": "ぜんそう",
      "meaning": "prelude, overture"
    },
    {
      "question": "四捨五入",
      "answer": "ししゃごにゅう",
      "meaning": "rounding (fractions), rounding half up"
    },
    {
      "question": "丑三つ時",
      "answer": "うしみつどき",
      "meaning": "dead of night, middle of the night, midnight, third quarter of the hour of the ox (2-2:30am, or 3-3:"
    },
    {
      "question": "急転直下",
      "answer": "きゅうてんちょっか",
      "meaning": "suddenly and precipitately, take a sudden turn"
    },
    {
      "question": "幡",
      "answer": "はた,ばん",
      "meaning": "flag, pataka (banner), banner (administrative division of Inner Mongolia)"
    },
    {
      "question": "花魁",
      "answer": "おいらん",
      "meaning": "oiran, high-ranking courtesan, prostitute"
    },
    {
      "question": "王配",
      "answer": "おうはい",
      "meaning": "prince consort"
    },
    {
      "question": "作戦計画",
      "answer": "さくせんけいかく",
      "meaning": "operation plan, scheme of operations, plan of campaign"
    },
    {
      "question": "西岸",
      "answer": "せいがん",
      "meaning": "west coast, west bank"
    },
    {
      "question": "徴候",
      "answer": "ちょうこう",
      "meaning": "sign, indication, omen, symptom"
    },
    {
      "question": "鰹",
      "answer": "かつお",
      "meaning": "skipjack tuna (Katsuwonus pelamis), oceanic bonito, victorfish"
    },
    {
      "question": "共産主義",
      "answer": "きょうさんしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "communism, collectivism"
    },
    {
      "question": "弁論",
      "answer": "べんろん",
      "meaning": "discussion, debate, argument"
    },
    {
      "question": "大麻",
      "answer": "たいま,おおあさ",
      "meaning": "hemp, cannabis, marijuana, pot, hashish, Shinto paper offerings"
    },
    {
      "question": "持久走",
      "answer": "じきゅうそう",
      "meaning": "marathon training in physical education classes in Japanese schools"
    },
    {
      "question": "晒",
      "answer": "さらし",
      "meaning": "bleaching, bleached cotton, doxxing, doxing, making someone's private information public without per"
    },
    {
      "question": "複",
      "answer": "ふく",
      "meaning": "compound, composite, multiple, re-, bi-, doubles (tennis, badminton, etc.), place bet (in horse raci"
    },
    {
      "question": "跳梁跋扈",
      "answer": "ちょうりょうばっこ",
      "meaning": "being rampant, domination"
    },
    {
      "question": "詰め襟",
      "answer": "つめえり",
      "meaning": "stand-up collar"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣り銭",
      "answer": "つりせん",
      "meaning": "change (for a purchase)"
    },
    {
      "question": "度肝",
      "answer": "どぎも",
      "meaning": "guts, pluck, nerve, spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "大有り",
      "answer": "おおあり",
      "meaning": "plentiful, abundant, definitely extant"
    },
    {
      "question": "類似点",
      "answer": "るいじてん",
      "meaning": "points of similarity"
    },
    {
      "question": "見渡し",
      "answer": "みわたし",
      "meaning": "viewing, view, viewpoint"
    },
    {
      "question": "丞相",
      "answer": "じょうしょう",
      "meaning": "prime minister (in ancient China)"
    },
    {
      "question": "絃",
      "answer": "つる,げん",
      "meaning": "bowstring, string (of shamisen, guitar, violin, etc.), bail (arched pot handle), diagonal levelling"
    },
    {
      "question": "創成",
      "answer": "そうせい",
      "meaning": "creation, formation, foundation, establishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "白兎",
      "answer": "しろうさぎ",
      "meaning": "white rabbit"
    },
    {
      "question": "本願",
      "answer": "ほんがん",
      "meaning": "Amida Buddha's original vow, long-cherished desire"
    },
    {
      "question": "入道",
      "answer": "にゅうどう",
      "meaning": "entering the priesthood, priest, monk, man with a shaven head, bald-headed monster"
    },
    {
      "question": "定宿",
      "answer": "じょうやど",
      "meaning": "one's regular inn, one's usual hotel"
    },
    {
      "question": "オペラ座",
      "answer": "オペラざ",
      "meaning": "opera house"
    },
    {
      "question": "山猿",
      "answer": "やまざる",
      "meaning": "mountain monkey, wild monkey, mountain dweller, bumpkin, boor"
    },
    {
      "question": "吸気",
      "answer": "きゅうき",
      "meaning": "inhalation (of air), inhaled air, intake (e.g. of air)"
    },
    {
      "question": "妹御",
      "answer": "いもうとご,いもとご",
      "meaning": "(another person's) younger sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱砂",
      "answer": "ねっさ",
      "meaning": "hot sand"
    },
    {
      "question": "着床",
      "answer": "ちゃくしょう",
      "meaning": "implantation (of an embryo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "短歌",
      "answer": "たんか,みじかうた",
      "meaning": "tanka, 31-mora Japanese poem"
    },
    {
      "question": "射掛ける",
      "answer": "いかける",
      "meaning": "to shoot or fire off an arrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "太っちょ",
      "answer": "ふとっちょ",
      "meaning": "fatty, fatso"
    },
    {
      "question": "網戸",
      "answer": "あみど",
      "meaning": "window screen, insect screen, mosquito screen, screen, screen door"
    },
    {
      "question": "親会社",
      "answer": "おやがいしゃ",
      "meaning": "parent company"
    },
    {
      "question": "富裕",
      "answer": "ふゆう",
      "meaning": "wealth, riches, affluence, opulence"
    },
    {
      "question": "面映い",
      "answer": "おもはゆい",
      "meaning": "embarrassed, self-conscious, bashful, abashed"
    },
    {
      "question": "青菜",
      "answer": "あおな",
      "meaning": "greens"
    },
    {
      "question": "熊手",
      "answer": "くまで",
      "meaning": "rake, fork, bamboo rake"
    },
    {
      "question": "張力",
      "answer": "ちょうりょく",
      "meaning": "tension, tensile strength"
    },
    {
      "question": "自他",
      "answer": "じた",
      "meaning": "oneself and others, (in philosophy) subject and object, transitivity, transitive and intransitive ve"
    },
    {
      "question": "組する",
      "answer": "くみする",
      "meaning": "to take part in, to be a party to, to side with, to support, to agree with"
    },
    {
      "question": "虫刺され",
      "answer": "むしさされ",
      "meaning": "insect bite, bug bite, sting"
    },
    {
      "question": "手遊び",
      "answer": "てあそび,てすさび",
      "meaning": "plaything, playing (with a toy), gambling, activity using hand-gestures (esp. playing games or singi"
    },
    {
      "question": "良う",
      "answer": "よう",
      "meaning": "well, properly, skillfully, often, how (could you), why (would you)"
    },
    {
      "question": "金回り",
      "answer": "かねまわり",
      "meaning": "financial circumstances, financial situation, circulation of money"
    },
    {
      "question": "極貧",
      "answer": "ごくひん",
      "meaning": "destitution"
    },
    {
      "question": "性犯罪",
      "answer": "せいはんざい",
      "meaning": "sex crime"
    },
    {
      "question": "対照",
      "answer": "たいしょう",
      "meaning": "contrast, antithesis, comparison"
    },
    {
      "question": "藻屑",
      "answer": "もくず",
      "meaning": "scraps of seaweed, death at sea (metaphor)"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳触り",
      "answer": "みみざわり",
      "meaning": "feeling one gets from listening to something"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬱積",
      "answer": "うっせき",
      "meaning": "accumulation (e.g. of emotions, grievances, etc.), buildup, suppression (e.g. of anger)"
    },
    {
      "question": "言語能力",
      "answer": "げんごのうりょく",
      "meaning": "(linguistic) competence, language capability"
    },
    {
      "question": "温もる",
      "answer": "ぬくもる",
      "meaning": "to get warm, to become warm"
    },
    {
      "question": "芽生え",
      "answer": "めばえ",
      "meaning": "bud, sprout"
    },
    {
      "question": "箔が付く",
      "answer": "はくがつく",
      "meaning": "to increase in value, to gain prestige"
    },
    {
      "question": "地が出る",
      "answer": "じがでる",
      "meaning": "to reveal one's true colors (colours), to betray oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "名月",
      "answer": "めいげつ",
      "meaning": "harvest moon (trad. 15th day of the 8th lunar month)"
    },
    {
      "question": "角刈り",
      "answer": "かくがり",
      "meaning": "crew cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "砲手",
      "answer": "ほうしゅ",
      "meaning": "gunner"
    },
    {
      "question": "族籍",
      "answer": "ぞくせき",
      "meaning": "one's class (and legal domicile)"
    },
    {
      "question": "都民",
      "answer": "とみん",
      "meaning": "city populace, resident of Tokyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀紙",
      "answer": "ぎんがみ",
      "meaning": "aluminum foil, aluminium foil, tinfoil, silver paper, silver-colored paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "源氏物語",
      "answer": "げんじものがたり",
      "meaning": "The Tale of Genji"
    },
    {
      "question": "譲位",
      "answer": "じょうい",
      "meaning": "abdication"
    },
    {
      "question": "様態",
      "answer": "ようたい",
      "meaning": "form, situation, condition"
    },
    {
      "question": "文化遺産",
      "answer": "ぶんかいさん",
      "meaning": "cultural heritage"
    },
    {
      "question": "大衆食堂",
      "answer": "たいしゅうしょくどう",
      "meaning": "cheap restaurant, eating place (house)"
    },
    {
      "question": "存ずる",
      "answer": "ぞんずる",
      "meaning": "to think, feel, consider, know, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "顔触れ",
      "answer": "かおぶれ",
      "meaning": "personnel, members, lineup (of a team), roster, cast (of a play), announcement of next day's match-u"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱帯雨林",
      "answer": "ねったいうりん",
      "meaning": "tropical forest, tropical rainforest"
    },
    {
      "question": "具体案",
      "answer": "ぐたいあん",
      "meaning": "concrete proposal"
    },
    {
      "question": "緊急措置",
      "answer": "きんきゅうそち",
      "meaning": "emergency measures, urgent countermeasures"
    },
    {
      "question": "行楽",
      "answer": "こうらく",
      "meaning": "outing, excursion, pleasure trip, going on a picnic"
    },
    {
      "question": "届け先",
      "answer": "とどけさき",
      "meaning": "destination, receiver's address, consignee"
    },
    {
      "question": "懲り懲り",
      "answer": "こりごり",
      "meaning": "bitter experience, learning from a bad experience, having had enough (of something unpleasant), havi"
    },
    {
      "question": "一日千秋",
      "answer": "いちじつせんしゅう,いちにちせんしゅう",
      "meaning": "(waiting) impatiently, (spending) many a weary day, each moment seeming like an eternity"
    },
    {
      "question": "原文",
      "answer": "げんぶん",
      "meaning": "original text"
    },
    {
      "question": "肖像権",
      "answer": "しょうぞうけん",
      "meaning": "rights to usage of one's likeness"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り外し",
      "answer": "とりはずし",
      "meaning": "removal, dismantling, detaching"
    },
    {
      "question": "小雪",
      "answer": "こゆき,しょうせつ",
      "meaning": "light snow, 'minor snow' solar term (approx. November 22)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉋",
      "answer": "かんな",
      "meaning": "plane (for working with wood)"
    },
    {
      "question": "職能",
      "answer": "しょくのう",
      "meaning": "occupational ability, function, role"
    },
    {
      "question": "浪士",
      "answer": "ろうし",
      "meaning": "ronin, lordless samurai"
    },
    {
      "question": "短銃",
      "answer": "たんじゅう",
      "meaning": "pistol, revolver"
    },
    {
      "question": "案内状",
      "answer": "あんないじょう",
      "meaning": "letter of invitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "養護",
      "answer": "ようご",
      "meaning": "nursing, (protective) care"
    },
    {
      "question": "航続距離",
      "answer": "こうぞくきょり",
      "meaning": "cruising range, flying range"
    },
    {
      "question": "蔭",
      "answer": "かげ",
      "meaning": "shade, shadow, behind (something), other side, back, background, behind the scenes, behind someone's"
    },
    {
      "question": "不逞",
      "answer": "ふてい",
      "meaning": "insubordination, outlawry"
    },
    {
      "question": "領有",
      "answer": "りょうゆう",
      "meaning": "possession (esp. of a territory)"
    },
    {
      "question": "空疎",
      "answer": "くうそ",
      "meaning": "empty (e.g. argument), insubstantial, hollow, fruitless"
    },
    {
      "question": "瀬戸内海",
      "answer": "せとないかい",
      "meaning": "Seto Inland Sea, Inland Sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "杏仁豆腐",
      "answer": "あんにんどうふ,きょうにんどうふ",
      "meaning": "(Chinese-style) almond jelly, dessert of powdered and jellied apricot kernels with fruit"
    },
    {
      "question": "カーキ色",
      "answer": "カーキいろ",
      "meaning": "khaki (colour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "旗揚げ",
      "answer": "はたあげ",
      "meaning": "raising an army, launching business"
    },
    {
      "question": "記録媒体",
      "answer": "きろくばいたい",
      "meaning": "recording medium, storage medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨海",
      "answer": "りんかい",
      "meaning": "coastal, seaside, oceanfront, maritime"
    },
    {
      "question": "心臓病",
      "answer": "しんぞうびょう",
      "meaning": "heart trouble, heart disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "同率",
      "answer": "どうりつ",
      "meaning": "the same ratio or percentage"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛り場",
      "answer": "さかりば",
      "meaning": "busy place, busy street, place that's always bustling with people, amusement quarters"
    },
    {
      "question": "暖気",
      "answer": "のんき,だんき",
      "meaning": "carefree, optimistic, careless, reckless, heedless, happy-go-lucky, easygoing, thoughtless, warmth,"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹持ち",
      "answer": "はらもち",
      "meaning": "feeling of fullness, ability of a food to fill you up"
    },
    {
      "question": "消化試合",
      "answer": "しょうかしあい",
      "meaning": "throwaway match (i.e. one played after a tournament has already been decided), dead rubber"
    },
    {
      "question": "抱き起す",
      "answer": "だきおこす",
      "meaning": "to lift (a person) in one's arms, to help (a person) sit up"
    },
    {
      "question": "神酒",
      "answer": "しんしゅ,みき,みわ",
      "meaning": "sacred wine or sake, sake offered to the gods"
    },
    {
      "question": "飯店",
      "answer": "はんてん",
      "meaning": "Chinese restaurant"
    },
    {
      "question": "機関士",
      "answer": "きかんし",
      "meaning": "engineer (on a train, ship, aircraft, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "連絡船",
      "answer": "れんらくせん",
      "meaning": "ferry, ferryboat"
    },
    {
      "question": "典礼",
      "answer": "てんれい",
      "meaning": "ceremony, etiquette, courtesy, (Catholic) liturgy"
    },
    {
      "question": "背番号",
      "answer": "せばんごう",
      "meaning": "number on back of player's shirt, uniform number, shirt number"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本庭園",
      "answer": "にほんていえん",
      "meaning": "Japanese-style garden, traditional Japanese landscape garden"
    },
    {
      "question": "引渡し",
      "answer": "ひきわたし",
      "meaning": "delivery, handing over, turning over, extradition"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄絹",
      "answer": "うすぎぬ",
      "meaning": "thin or light silk, sheer silk, veil (mystery)"
    },
    {
      "question": "越冬",
      "answer": "えっとう",
      "meaning": "passing the winter, hibernation"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗忽",
      "answer": "そこつ",
      "meaning": "careless, thoughtless, rash, rude, at fault"
    },
    {
      "question": "句切る",
      "answer": "くぎる",
      "meaning": "to demarcate, to delimit, to divide (an area), to mark off, to cut off, to punctuate, to put an end"
    },
    {
      "question": "峻厳",
      "answer": "しゅんげん",
      "meaning": "strict, stern, rigorous, severe"
    },
    {
      "question": "非才",
      "answer": "ひさい",
      "meaning": "lack of ability, incompetence, incapacity"
    },
    {
      "question": "群雄割拠",
      "answer": "ぐんゆうかっきょ",
      "meaning": "rivalry of local warlords, a number of powerful (talented, influential) persons standing by themselv"
    },
    {
      "question": "見合わす",
      "answer": "みあわす",
      "meaning": "to exchange glances, to look at each other, to postpone, to put off, to withhold, to abandon, to con"
    },
    {
      "question": "逃げ口上",
      "answer": "にげこうじょう",
      "meaning": "evasive answer, excuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "独自性",
      "answer": "どくじせい",
      "meaning": "originality, distinctiveness, uniqueness, individuality"
    },
    {
      "question": "頻出",
      "answer": "ひんしゅつ",
      "meaning": "frequent appearance, frequent occurrence"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き取る",
      "answer": "かきとる",
      "meaning": "to write down (what someone says), to take down dictation, to take notes (e.g. of a lecture), to cop"
    },
    {
      "question": "人並",
      "answer": "ひとなみ",
      "meaning": "ordinary, average, common, normal, like the average person, like most people"
    },
    {
      "question": "譲り合い",
      "answer": "ゆずりあい",
      "meaning": "compromise, mutual concessions, give-and-take"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄化粧",
      "answer": "うすげしょう",
      "meaning": "light makeup"
    },
    {
      "question": "閑",
      "answer": "ひま,かん,のど",
      "meaning": "spare time, free time, leisure, time (e.g. time it takes to do something), time off, day off, vacati"
    },
    {
      "question": "学芸",
      "answer": "がくげい",
      "meaning": "arts and sciences, liberal arts"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖天",
      "answer": "しょうてん,しょうでん",
      "meaning": "Nandikesvara (Ganesh in the Buddhist pantheon)"
    },
    {
      "question": "御国",
      "answer": "みくに,おくに",
      "meaning": "country, Japan, your native country, your hometown, my home country (i.e. Japan), countryside, daimy"
    },
    {
      "question": "行政府",
      "answer": "ぎょうせいふ",
      "meaning": "the government, Administration"
    },
    {
      "question": "按摩",
      "answer": "あんま",
      "meaning": "massage (esp. anma, a traditional form of Japanese massage), masseur, masseuse, massager, blind pers"
    },
    {
      "question": "露台",
      "answer": "ろだい",
      "meaning": "balcony"
    },
    {
      "question": "卒論",
      "answer": "そつろん",
      "meaning": "graduation thesis, bachelor's degree thesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "直弟子",
      "answer": "じきでし",
      "meaning": "personal pupil"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒造",
      "answer": "しゅぞう",
      "meaning": "sake brewing"
    },
    {
      "question": "御輿",
      "answer": "みこし",
      "meaning": "portable shrine (carried in festivals), palanquin, buttocks, lower back, waist, hips"
    },
    {
      "question": "土管",
      "answer": "どかん",
      "meaning": "earthen pipe"
    },
    {
      "question": "離着陸",
      "answer": "りちゃくりく",
      "meaning": "takeoff and landing"
    },
    {
      "question": "火付け",
      "answer": "ひつけ",
      "meaning": "arson, incendiarism"
    },
    {
      "question": "感ずる",
      "answer": "かんずる",
      "meaning": "to feel, to sense"
    },
    {
      "question": "河岸",
      "answer": "かわぎし,かがん,かし",
      "meaning": "riverbank, riverside, market on the riverbank (esp. fish market), place (for activities), venue"
    },
    {
      "question": "失せ物",
      "answer": "うせもの",
      "meaning": "lost article"
    },
    {
      "question": "大言",
      "answer": "たいげん,だいげん",
      "meaning": "big talk, braggadocio"
    },
    {
      "question": "貧",
      "answer": "ひん",
      "meaning": "poverty, penury, want, need, insufficiency, shortage, deficiency"
    },
    {
      "question": "人相書き",
      "answer": "にんそうがき",
      "meaning": "personal description"
    },
    {
      "question": "熾火",
      "answer": "おきび",
      "meaning": "glowing ember (either red hot charcoal or the glowing remains of burnt firewood), live charcoal"
    },
    {
      "question": "轟かす",
      "answer": "とどろかす",
      "meaning": "to make a thundering sound, to make roar"
    },
    {
      "question": "説明責任",
      "answer": "せつめいせきにん",
      "meaning": "accountability, being held accountable"
    },
    {
      "question": "緞帳",
      "answer": "どんちょう",
      "meaning": "thick curtain, drop curtain"
    },
    {
      "question": "横線",
      "answer": "おうせん,よこせん",
      "meaning": "horizontal line"
    },
    {
      "question": "素地",
      "answer": "きじ,そじ",
      "meaning": "cloth, fabric, material, texture, dough, batter, inherent quality, one's true character, one's true"
    },
    {
      "question": "時節",
      "answer": "じせつ",
      "meaning": "season, the times, opportunity, occasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "開店休業",
      "answer": "かいてんきゅうぎょう",
      "meaning": "being open but having virtually no business"
    },
    {
      "question": "物知らず",
      "answer": "ものしらず",
      "meaning": "stupidity, ignorance, stupid person, ignorant person"
    },
    {
      "question": "大酒飲み",
      "answer": "おおざけのみ",
      "meaning": "heavy drinker"
    },
    {
      "question": "幼獣",
      "answer": "ようじゅう",
      "meaning": "young animal (esp. mammal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "新選組",
      "answer": "しんせんぐみ",
      "meaning": "Shinsengumi, Edo period police and military force dedicated to suppressing anti-shogunate activities"
    },
    {
      "question": "火車",
      "answer": "かしゃ",
      "meaning": "fiery chariot, kasha (mythical beast said to devour dead bodies), (in China) train (i.e. steam locom"
    },
    {
      "question": "精霊信仰",
      "answer": "せいれいしんこう",
      "meaning": "animism"
    },
    {
      "question": "三界",
      "answer": "さんがい",
      "meaning": "the three realms of existence, the whole universe (of a billion worlds) that Buddha enlightened, pas"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋼材",
      "answer": "こうざい",
      "meaning": "steel material"
    },
    {
      "question": "外海",
      "answer": "がいかい,そとうみ",
      "meaning": "ocean, open sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗室",
      "answer": "あんしつ",
      "meaning": "darkroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "凹",
      "answer": "おう,くぼ",
      "meaning": "concave, hollow, sunken, cavity, sunken place, vagina, female genitalia"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘湯",
      "answer": "ひとう",
      "meaning": "little-known hot spring, secret hot spring, secluded hot spring"
    },
    {
      "question": "異邦",
      "answer": "いほう",
      "meaning": "foreign country"
    },
    {
      "question": "児童文学",
      "answer": "じどうぶんがく",
      "meaning": "juvenile literature"
    },
    {
      "question": "北斗七星",
      "answer": "ほくとしちせい",
      "meaning": "the Big Dipper (asterism), the Plough, the Plow"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦災孤児",
      "answer": "せんさいこじ",
      "meaning": "war orphan"
    },
    {
      "question": "若僧",
      "answer": "わかぞう,にゃくそう,じゃくそう",
      "meaning": "youngster, neophyte, greenhorn, young monk, boy monk"
    },
    {
      "question": "工期",
      "answer": "こうき",
      "meaning": "building time, construction period"
    },
    {
      "question": "行進曲",
      "answer": "こうしんきょく",
      "meaning": "march"
    },
    {
      "question": "創世記",
      "answer": "そうせいき",
      "meaning": "Genesis (book of the Bible)"
    },
    {
      "question": "青汁",
      "answer": "あおじる",
      "meaning": "aojiru, vegetable juice drink made from green leafy vegetables"
    },
    {
      "question": "快勝",
      "answer": "かいしょう",
      "meaning": "sweeping victory, easy victory"
    },
    {
      "question": "四字熟語",
      "answer": "よじじゅくご",
      "meaning": "four-character compound word (esp. idiomatic)"
    },
    {
      "question": "面通し",
      "answer": "めんとおし",
      "meaning": "(police) line-up"
    },
    {
      "question": "妙薬",
      "answer": "みょうやく",
      "meaning": "wonder drug, miracle cure, elixir"
    },
    {
      "question": "非売品",
      "answer": "ひばいひん",
      "meaning": "article not for sale"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕事始め",
      "answer": "しごとはじめ",
      "meaning": "resuming work after the New Year's vacation, first time that one works in the year"
    },
    {
      "question": "泣きっ面",
      "answer": "なきっつら",
      "meaning": "tearful face"
    },
    {
      "question": "習わす",
      "answer": "ならわす",
      "meaning": "to make (someone) learn, to be accustomed to ..., to be used to ..., to always ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "明治神宮",
      "answer": "めいじじんぐう",
      "meaning": "Meiji Shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "浅葱",
      "answer": "あさぎ,あさつき",
      "meaning": "pale blue-green, chive (Allium schoenoprasum), chives"
    },
    {
      "question": "白浜",
      "answer": "しらはま",
      "meaning": "white sandy beach"
    },
    {
      "question": "調律師",
      "answer": "ちょうりつし",
      "meaning": "piano tuner"
    },
    {
      "question": "諒解",
      "answer": "りょうかい",
      "meaning": "comprehension, consent, understanding, agreement, OK, roger (on two-way radio)"
    },
    {
      "question": "近習",
      "answer": "きんじゅ,きんじゅう",
      "meaning": "attendant"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛮人",
      "answer": "ばんじん",
      "meaning": "savage, barbarian, aboriginal"
    },
    {
      "question": "門衛",
      "answer": "もんえい",
      "meaning": "gatekeeper, doorman, porter"
    },
    {
      "question": "発疹",
      "answer": "はっしん,ほっしん",
      "meaning": "rash, eruption"
    },
    {
      "question": "一発屋",
      "answer": "いっぱつや",
      "meaning": "one-hit wonder, flash in the pan, all-or-nothing gambler, one-shot speculator, someone who puts all"
    },
    {
      "question": "楼閣",
      "answer": "ろうかく",
      "meaning": "multistoried building"
    },
    {
      "question": "撥ね返す",
      "answer": "はねかえす",
      "meaning": "to reject, to repulse, to repel, to bounce back, to counterattack, to strike back"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬩ぎ合う",
      "answer": "せめぎあう",
      "meaning": "to fight each other"
    },
    {
      "question": "冬至",
      "answer": "とうじ",
      "meaning": "winter solstice"
    },
    {
      "question": "宿業",
      "answer": "しゅくごう",
      "meaning": "karma (from one's previous life)"
    },
    {
      "question": "疾風迅雷",
      "answer": "しっぷうじんらい",
      "meaning": "with lightning speed"
    },
    {
      "question": "髪結い",
      "answer": "かみゆい",
      "meaning": "hairdresser, hairdressing"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋳型",
      "answer": "いがた",
      "meaning": "mold, mould, template"
    },
    {
      "question": "見縊る",
      "answer": "みくびる",
      "meaning": "to underrate, to belittle, to look down on, to despise"
    },
    {
      "question": "時短",
      "answer": "じたん",
      "meaning": "reduction in working hours, time-saving"
    },
    {
      "question": "憩う",
      "answer": "いこう",
      "meaning": "to rest, to relax, to repose"
    },
    {
      "question": "屋号",
      "answer": "やごう",
      "meaning": "name of store, trade name (esp. of a sole proprietorship), stage name (e.g. of actor)"
    },
    {
      "question": "凶弾",
      "answer": "きょうだん",
      "meaning": "assassin's bullet"
    },
    {
      "question": "通り抜け",
      "answer": "とおりぬけ",
      "meaning": "passing through, through passage"
    },
    {
      "question": "無目的",
      "answer": "むもくてき",
      "meaning": "purposeless, aimless"
    },
    {
      "question": "急逝",
      "answer": "きゅうせい",
      "meaning": "sudden death"
    },
    {
      "question": "最少",
      "answer": "さいしょう",
      "meaning": "fewest, least, smallest (number), lowest, minimum, youngest"
    },
    {
      "question": "火の気",
      "answer": "ひのけ,ほのけ",
      "meaning": "source of fire, sign of fire, warmth of fire, heat"
    },
    {
      "question": "子々孫々",
      "answer": "ししそんそん",
      "meaning": "one's descendants, one's offspring, posterity"
    },
    {
      "question": "単色",
      "answer": "たんしょく",
      "meaning": "single colour (color), monochrome"
    },
    {
      "question": "現実主義",
      "answer": "げんじつしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "realism"
    },
    {
      "question": "口裏",
      "answer": "くちうら",
      "meaning": "determining a speaker's true or hidden meaning, determining a speaker's intentions from his manner o"
    },
    {
      "question": "物持ち",
      "answer": "ものもち",
      "meaning": "rich person, wealthy person, taking good care of things, keeping things for a long time and taking c"
    },
    {
      "question": "大枚",
      "answer": "たいまい",
      "meaning": "large sum (of money)"
    },
    {
      "question": "滝川",
      "answer": "たきがわ",
      "meaning": "rapids"
    },
    {
      "question": "安土",
      "answer": "あずち",
      "meaning": "mound on which targets are placed (in archery), firing mound"
    },
    {
      "question": "変電所",
      "answer": "へんでんしょ",
      "meaning": "transformer substation"
    },
    {
      "question": "偽装結婚",
      "answer": "ぎそうけっこん",
      "meaning": "sham marriage, fake marriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "江戸幕府",
      "answer": "えどばくふ",
      "meaning": "Edo shogunate (1603-1867)"
    },
    {
      "question": "執",
      "answer": "たらし,しゅう",
      "meaning": "bow (and arrow; esp. of a noble), attachment, obsession, persistence"
    },
    {
      "question": "若武者",
      "answer": "わかむしゃ",
      "meaning": "young warrior"
    },
    {
      "question": "風土病",
      "answer": "ふうどびょう",
      "meaning": "endemic disease, local disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "即位式",
      "answer": "そくいしき",
      "meaning": "enthronement ceremony, coronation"
    },
    {
      "question": "股座",
      "answer": "またぐら",
      "meaning": "crotch"
    },
    {
      "question": "湖岸",
      "answer": "こがん",
      "meaning": "lakeshore, lakeside"
    },
    {
      "question": "闘牛士",
      "answer": "とうぎゅうし",
      "meaning": "bullfighter, matador"
    },
    {
      "question": "政治犯",
      "answer": "せいじはん",
      "meaning": "political offense, political offence, political crime, political offender, political prisoner, priso"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝餉",
      "answer": "あさげ,あさけ",
      "meaning": "breakfast"
    },
    {
      "question": "誅",
      "answer": "ちゅう",
      "meaning": "death penalty"
    },
    {
      "question": "卵巣",
      "answer": "らんそう",
      "meaning": "ovary"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾き語り",
      "answer": "ひきがたり",
      "meaning": "singing to one's own accompaniment"
    },
    {
      "question": "草稿",
      "answer": "そうこう",
      "meaning": "notes, draft, manuscript"
    },
    {
      "question": "膝掛け",
      "answer": "ひざかけ",
      "meaning": "lap blanket"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘔吐く",
      "answer": "えずく,えづく",
      "meaning": "to vomit, to throw up, to feel nauseated, to feel sick"
    },
    {
      "question": "創出",
      "answer": "そうしゅつ",
      "meaning": "creation, generation"
    },
    {
      "question": "幾人",
      "answer": "いくにん,いくたり",
      "meaning": "number of people"
    },
    {
      "question": "放熱",
      "answer": "ほうねつ",
      "meaning": "radiant heat, heat radiation, heat dissipation, thermolysis"
    },
    {
      "question": "平社員",
      "answer": "ひらしゃいん",
      "meaning": "rank-and-file member of staff, ordinary employee, low-grade employee"
    },
    {
      "question": "数列",
      "answer": "すうれつ",
      "meaning": "progression, sequence"
    },
    {
      "question": "石製",
      "answer": "せきせい",
      "meaning": "stone, made of stone"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛羽立つ",
      "answer": "けばだつ",
      "meaning": "to become fluffy"
    },
    {
      "question": "英訳",
      "answer": "えいやく",
      "meaning": "English translation"
    },
    {
      "question": "突き指",
      "answer": "つきゆび",
      "meaning": "jamming a finger, stubbing a toe, spraining a finger (toe)"
    },
    {
      "question": "近似",
      "answer": "きんじ",
      "meaning": "approximation, having a close resemblance"
    },
    {
      "question": "青痣",
      "answer": "あおあざ",
      "meaning": "bruise"
    },
    {
      "question": "混じり気",
      "answer": "まじりけ",
      "meaning": "mixture, impurities"
    },
    {
      "question": "消費期限",
      "answer": "しょうひきげん",
      "meaning": "expiry date (esp. on food), expiration date, use-by date"
    },
    {
      "question": "無給",
      "answer": "むきゅう",
      "meaning": "unpaid, nonsalaried"
    },
    {
      "question": "揚々",
      "answer": "ようよう",
      "meaning": "triumphant, exultant, in high and proud spirits"
    },
    {
      "question": "風雅",
      "answer": "ふうが",
      "meaning": "elegance, grace, refinement, good taste"
    },
    {
      "question": "真四角",
      "answer": "ましかく",
      "meaning": "square"
    },
    {
      "question": "安まる",
      "answer": "やすまる",
      "meaning": "to be rested, to feel at ease, to repose, to be relieved"
    },
    {
      "question": "頓珍漢",
      "answer": "とんちんかん",
      "meaning": "absurdity, contradiction, incoherence, irrelevance"
    },
    {
      "question": "空瓶",
      "answer": "からびん",
      "meaning": "empty bottle"
    },
    {
      "question": "先住",
      "answer": "せんじゅう",
      "meaning": "original inhabitant, aboriginal, previous priest"
    },
    {
      "question": "専制",
      "answer": "せんせい",
      "meaning": "despotism, autocracy"
    },
    {
      "question": "恵",
      "answer": "え",
      "meaning": "wisdom, enlightenment, prajñā (one of the three divisions of the noble eightfold path)"
    },
    {
      "question": "四角錐",
      "answer": "しかくすい",
      "meaning": "quadrangular pyramid"
    },
    {
      "question": "慨嘆",
      "answer": "がいたん",
      "meaning": "deploring, lamentation, regret, complaint"
    },
    {
      "question": "一輪車",
      "answer": "いちりんしゃ",
      "meaning": "unicycle, monocycle, wheelbarrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "面舵",
      "answer": "おもかじ",
      "meaning": "starboard (side of a ship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "打擲",
      "answer": "ちょうちゃく",
      "meaning": "thrashing, beating"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋の歌",
      "answer": "こいのうた",
      "meaning": "love song, love poem"
    },
    {
      "question": "満身",
      "answer": "まんしん",
      "meaning": "the whole body, all one's (strength, anger, spirit, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "玩ぶ",
      "answer": "もてあそぶ",
      "meaning": "to play with (a toy, one's hair, etc.), to fiddle with, to toy with (one's emotions, etc.), to trifl"
    },
    {
      "question": "往時",
      "answer": "おうじ",
      "meaning": "ancient times"
    },
    {
      "question": "露悪",
      "answer": "ろあく",
      "meaning": "making a show of one's faults"
    },
    {
      "question": "席上",
      "answer": "せきじょう",
      "meaning": "at the meeting, on the occasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "都道府県",
      "answer": "とどうふけん",
      "meaning": "administrative divisions of Japan: Tokyo-to, Hokkai-do, Osaka-fu, Kyoto-fu and remaining prefectures"
    },
    {
      "question": "大洋",
      "answer": "たいよう",
      "meaning": "ocean"
    },
    {
      "question": "徒手",
      "answer": "としゅ",
      "meaning": "being empty-handed, bare hand (e.g. fight), being penniless"
    },
    {
      "question": "早春",
      "answer": "そうしゅん",
      "meaning": "early spring"
    },
    {
      "question": "缶詰め",
      "answer": "かんづめ",
      "meaning": "canned food, tinned food, confining someone (e.g. so they can concentrate on work), being stuck in a"
    },
    {
      "question": "起承転結",
      "answer": "きしょうてんけつ",
      "meaning": "introduction, development, turn and conclusion (quadripartite structure of certain Chinese poetry),"
    },
    {
      "question": "曖昧模糊",
      "answer": "あいまいもこ",
      "meaning": "obscure, vague, ambiguous"
    },
    {
      "question": "水責め",
      "answer": "みずぜめ",
      "meaning": "water torture"
    },
    {
      "question": "艶姿",
      "answer": "あですがた,えんし",
      "meaning": "charming figure, alluring figure"
    },
    {
      "question": "縊り殺す",
      "answer": "くびりころす",
      "meaning": "to strangle to death"
    },
    {
      "question": "擦過傷",
      "answer": "さっかしょう",
      "meaning": "abrasion, scratch"
    },
    {
      "question": "全盛",
      "answer": "ぜんせい",
      "meaning": "height of prosperity"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗旨替え",
      "answer": "しゅうしがえ",
      "meaning": "conversion (to a different religion, denomination, etc.), change (of ideology, interest, taste, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "生活音",
      "answer": "せいかつおん",
      "meaning": "daily life noise, household noises, noise that arises at home from everyday occurrences"
    },
    {
      "question": "下の部屋",
      "answer": "したのへや",
      "meaning": "downstairs room"
    },
    {
      "question": "樺",
      "answer": "かば,かんば,かにわ",
      "meaning": "birch (esp. Japanese white birch)"
    },
    {
      "question": "二葉",
      "answer": "によう,ふたば",
      "meaning": "two flat things, seed leaves (of a dicot), cotyledons, bud, sprout, early stages, very beginning"
    },
    {
      "question": "断章",
      "answer": "だんしょう",
      "meaning": "literary fragment, interpreting (and using) a passage without regard to its context"
    },
    {
      "question": "虎子",
      "answer": "まる,こし",
      "meaning": "bedpan, chamber pot, potty, baby tiger"
    },
    {
      "question": "公団",
      "answer": "こうだん",
      "meaning": "public corporation, public housing"
    },
    {
      "question": "周遊",
      "answer": "しゅうゆう",
      "meaning": "(circular) tour, round trip, excursion"
    },
    {
      "question": "本営",
      "answer": "ほんえい",
      "meaning": "headquarters"
    },
    {
      "question": "洋裁",
      "answer": "ようさい",
      "meaning": "(Western) dressmaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "武装蜂起",
      "answer": "ぶそうほうき",
      "meaning": "armed uprising"
    },
    {
      "question": "贈与",
      "answer": "ぞうよ",
      "meaning": "donation, presentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "猿山",
      "answer": "さるやま",
      "meaning": "hill in a monkey enclosure (at a zoo, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "地上げ",
      "answer": "じあげ",
      "meaning": "buying up plots of land by force to resell at a large profit, land sharking, raising the ground leve"
    },
    {
      "question": "男娼",
      "answer": "だんしょう",
      "meaning": "male prostitute"
    },
    {
      "question": "議案",
      "answer": "ぎあん",
      "meaning": "legislative bill, measure, agenda item"
    },
    {
      "question": "檀家",
      "answer": "だんか,だんけ",
      "meaning": "family which supports a temple, parishioner"
    },
    {
      "question": "肩胛骨",
      "answer": "けんこうこつ",
      "meaning": "shoulder blade, scapula"
    },
    {
      "question": "空揚げ",
      "answer": "からあげ",
      "meaning": "deep-fried food (esp. chicken)"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い足す",
      "answer": "いいたす",
      "meaning": "to say something additional, to add (to what was said before)"
    },
    {
      "question": "知悉",
      "answer": "ちしつ",
      "meaning": "complete knowledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "発泡酒",
      "answer": "はっぽうしゅ",
      "meaning": "happōshu, low-malt beer-like beverage, sparkling wine, sparkling liquor, sparkling alcohol"
    },
    {
      "question": "低頭",
      "answer": "ていとう",
      "meaning": "low bow"
    },
    {
      "question": "長短",
      "answer": "ちょうたん",
      "meaning": "(relative) length, advantages and disadvantages, pluses and minuses, strong and weak points, merits"
    },
    {
      "question": "無間地獄",
      "answer": "むげんじごく,むけんじごく",
      "meaning": "the Avici hell, the eighth and most painful of the eight hells in Buddhism, Buddhist hell of uninter"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖地巡礼",
      "answer": "せいちじゅんれい",
      "meaning": "pilgrimage to sacred places, visiting the real-life locations used in an anime, manga, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "刈り取り",
      "answer": "かりとり",
      "meaning": "harvesting, reaping"
    },
    {
      "question": "官庁",
      "answer": "かんちょう",
      "meaning": "government office, government agency, authorities"
    },
    {
      "question": "宛てがう",
      "answer": "あてがう",
      "meaning": "to allot, to allocate, to supply with, to furnish, to fit to, to fasten to, to apply to"
    },
    {
      "question": "南半球",
      "answer": "みなみはんきゅう",
      "meaning": "southern hemisphere"
    },
    {
      "question": "冒険小説",
      "answer": "ぼうけんしょうせつ",
      "meaning": "adventure story, novel of adventure"
    },
    {
      "question": "後家",
      "answer": "ごけ",
      "meaning": "widow"
    },
    {
      "question": "レア物",
      "answer": "レアもの",
      "meaning": "rare item (vintage, by a famous designer, etc.), rarity"
    },
    {
      "question": "破顔一笑",
      "answer": "はがんいっしょう",
      "meaning": "smiling broadly"
    },
    {
      "question": "自主規制",
      "answer": "じしゅきせい",
      "meaning": "voluntary restraints, self-limitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "窮鼠",
      "answer": "きゅうそ",
      "meaning": "cornered animal, cornered rat"
    },
    {
      "question": "談判",
      "answer": "だんぱん",
      "meaning": "negotiations, bargaining, talks, making demands"
    },
    {
      "question": "民間療法",
      "answer": "みんかんりょうほう",
      "meaning": "folk remedies"
    },
    {
      "question": "大腿骨",
      "answer": "だいたいこつ",
      "meaning": "thighbone, femur"
    },
    {
      "question": "果てし",
      "answer": "はてし",
      "meaning": "end, limit, bounds, extremity, result, fate"
    },
    {
      "question": "割れ物",
      "answer": "われもの",
      "meaning": "fragile item, broken article"
    },
    {
      "question": "十二神将",
      "answer": "じゅうにじんしょう",
      "meaning": "the twelve divine generals (of Bhaisajyaguru)"
    },
    {
      "question": "汎",
      "answer": "はん",
      "meaning": "pan-"
    },
    {
      "question": "石室",
      "answer": "せきしつ,いしむろ",
      "meaning": "stone hut, rock chamber, tomb, stone burial chamber"
    },
    {
      "question": "白鷺",
      "answer": "しらさぎ,はくろ",
      "meaning": "heron with all-white plumage (incl. egrets), white heron"
    },
    {
      "question": "撮影所",
      "answer": "さつえいじょ",
      "meaning": "film studio"
    },
    {
      "question": "為替",
      "answer": "かわせ,かわし",
      "meaning": "money order, draft, exchange (e.g. foreign)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大鉈",
      "answer": "おおなた",
      "meaning": "large sturdy broad-bladed knife, used in woodcraft and hunting"
    },
    {
      "question": "巡視",
      "answer": "じゅんし",
      "meaning": "inspection tour"
    },
    {
      "question": "天下人",
      "answer": "てんかびと,てんかにん",
      "meaning": "ruler of the whole country, person who holds the reins of government"
    },
    {
      "question": "発禁",
      "answer": "はっきん",
      "meaning": "prohibition of sale, ban on sale"
    },
    {
      "question": "延べ棒",
      "answer": "のべぼう",
      "meaning": "(metal) bar, (wooden) rolling pin"
    },
    {
      "question": "血清",
      "answer": "けっせい",
      "meaning": "serum, blood serum"
    },
    {
      "question": "音ゲー",
      "answer": "おとゲー,おんゲー",
      "meaning": "rhythm game (video game type), music game"
    },
    {
      "question": "自動制御",
      "answer": "じどうせいぎょ",
      "meaning": "automatic control"
    },
    {
      "question": "結核",
      "answer": "けっかく",
      "meaning": "tuberculosis, tubercule"
    },
    {
      "question": "昂然",
      "answer": "こうぜん",
      "meaning": "elated, triumphant, proud"
    },
    {
      "question": "酔漢",
      "answer": "すいかん",
      "meaning": "drunkard, drunken fellow"
    },
    {
      "question": "開園",
      "answer": "かいえん",
      "meaning": "opening of a park (theme park, botanical garden etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "前人未踏",
      "answer": "ぜんじんみとう",
      "meaning": "untrodden (region, field of study, etc.), unprecedented (discovery, achievement, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "実食",
      "answer": "じっしょく",
      "meaning": "tasting a food that one has previously heard of"
    },
    {
      "question": "報償",
      "answer": "ほうしょう",
      "meaning": "compensation, indemnity, reparation"
    },
    {
      "question": "名鑑",
      "answer": "めいかん",
      "meaning": "directory, list"
    },
    {
      "question": "希少金属",
      "answer": "きしょうきんぞく",
      "meaning": "rare metal, minor metal"
    },
    {
      "question": "人種差別",
      "answer": "じんしゅさべつ",
      "meaning": "racial discrimination, racism"
    },
    {
      "question": "手込め",
      "answer": "てごめ",
      "meaning": "rape, violation"
    },
    {
      "question": "互助",
      "answer": "ごじょ",
      "meaning": "mutual aid, cooperation, benefit"
    },
    {
      "question": "痺れ薬",
      "answer": "しびれぐすり",
      "meaning": "anesthetic, anaesthetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤土",
      "answer": "あかつち",
      "meaning": "red clay, tuff loam, dark-red paint"
    },
    {
      "question": "裸の王様",
      "answer": "はだかのおうさま",
      "meaning": "person of high standing facing no opposition and with a warped view of reality, naked emperor"
    },
    {
      "question": "汚辱",
      "answer": "おじょく",
      "meaning": "disgrace, humiliation, insult"
    },
    {
      "question": "公僕",
      "answer": "こうぼく",
      "meaning": "public servant"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ正直",
      "answer": "まっしょうじき",
      "meaning": "perfectly honest"
    },
    {
      "question": "未確定",
      "answer": "みかくてい",
      "meaning": "unsettled, pending"
    },
    {
      "question": "デパ地下",
      "answer": "デパちか",
      "meaning": "basement of a department store (where foodstuffs are usually sold)"
    },
    {
      "question": "喧々囂々",
      "answer": "けんけんごうごう",
      "meaning": "wild uproar, pandemonium, clamor of voices, tumult, noisy, uproarious, clamorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "精細",
      "answer": "せいさい",
      "meaning": "detail"
    },
    {
      "question": "男運",
      "answer": "おとこうん",
      "meaning": "luck with men"
    },
    {
      "question": "皺寄せ",
      "answer": "しわよせ",
      "meaning": "shifting (the burden) onto, ill effects, negative consequences, burden, strain, brunt, loss"
    },
    {
      "question": "二部",
      "answer": "にぶ",
      "meaning": "two parts, two copies, the second part"
    },
    {
      "question": "通信販売",
      "answer": "つうしんはんばい",
      "meaning": "online shopping service (with delivery by mail), mail order, mail-order sales, shop-by-mail service"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜け目",
      "answer": "ぬけめ",
      "meaning": "imprudence, oversight, omission, mistake"
    },
    {
      "question": "一雨",
      "answer": "ひとあめ",
      "meaning": "shower, rainfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "古老",
      "answer": "ころう",
      "meaning": "old people, seniors, elders, old-timer"
    },
    {
      "question": "駕籠",
      "answer": "かご",
      "meaning": "palanquin, litter, bier"
    },
    {
      "question": "無銘",
      "answer": "むめい",
      "meaning": "unsigned, without a signature"
    },
    {
      "question": "来館",
      "answer": "らいかん",
      "meaning": "coming to an embassy, theatre, library, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "餓狼",
      "answer": "がろう",
      "meaning": "hungry wolf"
    },
    {
      "question": "狭隘",
      "answer": "きょうあい",
      "meaning": "narrow, small, confined, narrow-minded, intolerant"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧縮空気",
      "answer": "あっしゅくくうき",
      "meaning": "compressed air"
    },
    {
      "question": "純文学",
      "answer": "じゅんぶんがく",
      "meaning": "pure literature, belles-lettres"
    },
    {
      "question": "四十九日",
      "answer": "しじゅうくにち",
      "meaning": "forty-ninth day after a person's death"
    },
    {
      "question": "通行税",
      "answer": "つうこうぜい",
      "meaning": "toll"
    },
    {
      "question": "産着",
      "answer": "うぶぎ",
      "meaning": "clothes for a newborn baby, baby clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "職権",
      "answer": "しょっけん",
      "meaning": "one's (official) authority, power"
    },
    {
      "question": "御大層",
      "answer": "ごたいそう",
      "meaning": "exaggerated, extravagant, overdone"
    },
    {
      "question": "汗水流す",
      "answer": "あせみずながす",
      "meaning": "to sweat and slave, to toil away"
    },
    {
      "question": "差し込み",
      "answer": "さしこみ",
      "meaning": "insertion, plug, (electrical) outlet, power point, spasm of pain, griping pain, (fit of) convulsions"
    },
    {
      "question": "同文",
      "answer": "どうぶん",
      "meaning": "same text, same wording, same script, same language"
    },
    {
      "question": "拘束時間",
      "answer": "こうそくじかん",
      "meaning": "total hours spent working"
    },
    {
      "question": "変体",
      "answer": "へんたい",
      "meaning": "unusual form, different shape, variant (e.g. kanji, kana)"
    },
    {
      "question": "桃花",
      "answer": "とうか",
      "meaning": "peach blossom"
    },
    {
      "question": "式部",
      "answer": "しきぶ",
      "meaning": "(Meiji era) official responsible for court ceremonies"
    },
    {
      "question": "防疫",
      "answer": "ぼうえき",
      "meaning": "communicable disease control (e.g. by quarantine, disinfection, etc.), prevention of epidemics"
    },
    {
      "question": "組紐",
      "answer": "くみひも",
      "meaning": "braid, plaited cord"
    },
    {
      "question": "孵す",
      "answer": "かえす",
      "meaning": "to hatch, to incubate"
    },
    {
      "question": "行灯",
      "answer": "あんどん,あんどう",
      "meaning": "fixed paper-enclosed lantern, paper-covered wooden stand housing an (oil) lamp"
    },
    {
      "question": "背泳ぎ",
      "answer": "せおよぎ",
      "meaning": "backstroke (swimming)"
    },
    {
      "question": "貨物列車",
      "answer": "かもつれっしゃ",
      "meaning": "freight train"
    },
    {
      "question": "稲作",
      "answer": "いなさく",
      "meaning": "rice cultivation, rice crop"
    },
    {
      "question": "芸事",
      "answer": "げいごと",
      "meaning": "traditional performing arts (e.g. shamisen, koto, dance, etc.), accomplishments"
    },
    {
      "question": "情け無い",
      "answer": "なさけない",
      "meaning": "miserable, pitiable, shameful, deplorable, pathetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "照明弾",
      "answer": "しょうめいだん",
      "meaning": "a flare"
    },
    {
      "question": "職業軍人",
      "answer": "しょくぎょうぐんじん",
      "meaning": "career soldier"
    },
    {
      "question": "車載",
      "answer": "しゃさい",
      "meaning": "in-vehicle, on-board"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰部",
      "answer": "ようぶ",
      "meaning": "loins, hips, pelvic region, waist"
    },
    {
      "question": "浅漬け",
      "answer": "あさづけ",
      "meaning": "lightly pickled vegetables"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽隊",
      "answer": "がくたい",
      "meaning": "band, orchestra"
    },
    {
      "question": "不精",
      "answer": "ぶしょう",
      "meaning": "indolence, laziness, sloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "失効",
      "answer": "しっこう",
      "meaning": "lapse, abatement, invalidation, expiration, expiry, becoming void"
    },
    {
      "question": "生半",
      "answer": "なまなか",
      "meaning": "halfway-done, mediocre, uncertain, half-hearted, half-heartedly, insufficiently"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻頭",
      "answer": "はながしら",
      "meaning": "tip of the nose"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝負所",
      "answer": "しょうぶどころ",
      "meaning": "decisive moment, turning point, critical moment, win-or-bust situation"
    },
    {
      "question": "心的外傷",
      "answer": "しんてきがいしょう",
      "meaning": "psychic trauma, psychological trauma"
    },
    {
      "question": "実現性",
      "answer": "じつげんせい",
      "meaning": "practicability, feasibility, operability, expected implementation"
    },
    {
      "question": "偃月刀",
      "answer": "えんげつとう",
      "meaning": "scimitar"
    },
    {
      "question": "小母",
      "answer": "おば",
      "meaning": "old lady, ma'am"
    },
    {
      "question": "十傑",
      "answer": "じっけつ",
      "meaning": "ten best people (in a particular field)"
    },
    {
      "question": "分霊",
      "answer": "ぶんれい",
      "meaning": "division of a shrine's tutelary deity, in order to share it with another shrine, spirit divided in s"
    },
    {
      "question": "地検",
      "answer": "ちけん",
      "meaning": "District Public Prosecutor's Office"
    },
    {
      "question": "鱒",
      "answer": "ます",
      "meaning": "trout, sea trout"
    },
    {
      "question": "密猟",
      "answer": "みつりょう",
      "meaning": "poaching"
    },
    {
      "question": "統御",
      "answer": "とうぎょ",
      "meaning": "control"
    },
    {
      "question": "見出だす",
      "answer": "みいだす",
      "meaning": "to find out, to discover, to notice, to detect, to select, to pick out, to look out (from the inside"
    },
    {
      "question": "璧",
      "answer": "へき",
      "meaning": "bi (ancient Chinese artifact; flat jade or glass disc with a circular hole in the centre)"
    },
    {
      "question": "炭焼き",
      "answer": "すみやき",
      "meaning": "charcoal making, charcoal maker, charcoal-roasted, charcoal-grilled"
    },
    {
      "question": "田植え",
      "answer": "たうえ",
      "meaning": "rice planting"
    },
    {
      "question": "罪業",
      "answer": "ざいごう",
      "meaning": "sin, iniquity, crime"
    },
    {
      "question": "家計簿",
      "answer": "かけいぼ",
      "meaning": "household account book"
    },
    {
      "question": "扱き",
      "answer": "しごき",
      "meaning": "hazing, gruelling training, waistband, woman's undergirdle"
    },
    {
      "question": "空笑い",
      "answer": "そらわらい",
      "meaning": "feigned laughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "人集り",
      "answer": "ひとだかり",
      "meaning": "crowd, throng"
    },
    {
      "question": "推量",
      "answer": "すいりょう",
      "meaning": "guess, conjecture, supposition, inference"
    },
    {
      "question": "情婦",
      "answer": "じょうふ",
      "meaning": "mistress, lover, prostitute"
    },
    {
      "question": "瓦屋根",
      "answer": "かわらやね",
      "meaning": "tiled roof"
    },
    {
      "question": "幼児期",
      "answer": "ようじき",
      "meaning": "early childhood"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧約聖書",
      "answer": "きゅうやくせいしょ",
      "meaning": "Old Testament"
    },
    {
      "question": "性生活",
      "answer": "せいせいかつ",
      "meaning": "sex life, sexual activities"
    },
    {
      "question": "税務署",
      "answer": "ぜいむしょ",
      "meaning": "tax office"
    },
    {
      "question": "人物画",
      "answer": "じんぶつが",
      "meaning": "portrait painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "専心",
      "answer": "せんしん",
      "meaning": "undivided attention, concentration"
    },
    {
      "question": "序曲",
      "answer": "じょきょく",
      "meaning": "overture, prelude"
    },
    {
      "question": "多芸",
      "answer": "たげい",
      "meaning": "versatility"
    },
    {
      "question": "激戦地",
      "answer": "げきせんち",
      "meaning": "site of a bloody battle"
    },
    {
      "question": "一本気",
      "answer": "いっぽんぎ",
      "meaning": "single-minded (esp. personality or person), one-track mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄給",
      "answer": "はっきゅう",
      "meaning": "small salary, meagre salary, low pay"
    },
    {
      "question": "香しい",
      "answer": "かんばしい,かぐわしい",
      "meaning": "sweet-smelling, fragrant, aromatic, good (reputation, condition, results, etc.), favorable, scentful"
    },
    {
      "question": "降り止む",
      "answer": "ふりやむ",
      "meaning": "to stop raining or snowing"
    },
    {
      "question": "一役",
      "answer": "いちやく,ひとやく",
      "meaning": "an office, an important office, role (which someone or something plays in a given situation), part,"
    },
    {
      "question": "機運",
      "answer": "きうん",
      "meaning": "opportunity, chance, good time (to do), trend, tendency, momentum"
    },
    {
      "question": "競争心",
      "answer": "きょうそうしん",
      "meaning": "competitive spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "畑違い",
      "answer": "はたけちがい",
      "meaning": "out of one's line, out of one's field"
    },
    {
      "question": "日進月歩",
      "answer": "にっしんげっぽ",
      "meaning": "steady progress, rapid advance"
    }
  ]}